<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>ionic framework Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<atom:link href="/blog/tag/ionic-framework/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/tag/ionic-framework/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:35:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/cropped-logo-1-rb-32x32.png</url>
	<title>ionic framework Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/tag/ionic-framework/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ionic Application Development &#8211; Pros And Cons</title>
		<link>/blog/ionic-application-development-pros-and-cons/</link>
					<comments>/blog/ionic-application-development-pros-and-cons/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ionic Framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cons]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pros]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web app]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6366</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Businesses worldwide desire an advanced mobile app on their Android and iOS platforms to serve their company. Most of them are caught in the middle where they have difficulty selecting the ideal technologies like ionic, hybrid, native for themselves. Each approach to technology and development has its pros and cons, from which you have to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/ionic-application-development-pros-and-cons/">Ionic Application Development &#8211; Pros And Cons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Businesses worldwide desire an advanced mobile app on their Android and iOS platforms to serve their company. Most of them are caught in the middle where they have difficulty selecting the ideal technologies like ionic, hybrid, native for themselves. </p>



<p>Each approach to technology and development has its pros and cons, from which you have to select the best solution for your company. If you think Ionic is the correct platform application development, below are a few advantages and disadvantages of Ionic development.</p>



<p>Ionic Framework helps us to develop apps using only one codebase for several platforms. Let us learn how it works and what are this solution&#8217;s benefits and downsides. The frameworks are quite popular, however, in this blog, we will focus on the advantages and disadvantages of ionic application development. Let&#8217;s get right in with that statement!</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><br><strong>What is an Ionic Application?</strong></p>



<p>It is used to build <a href="https://hasotech.com/why-we-love-hybrid-mobile-app-development/">hybrid mobile apps </a>using the Open Source Software Development Kit(SDK). It is fully Apache Cordova and Angular based on this ionic framework. More specifically, Ionic is an npm module that requires Node JS to be installed.</p>



<p>The conditions for building these applications are excellent HTML, CSS and JavaScript commands. Because of their suitable properties and usefulness, many developers today opt for ionic frameworks. The main objective is to construct a hybrid mobile app in ionic framework development.</p>



<p>Hybrid applications provide several advantages compared with native applications, in particular in terms of development time. Essentially, the construction of ionic apps allows the captivating design and soft animations of native mobile components.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center has-black-color has-text-color has-large-font-size"><strong><a href="http://Ionic/ Mobile App Developer">Ionic Mobile App Developer</a></strong></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><br><strong>Ionic Applications</strong> <strong>Are</strong></p>



<p><br>●<strong> <a href="https://uptech.team/blog/native-vs-cross-platform-app-development">The cross-platform </a></strong>– single code base for both platforms (except native components)</p>



<p>● <strong>Web-based </strong>– Built using web-views and can be displayed in a browser like PWAs.</p>



<p>● <strong>Access to native API components</strong> – They can access the native device’s cameras, files, and others.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><br><strong>Advantages Of Ionic Application</strong></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>A single codebase across various platforms</strong></p>



<p>It was developed using the Angular and Apache Cordova frame and used as the fundamental technologies for app development HTML 5, CSS, and JavaScript. Alongside the current release of the Ionic, you may utilize Angular with all its advantages and disadvantages for the first time.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Free Open Source Framework</strong></p>



<p>This frame is an open-source framework that is entirely free. Ionic framework applications offer platform-specific, optimized CSS features to match the native appearance of the different mobile operating systems. This Framework offers one of the primary advantages in the provision of CSS, HTML, and JS mobile-optimized code and reducing code rewriting needs.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Cross Mobile App Development</strong></p>



<p>In application development, the development of efficient, compatible, and bespoke apps is of major importance. Ionic integrates with AngularJS, which enhances the interoperability of this code with mobile platforms. Ionic helps to swiftly create apps that make the app more popular and save time and money.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Testing convenience</strong></p>



<p>While Ionic Apps only operate via a review, the browser of the device may be used to test the app. It is much handier because test equipment does not even need to be used to make sure it is all working properly. The same principle applies in the current world to a range of mobile devices.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Appealing Default UI</strong></p>



<p>There are numerous common JavaScript and CSS components in these Framework apps covering many fundamental elements that would like to be developed by a moving app. The menu slides, inputs, buttons, lists, navigation, tab, sliding box, and pop-ups. standard styles are clean and simple, and developers may simply change them by adding CSS classes that have been given by the user to the device.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Quick Development and Time To Market</strong></p>



<p>This development may benefit entrepreneurs and company owners when comparing a mobile app with native apps on both platforms in a short time. Constructing native apps particularly for each platform can take time, which can lead to a market delay and the cost of development of native applications is sometimes costly.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><br><strong>Disadvantages Of Ionic Application</strong></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Performance Issue</strong></p>



<p>The performance of heavy apps is inappropriate for this application. When created with this Framework, apps with heavy realism or heavy graphics might crash.</p>



<p>The major reason behind this is that this application makes its graphics using a browser that does many stages on the screen.</p>



<p>There are, then, study performance optimization strategies to achieve better outcomes if you still want to develop a high-performance application utilizing Ionic.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Security Issues</strong></p>



<p>You must not regard it as a con of this application on your own, but rather the possibility of a hazard with which you have to cope. </p>



<p>Security is a typical problem for the creation of hybrid apps as long as your program can be reversed. Ionic CLI is a prevalent approach since version 4 that makes the code tough for hackers to understand.</p>



<p> But you must also realize that there is no code uglification when you use Angular CLI or earlier versions of Ionic. The code will have to be Uglified by your developers yourself.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Dependency on Plugins</strong></p>



<p>Even Ionic app development firms would admit that they must rely on plugins to have access to native features. You won&#8217;t be able to locate a corresponding plugin in the ionic toolset in some situations.</p>



<p>To build a plugin for very specialized features and functions, you must use the Ionic App development company. </p>



<p>If there is no plug-in, you will be able to discover a module most commonly. You&#8217;d probably have to make something that&#8217;s not in store with the aid of a native developer.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Hot Reloading not Available</strong></p>



<p>To make modifications to the application code, this platform employs a variety of approaches. Hot reloading is regarded as a vital characteristic in the software engineering industry. </p>



<p>Because it allows you to make changes without having to refresh the entire program. It takes some getting accustomed to because it does not support hot reloading and instead relies on live reloading. </p>



<p>When you make changes, live reloading will refresh the whole app to make the changes active. That implies that whenever your developers wish to make changes, their program will be restarted.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><strong>conclusion</strong></p>



<p>For your development, you have reviewed the pros and cons of utilizing this framework. Finally, it is crucial to have your application supported and problems solved on time by the proper Ionic application development firm.</p>



<p><em>If you are looking to<a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"> hire an ionic application developer for your application</a>, you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/ionic-application-development-pros-and-cons/">Ionic Application Development &#8211; Pros And Cons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/ionic-application-development-pros-and-cons/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pros And Cons Of Hybrid Mobile App Development</title>
		<link>/blog/pros-and-cons-of-hybrid-mobile-app-development/</link>
					<comments>/blog/pros-and-cons-of-hybrid-mobile-app-development/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cross platform mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ionic Framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web app]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6377</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New heights have reached the evolution of customized app creation. Not just smartphones and tablets, but also other user devices and smart gadgets, are available for development. Time has become a requirement for cross-platform, hybrid, and native application development, which enables companies to produce more efficient goods. While native applications offer numerous benefits, the popularity [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/pros-and-cons-of-hybrid-mobile-app-development/">Pros And Cons Of Hybrid Mobile App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>New heights have reached the evolution of customized app creation. Not just smartphones and tablets, but also other user devices and smart gadgets, are available for development. Time has become a requirement for cross-platform, hybrid, and native application development, which enables companies to produce more efficient goods. </p>



<p>While native applications offer numerous benefits, the popularity of hybrid mobile applications has grown. It&#8217;s due to its flexibility on many platforms. This idea leads to the development of a single application for many platforms. In addition, these apps make reserving a position in the app store market somewhat faster.</p>



<p>Those platform frameworks are extremely popular however, the advantage and disadvantages of hybrid mobile apps will be discussed in this article. Let&#8217;s get right in with that statement!</p>



<h2 style="font-size:35px">What Is a Hybrid Application?</h2>



<p>A <strong>hybrid application </strong>allows the same software to be installed and even execute on different browsers in different operating systems like Android, iOS, Windows, and so on.</p>



<p>The use of a third-party <a href="https://medium.com/flutterdevs/hybrid-apps-the-future-of-mobile-technology-259bac9a985f">hybrid platform</a> is the development of a hybrid app or hybrid strategy. Third-party examples include React Native, PhoneGap, Ionic, Cordoba, or Xamarin. You may also use web technologies to create the app (HTML, CSS, and Javascript).</p>



<p>The development of this mobile app is primarily a way to build a mobile application utilizing a single code base for several platforms, such as Android and iOS. In this way, development expenses are dramatically reduced. On the other side though, there are certain advantages and disadvantages to this app creation.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:30px"><strong>Pros Of Hybrid Mobile Application</strong></p>



<p><strong>Lower Development Costs</strong></p>



<p>The creation of hybrid apps has proven 30% cheaper compared to the native application development strategy. The hybrid method means that the developers just require an Android and iOS project. However, the expense of maintaining the mobile app on both platforms is increasing as the requirement for customization rises.</p>



<p><strong>Easy To Maintain</strong></p>



<p>The simpler maintenance of these mobile applications also benefits. For native applications, new versions need to be developed by the development teams. In addition, with each new version release, consumers will need to upgrade their apps. This app skips versioning and facilitates app maintenance in real-time, as it updates a web page.</p>



<p><strong>Easy Scaling</strong></p>



<p>Scale hybrid programs to a number of devices and OSes is extremely simple. That&#8217;s because web technology on all platforms is nearly 100% the same. This allows the code to be reused easily without any need to recompile the app at all.</p>



<p><strong>Offline Support</strong></p>



<p>The lack of offline support often implies that mobile applications suffer from restrictions. It is difficult for firms who serve clients in rural areas or places where connection to the Internet is a challenge. Statistics show that 70% of users quit an app because it takes too much loading time. One of the advantages of this application is its offline accessibility. The end-users thereby have continuous access to the data without any performance breakdowns.</p>



<p><strong>Support for Cloud &amp; Enterprise-Level Solutions</strong></p>



<p>The Exchange Integration Code may be simply included in the cloud in this framework such as Ionic, Titanium, and PhoneGap. These frameworks are essentially simple to utilize, helping developers update program features, aesthetics, and validity. This allows developers to integrate hybrid applications easily with well-known cloud platforms such as Salesforce and AWS.</p>



<p><strong>Improved Performance</strong></p>



<p>Like native applications, this app provides excellent speed and performance. In fact, they are significantly quicker than advanced and responsive applications in some situations. The reason for this is that there is no reliance on network connectivity and even on apps with more users on all devices is greater.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center has-black-color has-text-color has-large-font-size"><strong><a href="https://hasotech.com/10-quick-tips-for-hybrid-mobile-app-developers/">10 Quick Tips for Hybrid Mobile App Developers</a></strong></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:30px"><strong>Cons Of Hybrid Mobile Application</strong></p>



<p><strong>UX</strong></p>



<p>UX is really concerned with these applications. A hybrid application can never deliver a totally native experience for users. Native applications employ user-friendly system interface components, may produce a meaningful solution, and can contribute to maintaining the entire workflow. Without compromising performance, this cannot be accomplished with a hybrid app. Better UX enables increased consumer participation and the app&#8217;s future.</p>



<p><strong>Limited capabilities</strong></p>



<p>Due to the nature of the design of this mobile app, plugins allow you to use the integrated device capabilities. A method&#8217;s drawback is that these are outdated or unlikely to be trustworthy. In addition, if there are no prepared solutions that allow you to have access to a specific element of the device functionality, developers may require plug-ins alone.</p>



<p><strong>Long Wait for New Features</strong></p>



<p>Whenever Apple and Google release a new feature for iOS and Android platforms, hybrid app developers need some time to add support to the new feature. This is because new SDKs are available in the native apps much more quickly than the multifunctional framework. If you have developed your mobile apps with a native approach, it provides your rivals an edge over you.</p>



<p><strong>Design</strong></p>



<p>Design problems remain a consideration as many OSes work differently. The designer must thus change the look according to different operating systems. This might compel us to challenge ourselves in the process of mending. In hybrid applications the breadth of visual and graphical representation is limited.</p>



<p><strong>Poor user experience</strong></p>



<p>This needs to be high irrespective of what you want: a hybrid app or a native app. Unfortunately, the experience of the user is not a strong part of the hybrid apps because the interface should meet in the middle both for iOS and Android platforms. If you concentrate too much on Android, for iOS users, the experience will be poorer and vice versa.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:30px"><strong><a href="https://hasotech.com/secrets-successful-hybrid-mobile-apps/">Secrets of the Successful Hybrid Mobile Apps</a></strong></p>



<h4>Conclusion&nbsp;</h4>



<p>Considering everything, whether or not you should go down to one thing with the construction of hybrid mobile apps. For companies to gain a competitive edge, hybrid mobile applications are crucial. Knowledge and experience in the development of mobile multi-platform applications.</p>



<p><em>If you are looking to</em><a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"><em> hire a hybrid mobile application developer for your application</em></a><em>, you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.&nbsp;</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/pros-and-cons-of-hybrid-mobile-app-development/">Pros And Cons Of Hybrid Mobile App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/pros-and-cons-of-hybrid-mobile-app-development/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Progressive Web App Advantages And Disadvantages</title>
		<link>/blog/progressive-web-app-advantages-and-disadvantages/</link>
					<comments>/blog/progressive-web-app-advantages-and-disadvantages/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cross platform mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ionic Framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[JavaScript]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[javascript]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PWA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web app]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6391</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Customers nowadays should be able to provide the best mobile experience for their visitors. Some companies thus opt not to apply native. We shall present another new technology called Progressive Web Apps in this post (PWAs). We discover how Progressive Web App operates, how they overcome the problems and weaknesses of PWA applications. Progressive web [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/progressive-web-app-advantages-and-disadvantages/">Progressive Web App Advantages And Disadvantages</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Customers nowadays should be able to provide the best mobile experience for their visitors. Some companies thus opt not to apply native. We shall present another new technology called Progressive Web Apps in this post (PWAs). We discover how Progressive Web App operates, how they overcome the problems and weaknesses of PWA applications.</p>



<p>Progressive web apps (PWAs) are a fascinating technology that can revolutionize the way we create mobile and online applications. Some people may suggest though that PWA is only a website that&#8217;s turned into a mobile app, while some people argue about its capacity, safety, and performance.</p>



<p>So, This article explains the <strong>pros and cons of Progressive web apps</strong>, useful for your future web and mobile apps.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:33px"><strong>What Is Progressive Web App?</strong></p>



<p>The progressive web app provides a user-like mobile experience. Therefore, the UX is tailored for the PWA device to provide the greatest information and features.</p>



<p>PWA is accessed by web users to enable consumers access to important native features, such as mobile home screen application, offline access, PWA notices of push</p>



<p>PWA allows web apps to load, synchronize and smoothly execute things when no network is present while giving your users a native experience.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:30px"><strong>Advantages Of Progressive Web App</strong></p>



<p><strong>PWAs are cheaper than other apps</strong></p>



<p>Material has to be generated only once, which saves time and money by making content for iOS, Android and a website individually. In addition, PWAs need not be updated (some find this feature specifically cool). No new information needs to be downloaded by users. You don&#8217;t have to worry about their development if a PWA is operating.</p>



<p><strong>Reliable</strong></p>



<p>When loading, the app should be bright and should be shut and open if there is not a network or a relatively low-speed network like 2G. Google discovered if the page was loaded longer than 3 seconds, that 53% of people left the website.</p>



<p><strong>User friendly</strong></p>



<p>You don&#8217;t depend on app stores with PWAs. Search engines and other platforms can find PWAs. You may also provide a PWA on social networks, on your homepage, or through another element of your ecosystem. However, app stores offer the benefit of being able to reach a wide public in one shot.</p>



<p><strong>Installable</strong></p>



<p>If we want to bring web apps closer to native applications, they must be installed and reside with other native applications on the home screen, so that the user can use PWA with only one click.</p>



<p><strong>Splash Screen</strong></p>



<p>Adds a splash screen upon starting the app to the progressive Web App. That makes the PWA more resemble a native application.</p>



<p><strong>Highly engage-able</strong></p>



<p>Users should remain engaged with the app. PWA offers features such as push notifications to help users glorify their commitment, home screen icon, the full screen, and offline-first app.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:25px"><strong>Disadvantage Of Progressive Web App</strong></p>



<p><strong>Drains battery power</strong></p>



<p>Since the phones have to work harder to comprehend the code, as they are written in complicated codes. This is why PWAs use more battery compared to native applications. So, consumers don&#8217;t worry about their battery life anymore and may not have to download such an application.</p>



<p><strong>Unable to access various device features&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>PWAs do not have access to numerous functionalities on your smartphone, therefore they are behind native applications. No access to NFC devices and also Bluetooth devices, sophisticated camera settings and so much more is available to PWAs. This means that the application is less than optimal for users.</p>



<p><strong>No access to app stores</strong></p>



<p>You are not exposed in an Apple or Android application store as a corporation if you build a <a href="https://medium.com/weekly-webtips/create-a-progressive-web-app-a-quick-tutorial-7e3b4e9c040a">PWA</a>. Apps are frequently identified since they appear on one of the renowned app marketplaces. Therefore, it is a significant drawback that this &#8220;springboard&#8221; cannot be used by a wider public.</p>



<p><strong>Functionalities&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Fewer and consequently less UX functionality. These web apps offer less functionality, unlike native apps. On Apple devices, iOS does not support complete PWAs functionality.&nbsp;</p>



<p>This means that many users have restricted choices for PWAs, which is a pity. A lack of experience in UX (user experience) is a genuine loss at least as important in a world as the marketing of the product itself.</p>



<p><strong>Lesser technical option</strong></p>



<p>It is not possible to apply to PWAs all technical alternatives, such as Bluetooth or Near Field Communication (NFC). This implies that the applications you may have for your application are restricted. The question is whether PWAs can also make use of other future advances.</p>



<h4 style="font-size:22px">Conclusion</h4>



<p>Using the Progressive Web App you have read the benefits and cons for development. In the end, it is vital that you have your application supported and solved problems on time by the proper PWA app development firm.</p>



<p><em>If you are looking to</em><a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"><em> hire an application developer for your application,</em></a><em> you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/progressive-web-app-advantages-and-disadvantages/">Progressive Web App Advantages And Disadvantages</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/progressive-web-app-advantages-and-disadvantages/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>10 Quick Tips for Hybrid Mobile App Developers</title>
		<link>/blog/10-quick-tips-for-hybrid-mobile-app-developers/</link>
					<comments>/blog/10-quick-tips-for-hybrid-mobile-app-developers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 06:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cross platform mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=5949</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/10-quick-tips-for-hybrid-mobile-app-developers/">10 Quick Tips for Hybrid Mobile App Developers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p>Though <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/hybrid-mobile-app-development-considered-underrated/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hybrid Mobile App development considered underrated</a>, There are still many Hybrid Mobile apps are being developed. Being Hybrid Mobile App Developers, <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/why-we-love-hybrid-mobile-app-development/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">we love Hybrid Mobile App Development.</a> There are many popular apps like Amazon, Uber, Evernote, Facebook etc., The frameworks used to develop Hybrid apps makes Hybrid Mobile app developers easy to make it. To develop a successful mobile app, Hybrid Mobile app developers should follow some <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/secrets-successful-hybrid-mobile-apps/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">secret methods</a>. Though there are many frameworks available to develop Hybrid Mobile apps like <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/ionic-mobile-app-developer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Ionic Framework</a>, There are some tips for Hybrid Mobile App developers to follow.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Choose the Right Framework</h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>When going with Hybrid Mobile app development, Choosing the right framework to develop is very important. There are many frameworks available. Some of them are Ionic Framework, React Native, Xamarin, PhoneGap etc., The very confusion moment is choosing between Ionic Framework or React Native. Ionic Framework is on Angular 4 and React Native is on React js. Since both are booming in the market, It&#8217;s hard to choose the right one.</li>
<li>Anyways, The purpose of developing the Hybrid Mobile App can define it. If you are looking to develop both Web and Mobile app, Then our suggestion is to go with Ionic Framework. Since it is on Angular JS which can be used in both Web and Mobile App, Number of resources to be used can be reduced.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h4><a href="https://www.web.hasotech.com/why-we-love-hybrid-mobile-app-development/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">We Love Hybrid Mobile App Development</a></h4>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>There is a licensing Problem with React Native. It license says They can make it to full premium version anytime. So before choosing React Native, Make sure you can able to overcome the license problem.</li>
<li>If you are a .NET / C# Developer, Then the only option is Xamarin. Xamarin is a Microsoft product which uses C# as a base language to develop Hybrid Mobile app. Of course, You need Visual Studio tools to complete the development.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Ionic Framework &#8211; Lazy Loading Issue</h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>If you are using Ionic Framework, Then you might be facing Lazy Loading issue in the new version. Still, Ionic Framework is working on it to overcome, There are some ways to fix the issue on our own. Instead of declaring all the Nodule Modules in the Main and pages where the node modules to be implemented. Declare the Node modules only in the pages. As the number of Node Modules increases on the Main page, The Lazy Loading time increases.</li>
<li>It is better to avoid unwanted node modules on the main page.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h4><a href="https://www.web.hasotech.com/not-go-hybrid-mobile-app-development/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Don’t go with Hybrid Mobile App Development</a></h4>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Choosing the right Plugins</h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>When we come to Hybrid Mobile App development, Definitely it is going to be on both Android and iOS and sometimes in Windows. While deploying the app to different platforms Plugins may get conflict. Some plugins may support only in Android and not on iOS.</li>
<li>Before choosing a plugin to implement the native function in Mobile App, Make sure it supports in all the platforms.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Checklist for Hybrid Mobile App Developers</h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>Before choosing Hybrid App, Make sure the requirement can be done in Hybrid. If there are more native functions or if the app is very complex, It is suggested to go with Native. But still, if you want to go with Hybrid, Then make sure the app is being developed with proper performance check.</li>
<li>Inspect the App in chrome browser and check for Network and console logs. Try creating the apps without any error in console logs. As the error increases, It may affect the performance.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3><a href="https://www.web.hasotech.com/hybridmobileapp/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hybrid Mobile App Development </a></h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>Make proper performance check in the browser and Mobile App testing before deploying in Play store or App store.</li>
<li>If the mobile app is targeted for lower versions of Android or iOS, Then Hybrid App is not the right choice. Hybrid Apps are meant for Android Lollipop versions and above and iOS 10. Though it supports from Jellybean, It is suggested to with Lollipop target.</li>
</ul>
<p>If you are still looking for any support to know more about Hybrid Mobile app development, Reach our <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/contact-us/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Free consultation team</a> for more details.</p>
<p><strong>Feel free to share your reviews over comments.</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/10-quick-tips-for-hybrid-mobile-app-developers/">10 Quick Tips for Hybrid Mobile App Developers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/10-quick-tips-for-hybrid-mobile-app-developers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why We Love Hybrid Mobile App Development</title>
		<link>/blog/why-we-love-hybrid-mobile-app-development/</link>
					<comments>/blog/why-we-love-hybrid-mobile-app-development/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 06:04:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hasotech.com/?p=2412</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/why-we-love-hybrid-mobile-app-development/">Why We Love Hybrid Mobile App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p>We have been talking Hybrid Mobile App development in <a href="http://www.hasotech.com/blog/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">many articles</a>. You might be wondering what&#8217;s in Hybrid Mobile App Development and what makes <a href="http://www.hasotech.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Hasoians</a> to write more articles on it. Hybrid technologies and it&#8217;s supportive on different platforms makes best.  Sorry, Not different platforms, It&#8217;s on all the platforms.</p>
<p>Hybrid Application development always reduces the development time and cost which made many of our clients beneficiary. And recent updates of Hybrid Application development makes deployment on Web and as Desktop Applications too.</p>
<h3>What can a Hybrid Mobile App do?</h3>
<p>The same thing as explained in other articles before. With Hybrid Mobile App development we can able to deploy on different platforms. Oh, wait, not only on web platforms, Now we can able to deploy it as Desktop Application and Web Application.</p>
<h4 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/secrets-successful-hybrid-mobile-apps/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Secrets of the Successful Hybrid Mobile Apps</a></h4>
<p>Progressive Web Apps are the next generation of web applications. Since the usage of mobile phones has been increased drastically. All the web applications are being developed with complete mobile optimized. But making the UI (User Interface) alone as mobile-optimized is not enough. There are lots of things to be considered for making a Mobile Optimized Web applications and that comes with Progressive Web Apps.</p>
<p>So what? <strong>Can a Hybrid Mobile App development help to make a Progressive Web Apps?</strong></p>
<p>Yes of course, why not? Hybrid apps are web nature.</p>
<h3>Hybrid Mobile App as Desktop App?</h3>
<p>And again the same answer, Why not? There are many Hybrid Desktop existing but the beauty part is. When you can deploy the code that you made for mobile application as a Desktop application. Hybrid Mobile App development can make it.</p>
<h3>What can we deploy with Hybrid Mobile App Development?</h3>
<p>Here we go with a list of applications what we can deploy with Hybrid Mobile App Development.</p>
<h4 class="stripe_2" style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/double-your-profit-with-mobile-app-for-blog/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Double Your Profit With Mobile App for Blog</a></h4>
<ul>
<li>Android Mobile and Tablet Applications</li>
<li>iOS Mobile and iPad Applications</li>
<li>Windows Mobile Applications</li>
<li>Windows Desktop Applications</li>
<li>Progressive Web Applications</li>
<li>Universal Windows Applications</li>
</ul>
<h3>Does Hybrid Mobile App Development support Native Mobile Functions?</h3>
<p>One of the reasons why some hesitate to go with Hybrid Mobile App development is, worrying about native functions. Like NativeMobile Application Development uses libraries to access native functions like camera, Bluetooth, NFC, Fingerprint etc.,  Hybrid Mobile App development is with many plugins which help to access all the native functions.</p>
<p>So, No worries about using Native functions in Hybrid Apps.</p>
<h3>What about Hybrid Mobile App Performance?</h3>
<p>Another main reason, Why some developers hesitate to use Hybrid platforms. When we compare the performance of Native Mobile Application and Hybrid Mobile Application, Always native performance is great. But it doesn&#8217;t mean that Hybrid Mobile app performance is very low. There might be some milliseconds lags between a Native and Hybrid Mobile applications. But is it possible to develop a Good standard application?  Experienced Hybrid Mobile app developer can make it.</p>
<h4 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/not-go-hybrid-mobile-app-development/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Don’t go with Hybrid Mobile App Development</a></h4>
<p>There are many tech giants using Hybrid platforms to develop mobile applications. Like Instagram, Facebook, Evernote, Twitter etc., At the end, Don&#8217;t hesitate to use Hybrid Mobile App development platforms. Make a small research on your own and get to know more about it.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://www.hasotech.com/hybridmobileapp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Stop wasting your time, Check this out </a></h3>
<p>Feel free to share your view on Hybrid Mobile App Development and we are happy to respond to your comments.</p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/why-we-love-hybrid-mobile-app-development/">Why We Love Hybrid Mobile App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/why-we-love-hybrid-mobile-app-development/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Is Hybrid Mobile App Development Considered Underrated</title>
		<link>/blog/hybrid-mobile-app-development-considered-underrated/</link>
					<comments>/blog/hybrid-mobile-app-development-considered-underrated/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 08:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hasotech.com/?p=2364</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/hybrid-mobile-app-development-considered-underrated/">Why Is Hybrid Mobile App Development Considered Underrated</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p><span style="font-family: 'times new roman', times, serif; font-size: 14pt;">The scope of Mobile App Development has been increasing day by day. There are Billions of Applications in Google Play store and Millions of application in App store. And many of them are in Hybrid Mobile App Development Platforms. The main reason for such amount of application in Google Play store and App store is the simplicity of Application development. Developing application has become easier one and also everyone started expressing their ideas through mobile apps. There are many technologies available to develop a mobile application. and certain drag and drop tools helps to develop a mobile application without a single line of code. </span></p>
<h4 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/hybrid-mobile-application-development/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Get to know more about Hybrid Mobile Application Development</a></h4>
<p><span style="font-family: 'times new roman', times, serif; font-size: 14pt;">Though there are many technologies available to develop a mobile application. Hybrid Mobile Application Development is one of the trending development platforms. With Native Mobile Application Development. One can able to develop a mobile app for one platform either on Android or iOS. But With Hybrid Mobile Application Development. It has made easy to develop the application and deploy it on different platforms with a single code. </span></p>
<h3>What is Hybrid Mobile App Development</h3>
<p><span style="font-family: 'times new roman', times, serif; font-size: 14pt;">If you can able to deploy an application on multiple platforms like Android, iOS, Windows etc., with a single code. For Example, If we are about to develop <strong><a href="https://www.web.hasotech.com/how-to-get-free-magento-2-mobile-app/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Magento E-commerce Mobile Application</a> </strong>in Android iOS, Then probably Hybrid Mobile Application might be the right choice.  With this we can able to deploy the application on both Android and iOS. Whereas if we choose to go with Native Mobile Application development. Then both Android and iOS have to be developed separately. And also the cost and time of developing Native Mobile application would be high. </span></p>
<h4 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.web.hasotech.com/whats-crazy-mobile-app-development/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">What’s crazy on Mobile App Development</a></h4>
<h3>Why Hybrid Mobile App Development is underrated!!</h3>
<p><span style="font-family: 'times new roman', times, serif; font-size: 14pt;">And here we come to core concept of the article. Why Is Hybrid Mobile App Development Considered Underrated?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'times new roman', times, serif; font-size: 14pt;">The main reason is the Frameworks. Ther are many frameworks available to develop Hybrid Mobile applications like Ionic Framework, React Native, Xamarin, Titanium, and the mother of all frameworks, PhoneGap. Though there are many frameworks, All the frameworks are not good as to develop a standard application. There is licensing problem on using React Native since Facebook has said that, they will start charging for it anytime. Intel HTML5 fails to provide proper native functions and No updates with PhoneGap. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'times new roman', times, serif; font-size: 14pt;">These issues made Hybrid Mobile App Development Considered Underrated. But still, there are some good frameworks like <a href="http://ionicframework.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ionic Framework,</a> which provides regular updates and many trusted companies are using it. There are many certain ways to follow to develop a standard Hybrid Mobile Application. </span></p>
<h4 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/ionic-mobile-app-developer/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">You may check about Ionic Mobile App Developer</a></h4>
<p><span style="font-family: 'times new roman', times, serif; font-size: 14pt;">If you are looking for any support on Hybrid Mobile App Development, Feel free to <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/contact-us/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>reach our consulting team</strong></a> or comment below. </span></p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/hybrid-mobile-app-development-considered-underrated/">Why Is Hybrid Mobile App Development Considered Underrated</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/hybrid-mobile-app-development-considered-underrated/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Secrets of the Successful Hybrid Mobile Apps</title>
		<link>/blog/secrets-successful-hybrid-mobile-apps/</link>
					<comments>/blog/secrets-successful-hybrid-mobile-apps/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 12:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ionic Framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hasotech.com/?p=2345</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/secrets-successful-hybrid-mobile-apps/">Secrets of the Successful Hybrid Mobile Apps</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p>Mobile apps are one of the best ways for making money. But not all the business apps or Hybrid Mobile apps are successful. If you are looking to develop a successful mobile app, that too in the Hybrid platform.  Then you must know these secrets of the successful Hybrid Mobile Apps. We have gone through several Hybrid Mobile apps that are running successfully. And we came up with some secrets that actually made those apps successful.</p>
<h2>Choosing the Right Platform</h2>
<p>When it comes to Hybrid Mobile App Development, choosing the right framework is the most important one. There are many frameworks available and PhoneGap is the mother of all. However, PhoneGap has become outdated one and there are many new frameworks with more features. Some of them are Ionic Framework, Xamarin, Unity, Titanium. Most of the Hybrid apps are powered by Cordova backbone. Out of all these frameworks, Ionic Framework is said to be the best one which provides many components and plugins. If you are a c# Developer then you may go with Xamarin or Unity. And Unity is must if you are looking at developing games.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/get-your-virtual-reality-mobile-application/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Get your Virtual Reality Mobile Application</a></h3>
<h2>Designing Hybrid Mobile Apps</h2>
<p>The more the app is user-friendly with good user experience, The more that app will be a successful one. Though there are many ready designs are available. It is better to go with a unique design which is impressive. Ionic Framework is providing many UI components which made the designing bit easier. The more we make easy to use the app and understand the concept of the app, The more chance for the success we will get.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/not-go-hybrid-mobile-app-development/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Don’t go with Hybrid Mobile App Development</a></h3>
<h2>Why Hybrid Mobile Apps</h2>
<p>This might be the first question while reading this article. Though there are native platforms available for developing Android and iOS applications. There must be a special reason to choose Hybrid mobile platform. If you are looking to make the application on a different platform in short period of time. And also in low budget, then the Hybrid platform is the best one.</p>
<p>There are many constraints to be considered before going with Hybrid Mobile apps platform. Feel free to <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/contact-us/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">contact us</a> for a free consultation on developing with Hybrid mobile apps.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/cross-platform-mobile-app-development-things-to-know/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cross Platform Mobile App Development – Things To Know</a></h3>
<h2>Choosing the right Niche</h2>
<p>Focusing on particular Niche will increase the chance of getting the app success. The more the app solves a particular problem, The more the app will get succeed. Most of the successful apps are concentrating on a very specific niche and Solving a specific problem. Also making the app more interactive and entertainment will get more user engagement.</p>
<h2>Making the Revenue Model</h2>
<p>The revenue model and the amount of revenue of an application decides the success of an app. The more revenue it gets, The more success the app is. Concentrating more on attracting a huge range of customers automatically increase revenue. More customers =  More revenue. With the ads in free app version, or launching business driving model with app surely will help for more revenue.</p>
<p>Shameless marketing is more important. After making the app with perfect UI and good revenue model, Marketing has to be done in proper way. The amount and time used to develop the application, Double it in marketing for a good reach.</p>
<p>Feel free to share your reviews over comments and <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/contact-us/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reach us</a> for any clarifications or consultations.</p>
<h4 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/double-your-profit-with-mobile-app-for-blog/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Double Your Profit With Mobile App for Blog</a></h4>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/secrets-successful-hybrid-mobile-apps/">Secrets of the Successful Hybrid Mobile Apps</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/secrets-successful-hybrid-mobile-apps/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cross Platform Mobile App Development &#8211; Things To Know</title>
		<link>/blog/cross-platform-mobile-app-development-things-to-know/</link>
					<comments>/blog/cross-platform-mobile-app-development-things-to-know/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 13:46:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ionic Framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hasotech.com/?p=2311</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/cross-platform-mobile-app-development-things-to-know/">Cross Platform Mobile App Development &#8211; Things To Know</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p><span style="font-family: verdana, geneva, sans-serif; font-size: 12pt;">The scope of Cross Platform Mobile App Development has been increasing. And the range of developing multi-platform applications is also increasing. Cross platform mobile app development is not something web app. Creating web app is different and Creating Hybrid or cross platform mobile app development. HTML5 app development is basically mentioned as a Web app. And using some frameworks to develop the mobile app is different. Before proceeding with Cross platform Mobile app, Make sure you are aware of these things.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-family: verdana, geneva, sans-serif;">What is Cross Platform Mobile App Development</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-family: verdana, geneva, sans-serif; font-size: 12pt;">A cross platform mobile app development is the development of Mobile apps. These apps can be deployed on multiple platforms like Android, iOS, Windows, Blackberry etc.,  The development of mobile application over multiple platforms may cost more time and money.  Whereas in Cross Platform Mobile App Development, This can be done at the cost and time of developing a single platform app. HTML5 apps are web apps, and if the application is developed using any frameworks which can be mentioned as cross platform mobile app.</span></p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><span style="font-family: verdana, geneva, sans-serif;"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/not-go-hybrid-mobile-app-development/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Don’t go with Hybrid Mobile App Development</a></span></h3>
<h2><span style="font-family: verdana, geneva, sans-serif;">What all the frameworks available for Cross Platform Mobile App Development</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-family: verdana, geneva, sans-serif; font-size: 12pt;">When it comes to choosing the right technology and frameworks for developing cross platform mobile apps. It is difficult to choose the right one. After going through certain research process we came up with some frameworks which can be used.</span></p>
<h3><span style="font-family: verdana, geneva, sans-serif;">Ionic Framework</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-family: verdana, geneva, sans-serif; font-size: 12pt;">Ionic Framework is one of the popular Cross-platform app development frameworks. This framework has been coming up with regular updates with lots of bug fixes. The recent launch iPhone X screen can be supported by this framework.  This app is completely based on Angular which is well-grooming technology and it is powered by cordova.</span></p>
<h3><span style="font-family: verdana, geneva, sans-serif;">Xamarin</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-family: verdana, geneva, sans-serif; font-size: 12pt;">As like Ionic Framework, Xamarin is one of the best frameworks for developing the cross-platform mobile app. Xamarin is purely based on C# Microsoft technology. If you are looking to move to enterprise edition app then you may go with Xamarin rather than going with Open source technology.</span></p>
<h3><span style="font-family: verdana, geneva, sans-serif;">Unity</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-family: verdana, geneva, sans-serif; font-size: 12pt;">Unity Frameworks are for Game Developers. If your application is going to use many animated modules. If you are planning to develop a game on multiple platforms, Then unity is the best choice.</span></p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><span style="font-family: verdana, geneva, sans-serif;"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/double-your-profit-with-mobile-app-for-blog/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Double Your Profit With Mobile App for Blog</a></span></h3>
<h2><span style="font-family: verdana, geneva, sans-serif;">Pros and Cons of Cross-Platform Mobile App Development</span></h2>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-family: verdana, geneva, sans-serif; font-size: 12pt;">The biggest advance of going to Cross-Platform Mobile App Development is cost and time. If you are looking to develop the multiplatform app in less time or cost then it is the best choice</span></li>
<li><span style="font-family: verdana, geneva, sans-serif; font-size: 12pt;">In same time if you are looking to the develop mobile app which uses many native functions then it is not recommended</span></li>
<li><span style="font-family: verdana, geneva, sans-serif; font-size: 12pt;">To develop a standard Multi-platform mobile app, experienced developer is needed on cross-platform</span></li>
<li><span style="font-family: verdana, geneva, sans-serif; font-size: 12pt;">Using frameworks to make the mobile app to make the app stronger</span></li>
<li><span style="font-family: verdana, geneva, sans-serif; font-size: 12pt;">Native apps only suit if you are looking to develop a high-performance mobile app with many native functions with a high cost.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-family: verdana, geneva, sans-serif; font-size: 12pt;">If you are looking to develop cross-platform mobile app <a href="http://www.hasotech.com/contact-us/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>utilize our free consultation</strong></a>. Reach us <a href="mailto:info@hasotech.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">info@hasotech.com</a> or contact us.</span></p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><span style="font-family: verdana, geneva, sans-serif;"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/five-things-that-you-never-expect-on-mobile-app-development/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Five Things That You Never Expect On Mobile App Development</a></span></h3>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/cross-platform-mobile-app-development-things-to-know/">Cross Platform Mobile App Development &#8211; Things To Know</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/cross-platform-mobile-app-development-things-to-know/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Double Your Profit With Mobile App for Blog</title>
		<link>/blog/double-your-profit-with-mobile-app-for-blog/</link>
					<comments>/blog/double-your-profit-with-mobile-app-for-blog/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 07:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hasotech.com/?p=2141</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/double-your-profit-with-mobile-app-for-blog/">Double Your Profit With Mobile App for Blog</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<h1>Double Your Profit With Mobile App for Blog</h1>
<p>Blogging is one of the best ways to gain knowledge and earn money. If you are looking this, you might be a blogger looking to earn more money. It&#8217;s easy to get started in blogging but very hard to be in blogging. There may be numerous tricks to earn more money with blogging. But in reality, it is very hard and it sets to few. Most difficult part of blogging is doing SEO and maintaining it for long period. Get rid of all these headaches. Get mobile app for blog and increase your profit.</p>
<h2>Mobile App for Blog</h2>
<p>We have made pretty simple to get a mobile app for blog. A ready-made solution for WordPress blogs. You can get mobile app for blog very easily. We have made the app with super cool mobile features like offline, night mode, easy sharing and more. Are you an Apple fan? Don&#8217;t worry, we provide the app for iOS too. You might be thinking how much do we have to pay to get this Mobile app for blog.  It&#8217;s ZERO cost and completely free. And of course, we expect some return back from your side for the free blog.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/whats-crazy-mobile-app-development/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">What’s crazy on Mobile App Development</a></h3>
<h2>How to get FREE Mobile app for Blog</h2>
<ul>
<li>Go to <a href="http://www.hasotech.com/wp2app" target="_blank" rel="noopener">http://www.hasotech.com/wp2app</a></li>
<li>Click on know more</li>
<li>Fill all the details asked for</li>
<li>Submit the application</li>
</ul>
<p>We will review the application and reach you over email.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/very-easy-to-develop-a-mobile-app/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Very easy to Develop a Mobile App</a></h3>
<h2>Benefits of Having Mobile App for Blog</h2>
<ul>
<li>Double your profit from Web and Mobile app</li>
<li>Engage your viewers with Mobile App</li>
<li>Instant Push Notification on each post publish</li>
<li>One time promotions to get Installs</li>
<li>Get rid of doing SEO regularly to maintain the blog</li>
<li>More custom features</li>
</ul>
<p>You can also check the demo app here <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.wp2app.hasotech" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.wp2app.hasotech</a></p>
<p>Feel free to share your reviews over comments.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/get-your-virtual-reality-mobile-application/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Get your Virtual Reality Mobile Application</a></h3>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/double-your-profit-with-mobile-app-for-blog/">Double Your Profit With Mobile App for Blog</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/double-your-profit-with-mobile-app-for-blog/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Get your Virtual Reality Mobile Application</title>
		<link>/blog/get-your-virtual-reality-mobile-application/</link>
					<comments>/blog/get-your-virtual-reality-mobile-application/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 04:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ionic Framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[virtual reality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hasotech.com/?p=2135</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/get-your-virtual-reality-mobile-application/">Get your Virtual Reality Mobile Application</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<h1>Get your Virtual Reality Mobile Application</h1>
<p><strong>Virtual reality mobile application</strong> has been an emerging technology. Medical, entertainment, gaming, fashion etc., are using Virtual reality technology. Virtual reality uses three-dimensional frames which make a user to feel the objects as real. Just take the users to the virtual world. One of the very best implementations of Virtual reality is E-commerce. If you are in <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/ecommerce-app-development/">E-Commerce business</a> and planning to develop an application. Virtual reality mobile application is the best technology to use. You might be thinking how about a user without virtual reality device. One can use the application in normal mode too.</p>
<h4 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/never-mess-business-mobile-app-development/">Never Mess With Business Mobile App Development</a></h4>
<p>Choosing the right tech stack to develop Virtual Reality Mobile Application is difficult one. The tech stack should be easy and beneficiary. Imagin, developing Web, Android and iOS VR application with same tech stack. With just one single code, Deploy on different platforms. Yes, It&#8217;s Hybrid Virtual Reality Mobile Application.</p>
<h2>Developing Hybrid Virtual Reality Mobile Application</h2>
<p>When it comes to <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/hybrid-mobile-application-development/">Developing Hybrid Mobile Application</a> we prefer <a href="https://www.web.hasotech.com/ionic-mobile-app-developer/">Ionic Framework</a>. Which is well-going technology for Hybrid. To deploy the application in different platform Ionic framework can be used. With single code get the app on Android and iOS and other mobile platforms. Developing Virtual reality mobile application is not possible with the Ionic framework. One of the best part going with Hybrid is, We can use Web Plugins in Mobile Applications. Similarly to develop virtual reality Mobile Application in Hybrid. We are going to use a Web Framework. <strong>aframe.io </strong>for building Virtual Reality Mobile application as well as Web Application.</p>
<h2>Get Started with Virtual Reality Mobile Application</h2>
<p>The installation process for Virtual Reality Mobile Application is very easy. aframe.io is a Javascript framework which obviously supports both on the web and hybrid mobile apps. For developing Virtual Reality Application, Initializing the Javascript file of aframe.io is enough. Check the link for detailed installation steps https://aframe.io/docs/0.7.0/introduction/installation.html</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.web.hasotech.com/whats-crazy-mobile-app-development/">What’s crazy on Mobile App Development</a></h3>
<h2>3D Models for Virtual Reality Mobile application</h2>
<p>3D Frames make best Virtual Reality Application. For a better experience, it must be developed with proper tools. There are many tools available to develop 3D images for Virtual reality.</p>
<p>Places to find 3D models include:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://sketchfab.com/" target="_blank" rel="external noopener">Sketchfab</a></li>
<li><a href="http://clara.io/" target="_blank" rel="external noopener">Clara.io</a></li>
<li><a href="http://archive3d.net/" target="_blank" rel="external noopener">Archive3D</a></li>
<li><a href="https://3dwarehouse.sketchup.com/" target="_blank" rel="external noopener">Sketchup’s 3D Warehouse</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.turbosquid.com/Search/3D-Models/free" target="_blank" rel="external noopener">TurboSquid</a></li>
</ul>
<p>These tools can be used to generate 3D images for developing Virtual reality mobile application.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/very-easy-to-develop-a-mobile-app/">Very easy to Develop a Mobile App</a></h3>
<h2>Integrating aframe.io and Ionic Framework</h2>
<p>To make virtual reality Mobile application, aframe.io should be integrated with Ionic Frameworks. The Ionic framework helps to deploy the application on Android and iOS. To make this happen, Create a new view in Ionic framework application and implement aframe.io application. This would bring the entire Virtual reality mobile application under the Ionic framework.</p>
<p>Now you are with Hybrid Virtual reality mobile application. Share your experience on virtual reality and developing such applications for your business.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/iphone-x-ios-11-mobile-app-development/">iPhone X iOS 11 Mobile App Development</a></h3>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/get-your-virtual-reality-mobile-application/">Get your Virtual Reality Mobile Application</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/get-your-virtual-reality-mobile-application/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: web.hasotech.com @ 2022-10-26 12:08:54 by W3 Total Cache
-->