<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Ecommerce Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<atom:link href="/blog/category/ecommerce/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/category/ecommerce/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 12:37:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/cropped-logo-1-rb-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Ecommerce Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/category/ecommerce/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Is One Page Checkout Better Than Multi-Page</title>
		<link>/blog/is-one-page-checkout-better-than-multi-page/</link>
					<comments>/blog/is-one-page-checkout-better-than-multi-page/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 12:22:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marketplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Multi Vendor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[multi-page checkout]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[one-page checkout]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=7017</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How many people visit your website, but how many converts it, depends not on the success of your eCommerce business. The more conversions you receive, the higher your income and it depends mostly on your page checkout. One of the important phases of the buying experience is the checkout procedure. Of course, bringing people to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/is-one-page-checkout-better-than-multi-page/">Is One Page Checkout Better Than Multi-Page</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>How many people visit your website, but how many converts it, depends not on the success of your eCommerce business. The more conversions you receive, the higher your income and it depends mostly on your page checkout.</p>



<p>One of the important phases of the buying experience is the checkout procedure. Of course, bringing people to your check-out page is never easy, and even if you get them to that stage, many things might arise to prevent them from paying.</p>



<p>For years, e-commerce specialists have been working on optimizing the checkout page. You should use the purchasing behavior of your purchasers to choose the greatest alternative for your buyers. Knowing your target consumers better and running an efficient test is a good thing to set up your various checkout pages.</p>



<p>There is no end to the argument over a one-page checkout vs a multi-page checkout. While several professional eCommerce experts favor a one-page review, some believe it is a superior alternative for a multi-page checkout.</p>



<p>We will compare both approaches in this post to help you choose the one that&#8217;s perfect for you. Let&#8217;s get started.</p>



<h2>One-Page Checkout</h2>



<p><strong>What is One-Page checkout?</strong></p>



<p>All functions and fields of the checkout are shown on one single page using a one-page checkout. This covers all information required for customers to complete their checkout, including billing, delivery address, payment choices, delivery options, and associated fields.</p>



<p>One-page checkout is a standard Magento 2 store model (the standard checkout page), which is very much improved in shopping optimization when compared to Magento 1, as all these stages may now be found in only one page, instead of 6 steps spanning over six pages.</p>



<h3><strong>Benefits of One-Page Checkout</strong></h3>



<p><strong>Quick Checkout</strong></p>



<p>It enables clients to check out rapidly with full checkout information at an early stage. You get rid of clicking repeatedly to get to the next phase (in the event of multi-phase checkout) and may input all your billing, shipping, and payment data on the same page.</p>



<p><strong>Reduce Carts Abandoned</strong></p>



<p>Studies have revealed that 21 percent of online consumers usually give up their carts before the checkout since the shopping site takes too slow to react and is difficult to grasp. You may minimize the abandoned number of cards by expediting the process by having all check-out items on one page and boosting the conversion rate.</p>



<p><strong>Higher Conversion Rates</strong></p>



<p>Statistics suggest that one-page check-outs are probably 10% to 20% more than multi-page checkouts however, this also relies on the sort of items you are marketing. The statistics showed that However, quicker and simpler checkout pages may certainly convert and promote purchase decisions more effectively.</p>



<p><strong>Easy to Understand</strong></p>



<p>A one-stage checkout makes it quick and easy to grasp the design of your website and gives your clients a clear image. It also makes it easier for you to check your data because you do not have to move between pages.</p>



<p><strong>Why You Shouldn’t Adopt One-Page Checkout?</strong></p>



<p><strong>Site speed</strong></p>



<p>It might increase the loading time required for the site than always because it comprises too many components on one page. Shoppers like to buy things quickly, therefore it is a good idea not only to work effectively but also to load your homepage swiftly. Otherwise, we worry you may lose consumers who fear wasting their valuable time.</p>



<p><strong>Limited Analysis</strong></p>



<p>If you use Google Analytics and utilize this tool to monitor your pages, you will not need a one-page checkout. It is difficult to identify with a one-page checkout at what point the client left the process. You can, however, read clearly on which page the consumer exited the purchase cycle using the multi-page checkout.</p>



<h4>Multi-Page Checkout</h4>



<p><strong>What is Multi-Page checkout?</strong></p>



<p>Checkouts multi-step, distribute over multiple pages the checkout procedures. Typically, this sort of checkout demands that customers enter their desired mode of delivery, delivery and billing information, and payment information manually. The full check-out procedure is completed in multiple pages through a multi-page or multi-phase check-out.&nbsp;</p>



<p>To complete the checkout process, customer must provide their data independently on each page. Checkouts of several pages are split into different Web sites, generally from 3 to 4 pages, as opposed to one-page checkout, which has all needed components and data on the same screen.</p>



<h5><strong>Benefits of Multi-Page Checkout</strong></h5>



<p><strong>Clean and Simple Layout</strong></p>



<p>As each page contains a certain type of information alone, input fields are presented in a clean design with fewer embroilments at every phase since the checkout is separated into parts. The consumers will not be overwhelmed, thus. Although it needs more clicks to proceed, it will be less frightening and easier to fill in for certain people.</p>



<p><strong>Good User Experience</strong></p>



<p>The multi-step inspection procedure separates the inspection process into many phases. Each stage includes simply a few fields to cover that can make consumers less frightening. In addition, the progress indicator enables clients to understand how far they have gone in the checkout process and how many further steps the purchase can take.</p>



<p><strong>Better Analytics</strong></p>



<p>Multi-page checkouts help website developers to understand better the behavior of their consumers to evaluate and discover stages through which users exit and abandon carts. This sort of information is very useful in making correct modifications and improving the conversion rates of any online shop.</p>



<p><strong>Higher Security</strong></p>



<p>If the procedure is slower and clients are permitted to fill in step-by-step their information, they will probably be more sure to shop on a website. This sensation is especially essential when customers buy something costly and worthwhile for minor nuances.</p>



<p><strong>Email Collection</strong></p>



<p>The customer’s contact data are collected in the first phase of the multi-stage checkout procedure. Even if the consumer does not finish the checkout, if the first stages have been completed, you will receive emails from potential customers. These emails can be used for advertising emails later.</p>



<p><strong>Why You Shouldn’t Adopt Multi-Page Checkout?</strong></p>



<p><strong>Time-consuming</strong></p>



<p>The consumers need to complete their orders by too many tiny stages instead of completing the check-out in one move. They may not be encouraged to go into another store rather than stay at your place if you&#8217;re in a quick hurry or don&#8217;t have much patience.</p>



<p><strong>Harder to change or correct details&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Since each stage includes various facts on multiple pages, if you wish, it is difficult to correct or modify information. For example, you should go back to update your billing address, if you are about to pay, but find there is a mistake. This might create irritation and the possibility of cart loss.</p>



<h6><strong>Conclusion</strong></h6>



<p>There is no single size suited for every eCommerce website check-out procedure because each site has a diverse mix of consumers and items. The optimal control procedure for your site varies depending on several aspects, including the percentage of repeat purchases, needs for sales funnel analytics, product type, and the amount of information necessary.</p>



<p>The ideal answer is to test the two checkouts A/B and find out if your online shop may be better by taking the one-page or multi-stage checkout procedure.</p>



<p><em>If you are looking to </em><a href="http://hasotech.com/contact-us/"><strong><em>hire an eCommerce application developer for your application</em></strong></a><em>, you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/is-one-page-checkout-better-than-multi-page/">Is One Page Checkout Better Than Multi-Page</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/is-one-page-checkout-better-than-multi-page/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Your eCommerce Site Needs Mobile Application?</title>
		<link>/blog/why-your-ecommerce-site-needs-mobile-application/</link>
					<comments>/blog/why-your-ecommerce-site-needs-mobile-application/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:35:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Needs Of Ecommerce Mobile App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Website]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6342</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For eCommerce companies, the sky is the limit. Today, more than ever, people buy online. All industries worldwide are involved in this assertion. The internet power has enabled you to contact consumers from any device at any time, anyplace. But your sort of gadgets will have a big influence on your success. The full potential [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/why-your-ecommerce-site-needs-mobile-application/">Why Your eCommerce Site Needs Mobile Application?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>For eCommerce companies, the sky is the limit. Today, more than ever, people buy online. All industries worldwide are involved in this assertion. The internet power has enabled you to contact consumers from any device at any time, anyplace. But your sort of gadgets will have a big influence on your success.</p>



<p><br>The full potential of your eCommerce shop with a website alone is never reached. When you study the latest trends in eCommerce, you notice immediately that everything is moving. In this article, we will discuss in detail, the importance of mobile apps to grow an e-commerce business. Take a look.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:23px"><br><strong>Reason Your eCommerce Site Needs Mobile Application</strong></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><br><strong>Easy Accessibility<br></strong></p>



<p>Smartphones are simple to carry, and currently, it&#8217;s a trend that makes mobile app access easier than websites. Mobile applications improve the comfort level by effortlessly linking them to a vital tool for on-the-go interaction with clients.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><br><strong>Direct-to-Customer Marketing Channel<br></strong></p>



<p>Brands must consistently and steadily engage with mobile eCommerce to exploit the potential of connected clients. The mobile trade app not only helps consumers remain linked to the business but also efficiently provides customers with agreements, offers, and promotions.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><br><strong>Shoppers prefer apps to browsers<br></strong></p>



<p>It is not unexpected that you choose to use Mobile applications. Ecommerce apps are considerably easier to use when buying, particularly when you are not visiting an online business on a one-off basis. To begin with, you don&#8217;t have to recall a URL and log in to the shop. Moreover, apps offer superior safety and performance than mobile browsers.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><br><strong>Personalization </strong></p>



<p><br>Use your clients&#8217; information in the application for your benefit. For example, by using priority features and relevant suggestions based on the previous buying, you can enable your consumers to personalize their experience in your business.<br></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><strong>Push notifications</strong></p>



<p>To communicate with your consumers, use push notifications. Notify them or make them know when they wish to return to stock on sales and special offers. Make alerts easier by specifying the name of your users.<br></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><strong>Ecommerce push notification<br></strong></p>



<p>Content exclusive. Implement only mobile offerings available – such as limited discounts or unique rates for applicants. Special incentives motivate your regular clients to download and raise conversion rates.<br></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><strong>Rewards system<br></strong></p>



<p>By creating a fidelity program you may urge your consumers to continue returning. They can be utilized in the form of points for a free item or a significant discount, early access to a new collection, or benefits for future purchases.<br></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><strong>Ecommerce rewards system on the mobile app<br></strong></p>



<p>Support advanced. Good assistance for customers goes much further. Create a strong connection between your shop and your consumers 24 hours a day. Instead of switching to the desktop version, customers should be able to fix their issues via live chat or chat in the app.<br></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><strong>Customer loyalty<br></strong></p>



<p>The key reason to take into account is to develop your mobile app for client loyalty. With all the distractions out there, due to the huge volume of advertising all around us, we eventually lose our effect on clients. It&#8217;s time to establish a true and honest relationship with your customers and make them loyal to your goods and service.<br></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><strong>Apps Referrals<br></strong></p>



<p>Mobile applications make social movement the most effective manner. The applications include common buttons that may be used to disseminate further information. A well-conceived and the effective app can achieve the consumers&#8217; confidence. It may be used to distribute information in this way. Thus, the number of individuals using a certain app might gradually rise.<br></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><a href="https://www.convinceandconvert.com/digital-marketing/improve-user-experience/"><strong>A better and enhanced UX</strong></a><strong><br></strong></p>



<p>A good presentation of e-business helps consumers comprehend the company goal in increasing mobile app marketing. Mobile applications offer considerably better navigation and are now built to take account of the screen size of the user utilizing responsive features. Less distraction and better navigation enable buyers to concentrate more on their items and therefore increase sales growth.<br></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><strong>Lower mobile shopping cart abandonment rate<br></strong></p>



<p>Shopping cart abandonment is a big issue for eCommerce. One thing is to get clients to add things to their carts and another is to take them fully through a checkout. Whereas in the mobile application the delivery and payment information is saved within the system, which enables users to make one-click transactions. This allows consumers, without unwanted distractions, to check out quickly.<br></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><strong>Conclusion</strong></p>



<p><br>We believe that the post will explain why the development of an e-commerce business is important to mobile apps. So, do not wait and start creating a mobile website for eCommerce shopping immediately if you are an eCommerce business owner.</p>



<p><br><em>If you are looking to <strong><a href="http://hasotech.com/contact-us/">hire an eCommerce application developer</a> </strong>for your application, you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/why-your-ecommerce-site-needs-mobile-application/">Why Your eCommerce Site Needs Mobile Application?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/why-your-ecommerce-site-needs-mobile-application/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Facial Recognition Mobile App: How To Built It?</title>
		<link>/blog/facial-recognition-mobile-app-how-to-built-it/</link>
					<comments>/blog/facial-recognition-mobile-app-how-to-built-it/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cross platform mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Neural Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biometric Recognization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Facial Recognization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpenCV Platform]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6381</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Can an app be unlocked with facial recognition? Yes! The revolutionary technologies that have been created are possible. In current days, facial recognition is becoming increasingly common. Facial identification technology fascinates many companies, but it remains unclear how to use the face release function. This article discusses &#8220;How to Build a Facial Recognition mobile app.&#8221; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/facial-recognition-mobile-app-how-to-built-it/">Facial Recognition Mobile App: How To Built It?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Can an app be unlocked with facial recognition? Yes! The revolutionary technologies that have been created are possible.</p>



<p>In current days, facial recognition is becoming increasingly common. Facial identification technology fascinates many companies, but it remains unclear how to use the face release function.</p>



<p>This article discusses &#8220;How to Build a Facial Recognition mobile app.&#8221; However, it is vital to grasp how and how the technology works by implementing it into your mobile solution.</p>



<h2>What Is Facial Recognition Technology?</h2>



<p>Facial recognition is a <a href="https://auth0.com/blog/3-critical-trends-in-biometric-authentication-in-2019/">biometric software</a> function that can identify or check a person uniquely by comparing and analyzing patterns based on the facial features of the individual.</p>



<p>Face recognition is mostly employed for security, but also in other fields of application, there is rising interest. The technology of face recognition has garnered considerable interest since it has the possibility of being used in a variety of applications.</p>



<h3>How does It work?</h3>



<p>Facial detection is the identification procedure for a human face in a scanned picture. Various face recognition techniques exist. The major distinction between all algorithms is that the characteristics are calculated and the data sets comparable with one another.</p>



<p>The entry is a stream of pictures or videos. The output is the item identifying or verifying the picture or video. Facial identification systems often function as follows. The face recognition process is typically characterized as a procedure in five stages:</p>



<ul><li>Facial detection and tracking</li><li>Facial alignment</li><li>Feature extraction</li><li>Feature matching</li><li>Facial recognition</li></ul>



<h3>How To Build Mobile Apps with Facial Recognition?</h3>



<p>There are many methods to build an app with facial recognition. Here is a list of methods like</p>



<ul><li>The OpenCV Platform</li><li>Artificial Neural Network</li></ul>



<p><strong>The OpenCV Platform</strong>&nbsp;</p>



<p>This is the standard platform for developing facial recognition applications and supports the implementation of computer vision and machine learning for the applications. It is a platform for object detection that uses several algorithms to identify all sorts of things. OpenCV is ideally suited for facial recognition and detection.</p>



<p>OpenCV is a library comprising more than 2,5 thousand properly modified, contemporary, and traditional algorithms. The emphasis of the study is computer vision and machine learning and may be used to recognize pictures, monitor movements, extract 3D object models, and many more in equal measure. OpenCV is a BSD product licensed that simplifies the programming effort considerably.</p>



<p>Facial recognition is supported with ready-to-use settings. The program is educated for the process of detection and positive photos are incorporated to assist optimize the images. There are many characteristics, scales, and weights that allow marketers to study the picture to create a variety of training image sets.</p>



<p>The OpenCV is a great framework for incorporating face recognition in your application. But in real-time applications, it is not suited. The greatest way to work against a fixed image is to use social networks or social media apps. It cannot identify pictures in real-time, taking lighting and other aspects into account.</p>



<p><strong>Artificial Neural Network</strong></p>



<p>Neural artificial networks are the most common facial recognition approach. They are used for extracting features and making decisions. A network based on a multi-lag perceptron, which permits the input picture categorization in accordance with the pre-trained network, is one of the most commonly utilized choices.</p>



<p>A series of learning examples are provided for neural networks. The neural network automatically identifies important functions during training, evaluates their significance, and creates connections between them. The trained neural network is expected to be able to generalize the expertise obtained in the course of the training to unfamiliar pictures.</p>



<p>However, because the trained neural networks were very time demanding, facial recognition results were fairly good and error rates decreased. The major difficulty is the addition of a new benchmark in the database which needs total network retraining across the database.</p>



<h4>Benefits Of Facial Recognition In Businesses</h4>



<p><strong>Pairing</strong></p>



<p>Dating services use the notion that persons who have similar face characteristics are more attracted to themselves. These dating services provide apps that combine users using facial recognition with possible Romantic partners.</p>



<p><strong>Financial Transactions</strong></p>



<p>Over recent years, online shopping has grown very popular. Renowned smartphone producers such as Apple and Google have included software for facial recognition on their phones so that users can quickly conduct financial transactions on the move and without having to remember their most complicated passwords.</p>



<p><strong>Healthcare</strong></p>



<p>Medical practitioners can utilize the technology of face recognition to recognize a disease by examining the characteristics of the patient. Doctors may recognize signs such as swelling or inflammation using facial recognition and start prescribing the best path ahead with no human.</p>



<p><strong>Advertising</strong></p>



<p>With face recognition technology, advertisers are given an opportunity to communicate their messages more precisely to their targeted target groups. Using this technology, cameras can detect the proper age and gender, enabling marketers to target the right client at the right moment with the right message.</p>



<p><strong>eCommerce / Retail</strong></p>



<p>Some of the most disturbing today&#8217;s eCommerce companies use face recognition to give their consumers better experiences.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><strong>Conclusion</strong></p>



<p>Although face recognition is limited for example, changes in posture, illumination, and image quality, the technology is becoming increasingly popular and is eventually a part of everyday life. Platforms that offer a basic implementation of the technology for face recognition utilize different algorithms and may thus be utilized in diverse applications.</p>



<p>You now know all you need to create a bespoke facial recognition application. The rest depends on the developers. You must talk to them about your project characteristics, prepare a plan and go to business.</p>



<p><em>If you are looking to</em><a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"><em> hire a mobile application developer for your application</em></a><em>, you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.&nbsp;</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/facial-recognition-mobile-app-how-to-built-it/">Facial Recognition Mobile App: How To Built It?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/facial-recognition-mobile-app-how-to-built-it/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Is SEO &#038; Why It Is Important?</title>
		<link>/blog/what-is-seo-why-it-is-important/</link>
					<comments>/blog/what-is-seo-why-it-is-important/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:23:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Digital Media Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Ocean]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Search Engine Optimization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Why SEO Is Important]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6409</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/what-is-seo-why-it-is-important/">What Is SEO &amp; Why It Is Important?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p>You undoubtedly have heard a hundred times, but even if you have a fundamental concept of what search engine optimization (SEO) means, you still can&#8217;t have a strong comprehension of this complicated and sophisticated monster.</p>
<p>The optimization of the search engines for marketers is quite essential. By optimizing your websites, including blog posts, you make your website more accessible to individuals who use search engines such as Google to input terms connected with your product or service.</p>
<p>You will find out in this post about &#8220;What is SEO?&#8221; and why is it so essential. To have a full understanding of search engine optimization, read it continuously.</p>
<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:35px"><strong>What Is Seo?</strong></p>
<p>SEO means &#8220;optimization of the search engine.&#8221; The use of &#8220;organic&#8221; (not sponsored) search engine results increases the quality and quantity of online traffic and visibility to your business.</p>
<p>Common responsibilities in the search engine optimization sector include the creation of high-quality content, content optimization by particular keywords, and backlink construction. search engine optimization is important simply because it will increase the visibility of your site.</p>
<p>Furthermore, it is also a valued instrument for brand awareness, for developing future relations, and promoting oneself in your domain as a leading and trustworthy expert.</p>
<p>Search engines are where your consumers are and you must distinguish your customers from rivals. Let&#8217;s be geared for this, therefore.</p>
<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:33px"><strong>Types Of SEO</strong></p>
<p><strong>White-Hat SEO</strong></p>
<p>White-hat SEO / Ethical search engine optimization refers to all optimization methods that comply with Google&#8217;s rules for the search engine. While you have to be patient about outcomes, they are durable and produce true goodwill around your business.</p>
<p>Furthermore, if there is a new algorithm, there is no danger that your website will be blacklisted or bumped in the search results. Overall, white-hat SEO is risk-low and highly rewarded if you execute it properly. White Hat search engine optimization is more often utilized by people that plan to invest in their website for a long time.</p>
<p><strong>Black-Hat SEO</strong></p>
<p>Black Hat SEO is employed more commonly than by long-term investment on its website, by individuals who are searching for fast cash returns. Black hat search engine optimization may lead to the search engine prohibition of your website.</p>
<p>But as the main focus is on fast return business models, most experts who utilize Black Hat search engine optimization methods see a relatively unimportant danger as prohibited by search engines. Black hat SEO can also be called unethical search engine optimization or spamdexing because spamdexing is a black hat search engine optimization tactic. Search engine optimization is often utilized.</p>
<p><strong>On-Page SEO</strong></p>
<p>On-Page SEO, high-quality content is written solely for the benefit of the visitors to your website; meta tags are added to enable Google bottles to better understand their content, HTML tags are used to highlight headings and other content elements, and the links or duplicate content are not broken down.</p>
<p>Cleaning up the URL structure, selecting pictures that are not too large while writing descriptive filenames, etc. are only a few additional search engine optimization strategies on a page and have an ordered namings system for different sites that fall under one category.</p>
<p><strong>Off-Page SEO</strong></p>
<p>Off-page SEO is about anything not happening on your website directly. The optimization of your website is referred to as search engine optimization on the webpage and involves factors like structure, content, and speed optimization. Off-page SEO concerns, among other things, the creation of links, social media, and local SEOs.</p>
<p>In other words, to generate visitors and make your company look like a genuine thing. It includes external ranking criteria such as developing links from reputable sites throughout the same area as you, good social media marketing, feedback from customers on online forums, etc.</p>
<p><strong>Grey-Hat SEO</strong></p>
<p>SEO companies commonly apply Gray-Hat search engine optimization methods because of the demand to quickly observe a customer&#8217;s findings and a drop in the approach between white and black hat SEO. Although Google&#8217;s webmaster standards are not specifically banned.</p>
<p>Still frowned, they might lead to unwanted search results. It is vital to have an adequate grasp of the Gray Hat search engine optimization, because it may enhance the ranking of your site without adverse effects or cost you thousands in lost visitors.</p>
<p><strong>Negative SEO</strong></p>
<p>This is by far the most disgusting and immoral of the many forms of search engine optimization.  A negative search is done so that you can take the place of your rival or take advantage of the rankings.</p>
<p>Negative SEO tactics involve a hack of a person&#8217;s site and the creation, in a variety of online forums, of a number of suspectly high-quality links. Negative search engine optimization can, of course, lead to legal proceedings if it is captured.&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Technical SEO</strong></p>
<p>Technical SEO mainly supports the success of Google Bots in tracking, interpreting, and indexing all of your site&#8217;s pages for future usage.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Creating a comprehensive XML map, making your site mobile, adding structured data to aid web spiders to sift your pages and categorize them according to their content type are some of the approaches.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It is referred to as &#8216;technical,&#8217; as the real contents of the website and promotional products are not included in this. Technical search engine optimization&#8217;s main objective is to optimize the website infrastructure.</p>
<h4>Why SEO Is Important?</h4>
<p><strong>Trust &amp; Credibility</strong></p>
<p>The objective of expert <a href="https://medium.com/menlo-office/medium-seo-how-to-rank-your-medium-articles-in-google-search-e7bdd8d962c0">search engine optimization</a> is to create a solid basis for a beautiful website with a clean, effective user experience that, via the trust and credibility of the brand and its digital properties, can be readily discovered. People have confidence in Google.&nbsp;</p>
<p>You find what you&#8217;re seeking every day. Your business builds confidence and credibility with your audience by being high on the search engines.</p>
<p><strong>Increased Traffic&nbsp;</strong></p>
<p>The majority of printouts and clicks on top places on the search engine results pages can lead to large increases in traffic to your website.&nbsp;</p>
<p>SEO also aims to provide useful title tags and meta descriptions that are related to keywords and that is displayed in the result pages. With optimized tags and descriptions the click-through rate rises as well as quality online traffic.</p>
<p><strong>Cost-effectiveness&nbsp;</strong></p>
<p>SEO is one of the cheapest marketing techniques, as this targets consumers who actively search online for their products and services. The inbound nature of search engine optimization enables firms to save money rather than outbound methods such as refrigeration.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Since search engine optimization mainly focuses on customers who seek items and services like yours actively, SEO traffic is more skilled than many other marketing techniques, which results in cost savings for businesses.</p>
<p><strong>High ROI and Conversions&nbsp;</strong></p>
<p>SEO accounts for a big part of visitors on a site, which implies more conversions can take place. Search engine optimization opens the doors for anything whether you wish to purchase your site traffic or sign up for your newsletter or post your material on your social media handle.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Search engine optimization is very measurable Google Analytics can offer you a never-ending overview of each tiny activity you are taking. SEO&#8217;s return on investments is very significant, as they are cheaper than other digital tactics and attract most site, buyers.</p>
<p><strong>Attract Local Customers</strong></p>
<p>Geospecific queries and local business listings are the emphases of the local search. The location where small and medium-sized enterprises operate has to be optimized.&nbsp;</p>
<p>You may help attract local consumers by having an optimized Google My Business profile and knowledge chart panel to customize the content of your website to answer local search questions. And you can target folks in a specific way if you play your local SEO cards correctly.</p>
<p><strong>Improve User Experience</strong></p>
<p>The ultimate objective of Google is to offer its consumers the finest available results. In consequence, many of their modifications to algorithms are designed to ensure that consumers are sent to sites with a great deal of experience and not simply pertinent material.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This is why technological aspects such as mobility, usability, and website performance have played a far larger role than ever before in rankings today.</p>
<h5>What Are Role For SEO&nbsp;</h5>
<p><strong>SEO copywriting&nbsp;</strong></p>
<p>Content is the king when it comes to website promotion. Copywriting from SEO generates fantastic content for your website which is engaging, and valuable. In addition to highlighting your website, the material must contain keyword words that are also commonly utilized by Internet users when searching online.</p>
<p><strong>Website redesigning&nbsp;</strong></p>
<p>You should surely give your website a facelift amid the widening competition facing website proprietors. This is one of the finest strategies to increase the appeal, conviction, and modernization of your website. Every website requires a competent SEO specialist, whose major objective is web redesign, whatever the typeface, aesthetics, or even the website loading speed.</p>
<p><strong>Link building&nbsp;</strong></p>
<p>Link building refers to the acquisition and linkage of web pages linked to your business. Buying sites (particularly those that are prominent) that connect to your sites will enhance your chances of being recognized and received further clicks.</p>
<h6><strong>Conclusion</strong></h6>
<p>However, any SEO service you require for your website should be given by specialized SEO businesses, who have a wealth of expertise with different components connected to the optimization of search engines. Experiencing will provide a<a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"> <em>high standard of service</em></a> customized to your needs.</p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/what-is-seo-why-it-is-important/">What Is SEO &amp; Why It Is Important?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/what-is-seo-why-it-is-important/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Does Your Business Need Social Media Marketing</title>
		<link>/blog/why-does-your-business-need-social-media-marketing/</link>
					<comments>/blog/why-does-your-business-need-social-media-marketing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:20:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Digital Media Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Ocean]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Search Engine Optimization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Email Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SMM]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6395</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Although the web provides a large quantity of information, many companies fight to get their heads around &#8220;social media marketing&#8221; and how it works. Social media platforms have quickly become an inseparable element of plans for corporate development. When creating meaningful connections with consumers, you must not neglect the effect of &#8220;social.&#8221; It may appear [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/why-does-your-business-need-social-media-marketing/">Why Does Your Business Need Social Media Marketing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Although the web provides a large quantity of information, many companies fight to get their heads around &#8220;social media marketing&#8221; and how it works. Social media platforms have quickly become an inseparable element of plans for corporate development. When creating meaningful connections with consumers, you must not neglect the effect of &#8220;social.&#8221;</p>



<p>It may appear overwhelming, but it cannot overestimate its value. It is so crucial that 97% of marketers use social media and 78% of salespeople out-sell their colleagues using social media.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:33px"><strong>What Is Social Media Marketing?</strong></p>



<p>Social media marketing is connecting your audience using social media platforms to grow your brand, improve sales and drive the traffic of the website. It entails producing outstanding content, listening to your supporters and engaging them and evaluating your outcomes, and executing social media publicities on your social media sites.</p>



<p>Marketing on social media is about meeting your target demographic and your customers and interacting with each other and your brand in society. Although social media marketing as a whole is of tremendous value and useful to your business growth (as you&#8217;ll discover in the next section), the social networks your audience is using differently.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:30px"><strong>Why Does Your Business Need Social Media Marketing?</strong></p>



<p><strong>Increased Brand Awareness</strong></p>



<p>Social media have demonstrated that their commitment has boosted brand recognition. Social participation covers items such as comments, likes, shares, and postings.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Social media also helps you improve awareness of the brand through direct visitors to your site. You may accomplish this using your profile, biography, and posts with direct connections to your website.</p>



<p><strong>Generates More Leads &amp; Conversions</strong></p>



<p>Platforms such as Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, and Linkedin enable businesses to create leads. You may make conversions by using a mix of paid and organic methods. Video marketing, sponsored ad campaigns, donations and e-mail opt are some of the main solutions to make your sales funnel perspective.</p>



<p><strong>Build Customer Loyalty</strong></p>



<p>Customers follow the brands they appreciate and connect with them. What&#8217;s noteworthy, though, is that 53% of your company clients will probably be loyal to your firm. It is a direct link that is evident: If clients follow them, they are more likely than competitors to pick them. They will also enhance your traffic if they are loyal consumers.</p>



<p><strong>Social Media Marketing Is Cost-Effective</strong></p>



<p>Probably the cost-effective and diversified approach to promote a business is through social media marketing (<a href="https://medium.com/@thebloggingguruji/what-is-social-media-marketing-smm-7de0249f6440">SMM</a>). The creation of a profile on most social networking sites does not cost anything.&nbsp;</p>



<p>If you choose to launch a sponsored campaign to enhance your content, then the cost compared with other publicity platforms is rather little. If you are successful, your chances are increased that your investment will make better profits.</p>



<p><strong>Learn From Competitors</strong></p>



<p>Social media are a good method to keep an eye on your rivals whether it&#8217;s their social media techniques, the items they promote, their campaigns, or their degree of contact with supporters.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Social media allows you to take a look at what your contest is and does not work and therefore helps you to decide what your firm strategy should or should not alter.</p>



<p><strong>Keep Your Customers Up-To-Date</strong></p>



<p>Social media is one of the finest and easiest ways to inform your consumers of new items or future events. If your company announces a big new item or an exciting event, people will be enthusiastic about it.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:27px"><strong>5 Pillars Of Social Media Marketing</strong></p>



<p><strong>Strategy</strong></p>



<p>Let&#8217;s take a step back and look at the larger picture before you plunge straight into it and share anything on social media. The first step is to reflect on your social media approach</p>



<ol><li>What are your goals?</li><li>Which social media platforms do you want to focus on?</li><li>What type of content do you want to share?&nbsp;</li></ol>



<p><strong>Planning and Publishing</strong></p>



<p>Social media publishing is just as simple as posting a blog post on a social media site, an image, or a video. It&#8217;s like sharing your Facebook page on a personal basis. But instead of generating and posting material impulsively, you want to prepare your content in advance.&nbsp;</p>



<p>You must also produce outstanding material, which your public enjoys, in the correct time and frequency to guarantee that you maximize your reach on social media.</p>



<p><strong>Listening and Engagement</strong></p>



<p>You may even talk on social media about your brand without informing you. Therefore, you want to watch your brand&#8217;s social media interactions. You get an opportunity to surprise and please them if it is favorable feedback.</p>



<p>Otherwise, before it gets worse, you may give help and remedy a problem. All alerts may be controlled manually through all social media platforms, however, this is not efficient, and postings that have not marked your company&#8217;s social media page are not visible.</p>



<p><strong>Analytics and Reporting</strong></p>



<p>Along the process, you will be able to know how your social media marketing works whether you post content or engage in social media. A key level of such information is the social media sites themselves.</p>



<p>You may utilize a broad range of accessible social media analysis tools, such as Buffer Analyze to obtain more in-depth analytic information or to compare it simply across social media platforms.</p>



<p><strong>Advertising</strong></p>



<p>If you have more money to increase the promotion of your social media, social media publicity is one area you may examine. You may reach a larger group than the people who follow you with social media advertisements.</p>



<p>Social media advertising systems are currently so strong that exactly to which ads you want to display may be specified. The target audiences can be created based on their demographics.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:25px"><strong>10 of the most crucial measurements to be followed by you</strong></p>



<ol><li><strong>Engagement</strong></li></ol>



<p>It comprises clicks, comments, enjoyments, and answers to social media posts. Platform-specific engagement kinds like &#8220;Saved&#8221; photos on Instagram and &#8220;Pinned&#8221; posts on Pinterest are also included.</p>



<ol start="2"><li><strong>Reach</strong></li></ol>



<p>Your reach is the number of individuals who have viewed any material related to your page or profile.</p>



<ol start="3"><li><strong>Followers</strong></li></ol>



<p>This is your profile number who hit the &#8220;Follow&#8221; option and view your content regularly in their feeds.</p>



<ol start="4"><li><strong>Impressions</strong></li></ol>



<p>This is the number of times an article is displayed on your profile or page, regardless of whether you are clicking on it or not. This is typically the case if someone scrolls through their newsfeed, but doesn&#8217;t click anything.</p>



<ol start="5"><li><strong>Video view</strong></li></ol>



<p>This is the number of views you get on Facebook, Snapchat, Instagram, and any other social platform.</p>



<ol start="6"><li><strong>Profile visits</strong></li></ol>



<p>Your number of profile visits is the number of individuals that opened your social media page.</p>



<ol start="7"><li><strong>Mentions</strong></li></ol>



<p>This is how often members of the public in their postings have cited your profile.</p>



<ol start="8"><li><strong>Tags</strong></li></ol>



<p>This is when your audience adds to a different post the name of your company profile or hashtag.</p>



<ol start="9"><li><strong>Reposts</strong></li></ol>



<p>This is when an audience member shares a portion of your material on his profile.</p>



<ol start="10"><li><strong>Shares</strong></li></ol>



<p>These are messages from your fans and your audience and share them with their network.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:22px"><strong>Conclusion&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>In the light of the fact that billions of people live on social media nowadays, it is simple to see why many companies and marketers utilize the channel to support and communicate with their goods.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Begin working now on the marketing plan of your business on social media to raise your number of followers, enhance involvement and encourage conversion.</p>



<p><em>If you are looking to</em><a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"><em> hire a digital marketer for your business,</em></a><em> you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/why-does-your-business-need-social-media-marketing/">Why Does Your Business Need Social Media Marketing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/why-does-your-business-need-social-media-marketing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Multi-vendor Marketplace For Lazada, Shopee, Qoo10</title>
		<link>/blog/multi-vendor-marketplace-for-lazada-shopee-qoo10/</link>
					<comments>/blog/multi-vendor-marketplace-for-lazada-shopee-qoo10/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 07:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cross platform mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marketplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Multi Vendor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Integration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lazada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Multi-vendor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Qoo10]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shopee]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6441</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The choice of a multi-vendor software supplier may be a crucial success element for active brands and salespeople in different markets. You might face inventory, order, and product synchronization problems across your sales channels by selecting the wrong multi-vendor software supplier. You may take advantage of a single management console to pick the correct multi-vendor [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/multi-vendor-marketplace-for-lazada-shopee-qoo10/">Multi-vendor Marketplace For Lazada, Shopee, Qoo10</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The choice of a multi-vendor software supplier may be a crucial success element for active brands and salespeople in different markets. You might face inventory, order, and product synchronization problems across your sales channels by selecting the wrong multi-vendor software supplier.</p>



<p>You may take advantage of a single management console to pick the correct multi-vendor software provider and you do not have to hop into the multiple sale center interfaces in order to calculate inventory and process orders and handle your product listings.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s a wonderful method to assist a new company start or to extend the brand of existing companies.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:35px"><strong>What Is Multi-Vendor Marketplace?</strong></p>



<p>A multi-selling market is a multi-vendor internet shop. The marketplace feature makes any online store like the famous Shopee Lazada Qoo10 an online marketplace. Selling and finding customers is easy. There is a large selection of goods that are updated and deployed continuously.</p>



<p>The presence of numerous independent vendors is a distinguishing aspect of such a shop. Sales, paperwork &#8211; invoices, and delivery control may be carried out and managed. Everything is done using a single control panel.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:33px"><strong>Why is the Multi-Vendor Marketplace Important?</strong></p>



<p>The online marketplace is a multi-vendor platform where numerous vendors may register themselves, establish their profiles, and add items to their selling plans.&nbsp; We approach all the multi-supplier eCommerce industry offers several advantages for both customers and suppliers.</p>



<p>We make this platform a hassle-free procedure that allows sellers to quickly submit and maintain their items. This type of platform is economical and web-friendly.</p>



<p>E-commerce has now claimed a large part of shopping and is a fast-growing sector. This business continuously promotes new concepts and enables distributors to improve sales.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:30px"><strong>What We Can Build?&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>All sellers from the same market are interested in you. Build a market for sellers to deal with infinite shops and products. Create multi-seller innovation for your unique, integrated, and tailor-made modules.</p>



<p>The program is customized. We can build the application with these platforms (Lazada, Shopee, Qoo10). The Multi Products provider uploads and offers its products. We follow the five-step strategy in essence.</p>



<ol><li>MarketPlace Owner.</li><li>Vendor.</li><li>Multi-vendor Products.</li><li>E-commerce Marketplace.</li><li>Customers.</li></ol>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:27px"><strong>Characteristics Of Multi-Vendor Marketplace</strong></p>



<p><strong>Several freelance vendors in one shop</strong></p>



<p>Sellers have full control of the management of articles, sales, invoicing, and shipments via an easy, customized dashboard.</p>



<p><strong>The owner&#8217;s income</strong></p>



<p>As the proprietor of an online multi-sales company, you earn a fixed fee for each order from vendors. There are two approaches to set up the commission:</p>



<ul><li>On the basis of a predetermined selling amount, regardless of the whole cost of the products or services offered.</li><li>Based on the rate in percentage of the sale value of products/services.</li></ul>



<p><strong>Third-party software integration</strong></p>



<p>Like a conventional online store, the required features of a multi-seller marketplace may be extended by modules from third parties. <a href="https://medium.com/@growthspark/why-you-should-be-blogging-on-shopify-3ffe7d509311">Shopify integration</a>, delivery services, and payment systems are allowed.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:25px"><strong>Why Multi-Vendor MarketPlace?</strong></p>



<p><strong>An additional income stream</strong></p>



<p>You may collect a commission on each of their sales by inviting new merchants into your marketplace. Create a set on-site commission rate or give seller rates that are linked to parameters such as several items and an established audience. Be prepared for your transaction charges and allow their sales to contribute to the maintenance cost of your site in general.</p>



<p><strong>Full control over members</strong></p>



<p>As the owner of the market, you decide what is shown on your website. Only those that suit the entire brand you&#8217;re developing can be accepted when you apply for new vendors. Suppliers acceptable for the WooCommerce dashboard can develop their own products, but you keep a quality check and only those you authorize will go live on the site.</p>



<p><strong>Create their own products and control their own inventory</strong></p>



<p>Providers have restricted access to WordPress dashboards for product development, uploading, pricing, and the most precise description of their goods. Seller also manages its own inventory figures, which means that the availability for visiting consumers is precise and updated immediately.</p>



<p><strong>Sell anything</strong></p>



<p>Vendors may now sell physical products, digital downloads, or both using this Application. You can give other options using extensions. This enables your suppliers to market their appointments and consultations.</p>



<p><strong>Synchronized Order Management</strong></p>



<p>Get stock activity from the marketplace in real-time. All channels update the stock levels automatically, thus enabling stock control, sales maximization, and oversees eradication.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:22px"><strong>Conclusion</strong></p>



<p>I hope you&#8217;re all aware of the multi-selling marketplace. Would want to start your multi-selling market, talk to our expert team and see how we are able to make your concept a reality.</p>



<p><em>If you are looking to</em><a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"><em> hire a developer for your Marketplace application</em></a><em>, you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/multi-vendor-marketplace-for-lazada-shopee-qoo10/">Multi-vendor Marketplace For Lazada, Shopee, Qoo10</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/multi-vendor-marketplace-for-lazada-shopee-qoo10/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ten Unbelievable Facts About Ecommerce App Development</title>
		<link>/blog/ecommerce-app-development/</link>
					<comments>/blog/ecommerce-app-development/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 08:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hasotech.com/?p=2025</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/ecommerce-app-development/">Ten Unbelievable Facts About Ecommerce App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p>Ecommerce App Development is one of the trending in the current century. The Ecommerce business includes buying and selling online. Making a purchase over the mobile app is trending now. Online payment or Cash on delivery payment has become easy. The Electronic Commerce or Ecommerce App Development makes Business to Consumer, Business to Business, Consumer to Business, Consumer to Consumer sales. The Ecommerce App Development has become easy which makes a rise in competitors. There are many frameworks available for Ecommerce App Development like Magento, Woocommerce, Shopify etc.,</p>
<h2>Ten Facts about Ecommerce App Development</h2>
<ul>
<li>
<h4><strong>Most of the</strong> <strong>Ecommerce App Development fails due to lack of investment </strong></h4>
<ul>
<li>Though there are many frameworks available, Ecommerce needs continuous development to survive in the market. Due to heavy competition, Ecommerce app development to be maintained properly.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<h4><strong>Ecommerce App Development can be done in 7 days </strong></h4>
<ul>
<li>Yes, Since there are many Web frameworks available, A basic Ecommerce site can be developed in a week with default functions.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<h4><strong>E-commerce Mobile App Needed for success </strong></h4>
<ul>
<li>There is no use of having Ecommerce App development on Web alone. 67% of the Online purchase is using Mobile application.</li>
<li>Ecommerce Mobile app development is must to survey with competitors</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/whats-crazy-mobile-app-development/">What’s crazy on Mobile App Development</a></h3>
<ul>
<li>
<h4><strong>Multivendor E-commerce app Development </strong></h4>
<ul>
<li>To move an E-commerce app development in a proper way. Better to start the development with multivendor support.</li>
<li>Multivendor helps to minimize the work and improves development</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<h4><strong>Another fail reason: More than Ecommerce App Development </strong></h4>
<ul>
<li>It&#8217;s not enough to just develop an app for Ecommerce. Proper promotion on Social Networks and SEO Optimization.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<h4><strong>It&#8217;s very cheaper to develop </strong></h4>
<ul>
<li>There is always a fact that, E-commerce app development always costs high. Of course, it costs high but at the same time, there are many ready-made solutions available on Ecommerce App development which it cheaper. The more money you invest, the more standard you get</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<h4><strong>Mobile app is easy with Hybrid </strong></h4>
<ul>
<li>If you are looking for Ecommerce mobile app development on both Android and iOS. Then it is best to go with <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/hybrid-mobile-application-development/">Hybrid Mobile App development</a>. Which are cost and time effective.</li>
<li>50% of Mobile apps are in Hybrid</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<h4><strong>Amazon is Using Hybrid </strong></h4>
<ul>
<li>The Ecommerce Gaint is using Hybrid Web view Mobile Application</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<h4><strong>Magento is Secured than Woocommerce and Shopify </strong></h4>
<ul>
<li>Magento is preferred than other frameworks When comes to Ecommerce App development,</li>
<li>Magento 2.x stands good but it is costlier</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/know-about-mobile-app-development/">Know about Mobile App Development</a></h3>
<ul>
<li>
<h4><strong>Dedicated Hosting </strong></h4>
<ul>
<li>Dedicated hosting is must one for making Ecommerce Application to manage huge data</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Let us know your view about Ecommerce app development in comments. We are always happy to answer your questions.</p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/ecommerce-app-development/">Ten Unbelievable Facts About Ecommerce App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/ecommerce-app-development/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: web.hasotech.com @ 2022-10-26 10:36:32 by W3 Total Cache
-->