<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Hybrid Mobile Application Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<atom:link href="/blog/category/hybrid-mobile-application/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/category/hybrid-mobile-application/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:35:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/cropped-logo-1-rb-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Hybrid Mobile Application Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/category/hybrid-mobile-application/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ionic Application Development &#8211; Pros And Cons</title>
		<link>/blog/ionic-application-development-pros-and-cons/</link>
					<comments>/blog/ionic-application-development-pros-and-cons/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ionic Framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cons]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pros]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web app]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6366</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Businesses worldwide desire an advanced mobile app on their Android and iOS platforms to serve their company. Most of them are caught in the middle where they have difficulty selecting the ideal technologies like ionic, hybrid, native for themselves. Each approach to technology and development has its pros and cons, from which you have to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/ionic-application-development-pros-and-cons/">Ionic Application Development &#8211; Pros And Cons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Businesses worldwide desire an advanced mobile app on their Android and iOS platforms to serve their company. Most of them are caught in the middle where they have difficulty selecting the ideal technologies like ionic, hybrid, native for themselves. </p>



<p>Each approach to technology and development has its pros and cons, from which you have to select the best solution for your company. If you think Ionic is the correct platform application development, below are a few advantages and disadvantages of Ionic development.</p>



<p>Ionic Framework helps us to develop apps using only one codebase for several platforms. Let us learn how it works and what are this solution&#8217;s benefits and downsides. The frameworks are quite popular, however, in this blog, we will focus on the advantages and disadvantages of ionic application development. Let&#8217;s get right in with that statement!</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><br><strong>What is an Ionic Application?</strong></p>



<p>It is used to build <a href="https://hasotech.com/why-we-love-hybrid-mobile-app-development/">hybrid mobile apps </a>using the Open Source Software Development Kit(SDK). It is fully Apache Cordova and Angular based on this ionic framework. More specifically, Ionic is an npm module that requires Node JS to be installed.</p>



<p>The conditions for building these applications are excellent HTML, CSS and JavaScript commands. Because of their suitable properties and usefulness, many developers today opt for ionic frameworks. The main objective is to construct a hybrid mobile app in ionic framework development.</p>



<p>Hybrid applications provide several advantages compared with native applications, in particular in terms of development time. Essentially, the construction of ionic apps allows the captivating design and soft animations of native mobile components.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center has-black-color has-text-color has-large-font-size"><strong><a href="http://Ionic/ Mobile App Developer">Ionic Mobile App Developer</a></strong></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><br><strong>Ionic Applications</strong> <strong>Are</strong></p>



<p><br>●<strong> <a href="https://uptech.team/blog/native-vs-cross-platform-app-development">The cross-platform </a></strong>– single code base for both platforms (except native components)</p>



<p>● <strong>Web-based </strong>– Built using web-views and can be displayed in a browser like PWAs.</p>



<p>● <strong>Access to native API components</strong> – They can access the native device’s cameras, files, and others.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><br><strong>Advantages Of Ionic Application</strong></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>A single codebase across various platforms</strong></p>



<p>It was developed using the Angular and Apache Cordova frame and used as the fundamental technologies for app development HTML 5, CSS, and JavaScript. Alongside the current release of the Ionic, you may utilize Angular with all its advantages and disadvantages for the first time.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Free Open Source Framework</strong></p>



<p>This frame is an open-source framework that is entirely free. Ionic framework applications offer platform-specific, optimized CSS features to match the native appearance of the different mobile operating systems. This Framework offers one of the primary advantages in the provision of CSS, HTML, and JS mobile-optimized code and reducing code rewriting needs.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Cross Mobile App Development</strong></p>



<p>In application development, the development of efficient, compatible, and bespoke apps is of major importance. Ionic integrates with AngularJS, which enhances the interoperability of this code with mobile platforms. Ionic helps to swiftly create apps that make the app more popular and save time and money.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Testing convenience</strong></p>



<p>While Ionic Apps only operate via a review, the browser of the device may be used to test the app. It is much handier because test equipment does not even need to be used to make sure it is all working properly. The same principle applies in the current world to a range of mobile devices.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Appealing Default UI</strong></p>



<p>There are numerous common JavaScript and CSS components in these Framework apps covering many fundamental elements that would like to be developed by a moving app. The menu slides, inputs, buttons, lists, navigation, tab, sliding box, and pop-ups. standard styles are clean and simple, and developers may simply change them by adding CSS classes that have been given by the user to the device.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Quick Development and Time To Market</strong></p>



<p>This development may benefit entrepreneurs and company owners when comparing a mobile app with native apps on both platforms in a short time. Constructing native apps particularly for each platform can take time, which can lead to a market delay and the cost of development of native applications is sometimes costly.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><br><strong>Disadvantages Of Ionic Application</strong></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Performance Issue</strong></p>



<p>The performance of heavy apps is inappropriate for this application. When created with this Framework, apps with heavy realism or heavy graphics might crash.</p>



<p>The major reason behind this is that this application makes its graphics using a browser that does many stages on the screen.</p>



<p>There are, then, study performance optimization strategies to achieve better outcomes if you still want to develop a high-performance application utilizing Ionic.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Security Issues</strong></p>



<p>You must not regard it as a con of this application on your own, but rather the possibility of a hazard with which you have to cope. </p>



<p>Security is a typical problem for the creation of hybrid apps as long as your program can be reversed. Ionic CLI is a prevalent approach since version 4 that makes the code tough for hackers to understand.</p>



<p> But you must also realize that there is no code uglification when you use Angular CLI or earlier versions of Ionic. The code will have to be Uglified by your developers yourself.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Dependency on Plugins</strong></p>



<p>Even Ionic app development firms would admit that they must rely on plugins to have access to native features. You won&#8217;t be able to locate a corresponding plugin in the ionic toolset in some situations.</p>



<p>To build a plugin for very specialized features and functions, you must use the Ionic App development company. </p>



<p>If there is no plug-in, you will be able to discover a module most commonly. You&#8217;d probably have to make something that&#8217;s not in store with the aid of a native developer.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Hot Reloading not Available</strong></p>



<p>To make modifications to the application code, this platform employs a variety of approaches. Hot reloading is regarded as a vital characteristic in the software engineering industry. </p>



<p>Because it allows you to make changes without having to refresh the entire program. It takes some getting accustomed to because it does not support hot reloading and instead relies on live reloading. </p>



<p>When you make changes, live reloading will refresh the whole app to make the changes active. That implies that whenever your developers wish to make changes, their program will be restarted.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><strong>conclusion</strong></p>



<p>For your development, you have reviewed the pros and cons of utilizing this framework. Finally, it is crucial to have your application supported and problems solved on time by the proper Ionic application development firm.</p>



<p><em>If you are looking to<a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"> hire an ionic application developer for your application</a>, you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/ionic-application-development-pros-and-cons/">Ionic Application Development &#8211; Pros And Cons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/ionic-application-development-pros-and-cons/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pros And Cons Of Hybrid Mobile App Development</title>
		<link>/blog/pros-and-cons-of-hybrid-mobile-app-development/</link>
					<comments>/blog/pros-and-cons-of-hybrid-mobile-app-development/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cross platform mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ionic Framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web app]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6377</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New heights have reached the evolution of customized app creation. Not just smartphones and tablets, but also other user devices and smart gadgets, are available for development. Time has become a requirement for cross-platform, hybrid, and native application development, which enables companies to produce more efficient goods. While native applications offer numerous benefits, the popularity [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/pros-and-cons-of-hybrid-mobile-app-development/">Pros And Cons Of Hybrid Mobile App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>New heights have reached the evolution of customized app creation. Not just smartphones and tablets, but also other user devices and smart gadgets, are available for development. Time has become a requirement for cross-platform, hybrid, and native application development, which enables companies to produce more efficient goods. </p>



<p>While native applications offer numerous benefits, the popularity of hybrid mobile applications has grown. It&#8217;s due to its flexibility on many platforms. This idea leads to the development of a single application for many platforms. In addition, these apps make reserving a position in the app store market somewhat faster.</p>



<p>Those platform frameworks are extremely popular however, the advantage and disadvantages of hybrid mobile apps will be discussed in this article. Let&#8217;s get right in with that statement!</p>



<h2 style="font-size:35px">What Is a Hybrid Application?</h2>



<p>A <strong>hybrid application </strong>allows the same software to be installed and even execute on different browsers in different operating systems like Android, iOS, Windows, and so on.</p>



<p>The use of a third-party <a href="https://medium.com/flutterdevs/hybrid-apps-the-future-of-mobile-technology-259bac9a985f">hybrid platform</a> is the development of a hybrid app or hybrid strategy. Third-party examples include React Native, PhoneGap, Ionic, Cordoba, or Xamarin. You may also use web technologies to create the app (HTML, CSS, and Javascript).</p>



<p>The development of this mobile app is primarily a way to build a mobile application utilizing a single code base for several platforms, such as Android and iOS. In this way, development expenses are dramatically reduced. On the other side though, there are certain advantages and disadvantages to this app creation.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:30px"><strong>Pros Of Hybrid Mobile Application</strong></p>



<p><strong>Lower Development Costs</strong></p>



<p>The creation of hybrid apps has proven 30% cheaper compared to the native application development strategy. The hybrid method means that the developers just require an Android and iOS project. However, the expense of maintaining the mobile app on both platforms is increasing as the requirement for customization rises.</p>



<p><strong>Easy To Maintain</strong></p>



<p>The simpler maintenance of these mobile applications also benefits. For native applications, new versions need to be developed by the development teams. In addition, with each new version release, consumers will need to upgrade their apps. This app skips versioning and facilitates app maintenance in real-time, as it updates a web page.</p>



<p><strong>Easy Scaling</strong></p>



<p>Scale hybrid programs to a number of devices and OSes is extremely simple. That&#8217;s because web technology on all platforms is nearly 100% the same. This allows the code to be reused easily without any need to recompile the app at all.</p>



<p><strong>Offline Support</strong></p>



<p>The lack of offline support often implies that mobile applications suffer from restrictions. It is difficult for firms who serve clients in rural areas or places where connection to the Internet is a challenge. Statistics show that 70% of users quit an app because it takes too much loading time. One of the advantages of this application is its offline accessibility. The end-users thereby have continuous access to the data without any performance breakdowns.</p>



<p><strong>Support for Cloud &amp; Enterprise-Level Solutions</strong></p>



<p>The Exchange Integration Code may be simply included in the cloud in this framework such as Ionic, Titanium, and PhoneGap. These frameworks are essentially simple to utilize, helping developers update program features, aesthetics, and validity. This allows developers to integrate hybrid applications easily with well-known cloud platforms such as Salesforce and AWS.</p>



<p><strong>Improved Performance</strong></p>



<p>Like native applications, this app provides excellent speed and performance. In fact, they are significantly quicker than advanced and responsive applications in some situations. The reason for this is that there is no reliance on network connectivity and even on apps with more users on all devices is greater.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center has-black-color has-text-color has-large-font-size"><strong><a href="https://hasotech.com/10-quick-tips-for-hybrid-mobile-app-developers/">10 Quick Tips for Hybrid Mobile App Developers</a></strong></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:30px"><strong>Cons Of Hybrid Mobile Application</strong></p>



<p><strong>UX</strong></p>



<p>UX is really concerned with these applications. A hybrid application can never deliver a totally native experience for users. Native applications employ user-friendly system interface components, may produce a meaningful solution, and can contribute to maintaining the entire workflow. Without compromising performance, this cannot be accomplished with a hybrid app. Better UX enables increased consumer participation and the app&#8217;s future.</p>



<p><strong>Limited capabilities</strong></p>



<p>Due to the nature of the design of this mobile app, plugins allow you to use the integrated device capabilities. A method&#8217;s drawback is that these are outdated or unlikely to be trustworthy. In addition, if there are no prepared solutions that allow you to have access to a specific element of the device functionality, developers may require plug-ins alone.</p>



<p><strong>Long Wait for New Features</strong></p>



<p>Whenever Apple and Google release a new feature for iOS and Android platforms, hybrid app developers need some time to add support to the new feature. This is because new SDKs are available in the native apps much more quickly than the multifunctional framework. If you have developed your mobile apps with a native approach, it provides your rivals an edge over you.</p>



<p><strong>Design</strong></p>



<p>Design problems remain a consideration as many OSes work differently. The designer must thus change the look according to different operating systems. This might compel us to challenge ourselves in the process of mending. In hybrid applications the breadth of visual and graphical representation is limited.</p>



<p><strong>Poor user experience</strong></p>



<p>This needs to be high irrespective of what you want: a hybrid app or a native app. Unfortunately, the experience of the user is not a strong part of the hybrid apps because the interface should meet in the middle both for iOS and Android platforms. If you concentrate too much on Android, for iOS users, the experience will be poorer and vice versa.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:30px"><strong><a href="https://hasotech.com/secrets-successful-hybrid-mobile-apps/">Secrets of the Successful Hybrid Mobile Apps</a></strong></p>



<h4>Conclusion&nbsp;</h4>



<p>Considering everything, whether or not you should go down to one thing with the construction of hybrid mobile apps. For companies to gain a competitive edge, hybrid mobile applications are crucial. Knowledge and experience in the development of mobile multi-platform applications.</p>



<p><em>If you are looking to</em><a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"><em> hire a hybrid mobile application developer for your application</em></a><em>, you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.&nbsp;</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/pros-and-cons-of-hybrid-mobile-app-development/">Pros And Cons Of Hybrid Mobile App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/pros-and-cons-of-hybrid-mobile-app-development/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Facial Recognition Mobile App: How To Built It?</title>
		<link>/blog/facial-recognition-mobile-app-how-to-built-it/</link>
					<comments>/blog/facial-recognition-mobile-app-how-to-built-it/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cross platform mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Neural Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biometric Recognization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Facial Recognization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpenCV Platform]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6381</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Can an app be unlocked with facial recognition? Yes! The revolutionary technologies that have been created are possible. In current days, facial recognition is becoming increasingly common. Facial identification technology fascinates many companies, but it remains unclear how to use the face release function. This article discusses &#8220;How to Build a Facial Recognition mobile app.&#8221; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/facial-recognition-mobile-app-how-to-built-it/">Facial Recognition Mobile App: How To Built It?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Can an app be unlocked with facial recognition? Yes! The revolutionary technologies that have been created are possible.</p>



<p>In current days, facial recognition is becoming increasingly common. Facial identification technology fascinates many companies, but it remains unclear how to use the face release function.</p>



<p>This article discusses &#8220;How to Build a Facial Recognition mobile app.&#8221; However, it is vital to grasp how and how the technology works by implementing it into your mobile solution.</p>



<h2>What Is Facial Recognition Technology?</h2>



<p>Facial recognition is a <a href="https://auth0.com/blog/3-critical-trends-in-biometric-authentication-in-2019/">biometric software</a> function that can identify or check a person uniquely by comparing and analyzing patterns based on the facial features of the individual.</p>



<p>Face recognition is mostly employed for security, but also in other fields of application, there is rising interest. The technology of face recognition has garnered considerable interest since it has the possibility of being used in a variety of applications.</p>



<h3>How does It work?</h3>



<p>Facial detection is the identification procedure for a human face in a scanned picture. Various face recognition techniques exist. The major distinction between all algorithms is that the characteristics are calculated and the data sets comparable with one another.</p>



<p>The entry is a stream of pictures or videos. The output is the item identifying or verifying the picture or video. Facial identification systems often function as follows. The face recognition process is typically characterized as a procedure in five stages:</p>



<ul><li>Facial detection and tracking</li><li>Facial alignment</li><li>Feature extraction</li><li>Feature matching</li><li>Facial recognition</li></ul>



<h3>How To Build Mobile Apps with Facial Recognition?</h3>



<p>There are many methods to build an app with facial recognition. Here is a list of methods like</p>



<ul><li>The OpenCV Platform</li><li>Artificial Neural Network</li></ul>



<p><strong>The OpenCV Platform</strong>&nbsp;</p>



<p>This is the standard platform for developing facial recognition applications and supports the implementation of computer vision and machine learning for the applications. It is a platform for object detection that uses several algorithms to identify all sorts of things. OpenCV is ideally suited for facial recognition and detection.</p>



<p>OpenCV is a library comprising more than 2,5 thousand properly modified, contemporary, and traditional algorithms. The emphasis of the study is computer vision and machine learning and may be used to recognize pictures, monitor movements, extract 3D object models, and many more in equal measure. OpenCV is a BSD product licensed that simplifies the programming effort considerably.</p>



<p>Facial recognition is supported with ready-to-use settings. The program is educated for the process of detection and positive photos are incorporated to assist optimize the images. There are many characteristics, scales, and weights that allow marketers to study the picture to create a variety of training image sets.</p>



<p>The OpenCV is a great framework for incorporating face recognition in your application. But in real-time applications, it is not suited. The greatest way to work against a fixed image is to use social networks or social media apps. It cannot identify pictures in real-time, taking lighting and other aspects into account.</p>



<p><strong>Artificial Neural Network</strong></p>



<p>Neural artificial networks are the most common facial recognition approach. They are used for extracting features and making decisions. A network based on a multi-lag perceptron, which permits the input picture categorization in accordance with the pre-trained network, is one of the most commonly utilized choices.</p>



<p>A series of learning examples are provided for neural networks. The neural network automatically identifies important functions during training, evaluates their significance, and creates connections between them. The trained neural network is expected to be able to generalize the expertise obtained in the course of the training to unfamiliar pictures.</p>



<p>However, because the trained neural networks were very time demanding, facial recognition results were fairly good and error rates decreased. The major difficulty is the addition of a new benchmark in the database which needs total network retraining across the database.</p>



<h4>Benefits Of Facial Recognition In Businesses</h4>



<p><strong>Pairing</strong></p>



<p>Dating services use the notion that persons who have similar face characteristics are more attracted to themselves. These dating services provide apps that combine users using facial recognition with possible Romantic partners.</p>



<p><strong>Financial Transactions</strong></p>



<p>Over recent years, online shopping has grown very popular. Renowned smartphone producers such as Apple and Google have included software for facial recognition on their phones so that users can quickly conduct financial transactions on the move and without having to remember their most complicated passwords.</p>



<p><strong>Healthcare</strong></p>



<p>Medical practitioners can utilize the technology of face recognition to recognize a disease by examining the characteristics of the patient. Doctors may recognize signs such as swelling or inflammation using facial recognition and start prescribing the best path ahead with no human.</p>



<p><strong>Advertising</strong></p>



<p>With face recognition technology, advertisers are given an opportunity to communicate their messages more precisely to their targeted target groups. Using this technology, cameras can detect the proper age and gender, enabling marketers to target the right client at the right moment with the right message.</p>



<p><strong>eCommerce / Retail</strong></p>



<p>Some of the most disturbing today&#8217;s eCommerce companies use face recognition to give their consumers better experiences.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><strong>Conclusion</strong></p>



<p>Although face recognition is limited for example, changes in posture, illumination, and image quality, the technology is becoming increasingly popular and is eventually a part of everyday life. Platforms that offer a basic implementation of the technology for face recognition utilize different algorithms and may thus be utilized in diverse applications.</p>



<p>You now know all you need to create a bespoke facial recognition application. The rest depends on the developers. You must talk to them about your project characteristics, prepare a plan and go to business.</p>



<p><em>If you are looking to</em><a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"><em> hire a mobile application developer for your application</em></a><em>, you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.&nbsp;</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/facial-recognition-mobile-app-how-to-built-it/">Facial Recognition Mobile App: How To Built It?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/facial-recognition-mobile-app-how-to-built-it/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Progressive Web App Advantages And Disadvantages</title>
		<link>/blog/progressive-web-app-advantages-and-disadvantages/</link>
					<comments>/blog/progressive-web-app-advantages-and-disadvantages/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cross platform mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ionic Framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[JavaScript]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[javascript]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PWA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web app]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6391</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Customers nowadays should be able to provide the best mobile experience for their visitors. Some companies thus opt not to apply native. We shall present another new technology called Progressive Web Apps in this post (PWAs). We discover how Progressive Web App operates, how they overcome the problems and weaknesses of PWA applications. Progressive web [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/progressive-web-app-advantages-and-disadvantages/">Progressive Web App Advantages And Disadvantages</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Customers nowadays should be able to provide the best mobile experience for their visitors. Some companies thus opt not to apply native. We shall present another new technology called Progressive Web Apps in this post (PWAs). We discover how Progressive Web App operates, how they overcome the problems and weaknesses of PWA applications.</p>



<p>Progressive web apps (PWAs) are a fascinating technology that can revolutionize the way we create mobile and online applications. Some people may suggest though that PWA is only a website that&#8217;s turned into a mobile app, while some people argue about its capacity, safety, and performance.</p>



<p>So, This article explains the <strong>pros and cons of Progressive web apps</strong>, useful for your future web and mobile apps.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:33px"><strong>What Is Progressive Web App?</strong></p>



<p>The progressive web app provides a user-like mobile experience. Therefore, the UX is tailored for the PWA device to provide the greatest information and features.</p>



<p>PWA is accessed by web users to enable consumers access to important native features, such as mobile home screen application, offline access, PWA notices of push</p>



<p>PWA allows web apps to load, synchronize and smoothly execute things when no network is present while giving your users a native experience.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:30px"><strong>Advantages Of Progressive Web App</strong></p>



<p><strong>PWAs are cheaper than other apps</strong></p>



<p>Material has to be generated only once, which saves time and money by making content for iOS, Android and a website individually. In addition, PWAs need not be updated (some find this feature specifically cool). No new information needs to be downloaded by users. You don&#8217;t have to worry about their development if a PWA is operating.</p>



<p><strong>Reliable</strong></p>



<p>When loading, the app should be bright and should be shut and open if there is not a network or a relatively low-speed network like 2G. Google discovered if the page was loaded longer than 3 seconds, that 53% of people left the website.</p>



<p><strong>User friendly</strong></p>



<p>You don&#8217;t depend on app stores with PWAs. Search engines and other platforms can find PWAs. You may also provide a PWA on social networks, on your homepage, or through another element of your ecosystem. However, app stores offer the benefit of being able to reach a wide public in one shot.</p>



<p><strong>Installable</strong></p>



<p>If we want to bring web apps closer to native applications, they must be installed and reside with other native applications on the home screen, so that the user can use PWA with only one click.</p>



<p><strong>Splash Screen</strong></p>



<p>Adds a splash screen upon starting the app to the progressive Web App. That makes the PWA more resemble a native application.</p>



<p><strong>Highly engage-able</strong></p>



<p>Users should remain engaged with the app. PWA offers features such as push notifications to help users glorify their commitment, home screen icon, the full screen, and offline-first app.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:25px"><strong>Disadvantage Of Progressive Web App</strong></p>



<p><strong>Drains battery power</strong></p>



<p>Since the phones have to work harder to comprehend the code, as they are written in complicated codes. This is why PWAs use more battery compared to native applications. So, consumers don&#8217;t worry about their battery life anymore and may not have to download such an application.</p>



<p><strong>Unable to access various device features&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>PWAs do not have access to numerous functionalities on your smartphone, therefore they are behind native applications. No access to NFC devices and also Bluetooth devices, sophisticated camera settings and so much more is available to PWAs. This means that the application is less than optimal for users.</p>



<p><strong>No access to app stores</strong></p>



<p>You are not exposed in an Apple or Android application store as a corporation if you build a <a href="https://medium.com/weekly-webtips/create-a-progressive-web-app-a-quick-tutorial-7e3b4e9c040a">PWA</a>. Apps are frequently identified since they appear on one of the renowned app marketplaces. Therefore, it is a significant drawback that this &#8220;springboard&#8221; cannot be used by a wider public.</p>



<p><strong>Functionalities&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Fewer and consequently less UX functionality. These web apps offer less functionality, unlike native apps. On Apple devices, iOS does not support complete PWAs functionality.&nbsp;</p>



<p>This means that many users have restricted choices for PWAs, which is a pity. A lack of experience in UX (user experience) is a genuine loss at least as important in a world as the marketing of the product itself.</p>



<p><strong>Lesser technical option</strong></p>



<p>It is not possible to apply to PWAs all technical alternatives, such as Bluetooth or Near Field Communication (NFC). This implies that the applications you may have for your application are restricted. The question is whether PWAs can also make use of other future advances.</p>



<h4 style="font-size:22px">Conclusion</h4>



<p>Using the Progressive Web App you have read the benefits and cons for development. In the end, it is vital that you have your application supported and solved problems on time by the proper PWA app development firm.</p>



<p><em>If you are looking to</em><a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"><em> hire an application developer for your application,</em></a><em> you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/progressive-web-app-advantages-and-disadvantages/">Progressive Web App Advantages And Disadvantages</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/progressive-web-app-advantages-and-disadvantages/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Improve Your Business With A Mobile App</title>
		<link>/blog/how-to-improve-your-business-with-a-mobile-app/</link>
					<comments>/blog/how-to-improve-your-business-with-a-mobile-app/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 07:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cross platform mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Custom Relationship Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[offers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OutSourcing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[App development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Improve business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile app Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6433</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A mobile app plays an important part in the growth of any business in the 21st century. The mobile app successfully enhances client loyalty, brand recognition, and efficiency for a company. Each entrepreneur&#8217;s objective is to enhance its sales and retain its customers in a rapid turnaround. They employed plenty of ads, leaflets, pamphlets, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/how-to-improve-your-business-with-a-mobile-app/">How To Improve Your Business With A Mobile App</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A mobile app plays an important part in the growth of any business in the 21st century. The mobile app successfully enhances client loyalty, brand recognition, and efficiency for a company.</p>



<p>Each entrepreneur&#8217;s objective is to enhance its sales and retain its customers in a rapid turnaround. They employed plenty of ads, leaflets, pamphlets, and catalogs a number of years ago to promote sales.</p>



<p>In addition, the notion of the mobile app is vital not only for major companies but also for small enterprises. In addition, a mobile app discusses the full advantages.</p>



<p>Mobile applications are great for any business growth. No random individual or company does, but many studies of various kinds of enterprises have demonstrated this.</p>



<p>So How To Improve Your Business With A Mobile App? Read on to find out.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:35px"><strong>How To Improve Your Business With Mobile App</strong></p>



<p><strong>Better Branding</strong></p>



<p>Mobile applications may assist raise brand recognition and improve loyalty to individuals. It is easy to forget or disregard whether the name or emblem of your organization is shown on the user&#8217;s mobile device. In addition, mobile applications include other capabilities, for example, push notifications.</p>



<p>A particular offer to draw consumers&#8217; attention might be reminded. Such personal branding will only work if you have the appropriate information or knowledge of your clients.</p>



<p><strong>Brings new customers</strong>&nbsp;</p>



<p>A mobile app is the leading digital platform to reach and attract new users with its broad audience. Mobile apps with user-friendly features may be readily downloaded from the app store and it also provides users 24&#215;7 access from wherever without any restriction.</p>



<p>The greatest approach to increase your business reach is with a powerful mobile app for your company. We all know that mobile apps are incredibly simple to use, making your mobile app increasingly available to clients.</p>



<p>The app also offers consumers a number of amenities that can be accessed with a few clicks. It&#8217;s a sensible move to get new clients into your business to develop a mobile app for your business.</p>



<p><strong>Customer Engagement</strong></p>



<p>Nearly 30 hours are spent on mobile applications each month. This provides companies a fantastic chance to get customers involved and get the desired result. As people already utilize their mobile devices, the commission rate on applications is higher.</p>



<p>All they need to do is launch the app and within a few seconds, you have the desired outcome. An easy approach to enhance involvement is to share social media which enables people to share their material and bring you more eyeballs on social media platforms.</p>



<p><strong>Increases loyal customers&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Customers may keep exclusive deals for all businesses at regular intervals. Mobile applications are the greatest way to tell clients about any decrease in the price of a certain product or service.</p>



<p>Offers and discount coupons are important in replicating and building a solid relationship with the prior consumers in any <a href="https://www.bigcommerce.com/blog/">e-commerce</a> business. Mobile applications are fantastic to develop client loyalty to your company.</p>



<p>And mobile applications are fantastic for building client loyalty for your organization with ongoing commitment through alerts and a customer service system.</p>



<p><strong>Push Notifications</strong></p>



<p>Push notifications are a great method to remind your clients to buy their favorite products. You can also market new items or services to regular purchasers based on their previous purchases and interests to keep them as loyal clients with the use of the push notification function in your mobile app.</p>



<p>On the other side, you may inform them about the discounts or deals that you are now offering. So give them a place to connect with and appreciate your brand directly. All of this helps to generate more visitors and more purchases.</p>



<p><strong>Competitive Advantage</strong></p>



<p>In this day, because of the tough competition on the app market, you cannot afford to be lazy. Well, your competitors and the services and goods that you provide require some time to investigate. You&#8217;re going to be creative from here.</p>



<p>You may attract more clients to your businesses if you are careful with this element. After that, you will have the opportunity to do a timely analysis to enhance these services.</p>



<p>This field should not be forgotten that it is not static. That is why when it comes to generating income for your application you have to do your best progress.</p>



<p><strong>Boost Profits</strong></p>



<p>Typically, sales also improve as customer happiness increases. The more individuals with your product and business are engaged and happy, the more consumer demand will increase.</p>



<p>And if you can&#8217;t wait to receive a product from your consumers, let me guarantee you that this request will provide you some big returns.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:25px"><strong>Conclusion</strong></p>



<p>You must understand the previous discussion on the importance of developing a mobile application to promote the brand, expand the accessibility of your services and raise your business sales.</p>



<p>So, I propose that you develop apps on both Android and iOS platforms if you have decided to make a mobile app. Both platforms are popular and your application may reach a pretty big number of users on these platforms.</p>



<p><em>If you are looking to</em><a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"><em> hire a mobile app developer for your application</em></a><em>, you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.&nbsp;</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/how-to-improve-your-business-with-a-mobile-app/">How To Improve Your Business With A Mobile App</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/how-to-improve-your-business-with-a-mobile-app/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is React Native Important In 2021?</title>
		<link>/blog/is-react-native-important-in-2021/</link>
					<comments>/blog/is-react-native-important-in-2021/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 07:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cross platform mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ionic Framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[JavaScript]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[App development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Native app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[react native]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6463</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/is-react-native-important-in-2021/">Is React Native Important In 2021?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p>There has been a really good option for indigenous development for quite some time now and this is React Native development. By utilizing the same code on all platforms, the major benefit is decreased time and cost.</p>
<p>Due to the worldwide pandemic and loss of direct relations between friends, participation in cultural events, and the operation of a business in the model we knew before, online shopping, gaming, social media trends have certainly grown over the last year.</p>
<p>We have found new smartphone apps that have enabled us to continue with most of our activities in many situations. You have to keep an eye on the facts if you want to create a mobile application.</p>
<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size: 35px"><strong>What is React Native?</strong></p>
<p>React Native is a complete framework for building mobile apps and reacting to native <a href="https://medium.com/flutter-community/create-a-cross-platform-app-using-flutter-in-2021-59e582cb625f">cross Platforms</a>. React Native is the finest technology to create an application for both iOS and Android.</p>
<p>The codebase may be reduced by roughly 95%, saving you time and money. It has several open-source libraries with pre-construction components and therefore accelerates the development process.</p>
<p>React Native apps have been designed with strong and state-of-the-art technology to enable companies around the world to reach new clients on mobile platforms.</p>
<p><strong>Native application</strong></p>
<p>Native applications are installed in an app store. They are particularly built for one platform and can use all smartphone capabilities, like the camera, GPS, speed meter, compass, contact list, etc.</p>
<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size: 30px"><strong>React Native is better than Native?</strong></p>
<p>React native is better and unique because it has</p>
<ul>
<li>Lower the <strong>development time</strong></li>
<li>Easy for <strong>Web developers </strong></li>
<li>Cost-effective </li>
</ul>
<p>Native </p>
<ul>
<li>High <strong>development time</strong></li>
<li>High cost</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Development Time</strong></p>
<p>In a native application, you need two distinct teams to make your application available on both platforms, i.e. the Android development team and the iOS development team. This includes additional effort and time to create a mobile app.</p>
<p>In React Native&#8217;s instance, the same developer writes a single code for both platforms, which implies that React native applications may be created for Android and iOS using the same codes.</p>
<p><strong>Mobile App Cost</strong></p>
<p>The response to the cost of developing the mobile app also helps to find the suitable technology for the creation of your mobile app. The app creation using React Native is the top mobile app development firm, but the cost of Native App Development for the same app project may be reduced by 30%-35% in comparison.</p>
<p><strong>Scalability</strong></p>
<p>It offers mobile app developers more chances in comparison with Native technology to handle a greater quantity of work in an app and to publish higher-functionality updates. The winner in terms of scalability of the Native app vs the Reacts Native app is thus React Native.</p>
<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size: 28px"><strong>React Native for Android Developers</strong></p>
<p>React Native is a smooth development in which the features of Native Code easily use, Hot Reloading, and the management of Hassle-free states lead to smooth, efficient, and efficient development.</p>
<p>A platform-sized experience, which boasts native Android and iOS components while the program runs, is the main advantage React Native offers.</p>
<p>This makes it possible for natives to manage the interaction even with a coding foundation written in JavaScript, so that memory, footprint, flexibility, and experience stay preserved.</p>
<p>It is compatible with native code. React Native is a structure that allows you to create the most powerful applications in combination with JavaScript. It offers impeccable performance with native components, guaranteeing that most applications operate seamlessly and native apps operate more often than before.</p>
<p>Reduce time to develop. Apart from open source projects, app developers might experience a 40 percent quicker development time because many elements can be used locally. Reaction Native also supports both Android and iOS, making it easy for both platforms to exchange data and a single code base. The task may therefore be accomplished in less time.</p>
<p>React Native comes with a Live Reload functionality which allows you to view the newest updates as soon as they are made. This makes it easy for the developer. We are passionate about online and mobile app development, we only advise our clients what is correct.</p>
<p>Find the ideal technological combination. You may use React Native to list your application in the Appstore and Playstore and make use of the sensors and device functionality and also wish to perform effectively. The first thing you want to do is to upgrade the mobile app and explore React Native.</p>
<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size: 25px"><strong>Conclusion</strong></p>
<p>In summary, therefore, you know to which end you are turning if you wish to build an ever-change multi-dimensional mobile app. From startups to successful business leaders, people embrace mobile applications instead of just websites. Most of you still know that mobile apps function totally differently from the standard website.</p>
<p><em>If you are looking to</em><a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"><em> hire an application developer, </em></a><em> you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.</em></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/is-react-native-important-in-2021/">Is React Native Important In 2021?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/is-react-native-important-in-2021/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why We Love Hybrid Mobile App Development</title>
		<link>/blog/why-we-love-hybrid-mobile-app-development/</link>
					<comments>/blog/why-we-love-hybrid-mobile-app-development/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 06:04:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hasotech.com/?p=2412</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/why-we-love-hybrid-mobile-app-development/">Why We Love Hybrid Mobile App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p>We have been talking Hybrid Mobile App development in <a href="http://www.hasotech.com/blog/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">many articles</a>. You might be wondering what&#8217;s in Hybrid Mobile App Development and what makes <a href="http://www.hasotech.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Hasoians</a> to write more articles on it. Hybrid technologies and it&#8217;s supportive on different platforms makes best.  Sorry, Not different platforms, It&#8217;s on all the platforms.</p>
<p>Hybrid Application development always reduces the development time and cost which made many of our clients beneficiary. And recent updates of Hybrid Application development makes deployment on Web and as Desktop Applications too.</p>
<h3>What can a Hybrid Mobile App do?</h3>
<p>The same thing as explained in other articles before. With Hybrid Mobile App development we can able to deploy on different platforms. Oh, wait, not only on web platforms, Now we can able to deploy it as Desktop Application and Web Application.</p>
<h4 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/secrets-successful-hybrid-mobile-apps/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Secrets of the Successful Hybrid Mobile Apps</a></h4>
<p>Progressive Web Apps are the next generation of web applications. Since the usage of mobile phones has been increased drastically. All the web applications are being developed with complete mobile optimized. But making the UI (User Interface) alone as mobile-optimized is not enough. There are lots of things to be considered for making a Mobile Optimized Web applications and that comes with Progressive Web Apps.</p>
<p>So what? <strong>Can a Hybrid Mobile App development help to make a Progressive Web Apps?</strong></p>
<p>Yes of course, why not? Hybrid apps are web nature.</p>
<h3>Hybrid Mobile App as Desktop App?</h3>
<p>And again the same answer, Why not? There are many Hybrid Desktop existing but the beauty part is. When you can deploy the code that you made for mobile application as a Desktop application. Hybrid Mobile App development can make it.</p>
<h3>What can we deploy with Hybrid Mobile App Development?</h3>
<p>Here we go with a list of applications what we can deploy with Hybrid Mobile App Development.</p>
<h4 class="stripe_2" style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/double-your-profit-with-mobile-app-for-blog/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Double Your Profit With Mobile App for Blog</a></h4>
<ul>
<li>Android Mobile and Tablet Applications</li>
<li>iOS Mobile and iPad Applications</li>
<li>Windows Mobile Applications</li>
<li>Windows Desktop Applications</li>
<li>Progressive Web Applications</li>
<li>Universal Windows Applications</li>
</ul>
<h3>Does Hybrid Mobile App Development support Native Mobile Functions?</h3>
<p>One of the reasons why some hesitate to go with Hybrid Mobile App development is, worrying about native functions. Like NativeMobile Application Development uses libraries to access native functions like camera, Bluetooth, NFC, Fingerprint etc.,  Hybrid Mobile App development is with many plugins which help to access all the native functions.</p>
<p>So, No worries about using Native functions in Hybrid Apps.</p>
<h3>What about Hybrid Mobile App Performance?</h3>
<p>Another main reason, Why some developers hesitate to use Hybrid platforms. When we compare the performance of Native Mobile Application and Hybrid Mobile Application, Always native performance is great. But it doesn&#8217;t mean that Hybrid Mobile app performance is very low. There might be some milliseconds lags between a Native and Hybrid Mobile applications. But is it possible to develop a Good standard application?  Experienced Hybrid Mobile app developer can make it.</p>
<h4 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/not-go-hybrid-mobile-app-development/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Don’t go with Hybrid Mobile App Development</a></h4>
<p>There are many tech giants using Hybrid platforms to develop mobile applications. Like Instagram, Facebook, Evernote, Twitter etc., At the end, Don&#8217;t hesitate to use Hybrid Mobile App development platforms. Make a small research on your own and get to know more about it.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://www.hasotech.com/hybridmobileapp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Stop wasting your time, Check this out </a></h3>
<p>Feel free to share your view on Hybrid Mobile App Development and we are happy to respond to your comments.</p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/why-we-love-hybrid-mobile-app-development/">Why We Love Hybrid Mobile App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/why-we-love-hybrid-mobile-app-development/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Is Hybrid Mobile App Development Considered Underrated</title>
		<link>/blog/hybrid-mobile-app-development-considered-underrated/</link>
					<comments>/blog/hybrid-mobile-app-development-considered-underrated/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 08:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hasotech.com/?p=2364</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/hybrid-mobile-app-development-considered-underrated/">Why Is Hybrid Mobile App Development Considered Underrated</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p><span style="font-family: 'times new roman', times, serif; font-size: 14pt;">The scope of Mobile App Development has been increasing day by day. There are Billions of Applications in Google Play store and Millions of application in App store. And many of them are in Hybrid Mobile App Development Platforms. The main reason for such amount of application in Google Play store and App store is the simplicity of Application development. Developing application has become easier one and also everyone started expressing their ideas through mobile apps. There are many technologies available to develop a mobile application. and certain drag and drop tools helps to develop a mobile application without a single line of code. </span></p>
<h4 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/hybrid-mobile-application-development/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Get to know more about Hybrid Mobile Application Development</a></h4>
<p><span style="font-family: 'times new roman', times, serif; font-size: 14pt;">Though there are many technologies available to develop a mobile application. Hybrid Mobile Application Development is one of the trending development platforms. With Native Mobile Application Development. One can able to develop a mobile app for one platform either on Android or iOS. But With Hybrid Mobile Application Development. It has made easy to develop the application and deploy it on different platforms with a single code. </span></p>
<h3>What is Hybrid Mobile App Development</h3>
<p><span style="font-family: 'times new roman', times, serif; font-size: 14pt;">If you can able to deploy an application on multiple platforms like Android, iOS, Windows etc., with a single code. For Example, If we are about to develop <strong><a href="https://www.web.hasotech.com/how-to-get-free-magento-2-mobile-app/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Magento E-commerce Mobile Application</a> </strong>in Android iOS, Then probably Hybrid Mobile Application might be the right choice.  With this we can able to deploy the application on both Android and iOS. Whereas if we choose to go with Native Mobile Application development. Then both Android and iOS have to be developed separately. And also the cost and time of developing Native Mobile application would be high. </span></p>
<h4 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.web.hasotech.com/whats-crazy-mobile-app-development/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">What’s crazy on Mobile App Development</a></h4>
<h3>Why Hybrid Mobile App Development is underrated!!</h3>
<p><span style="font-family: 'times new roman', times, serif; font-size: 14pt;">And here we come to core concept of the article. Why Is Hybrid Mobile App Development Considered Underrated?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'times new roman', times, serif; font-size: 14pt;">The main reason is the Frameworks. Ther are many frameworks available to develop Hybrid Mobile applications like Ionic Framework, React Native, Xamarin, Titanium, and the mother of all frameworks, PhoneGap. Though there are many frameworks, All the frameworks are not good as to develop a standard application. There is licensing problem on using React Native since Facebook has said that, they will start charging for it anytime. Intel HTML5 fails to provide proper native functions and No updates with PhoneGap. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'times new roman', times, serif; font-size: 14pt;">These issues made Hybrid Mobile App Development Considered Underrated. But still, there are some good frameworks like <a href="http://ionicframework.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ionic Framework,</a> which provides regular updates and many trusted companies are using it. There are many certain ways to follow to develop a standard Hybrid Mobile Application. </span></p>
<h4 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/ionic-mobile-app-developer/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">You may check about Ionic Mobile App Developer</a></h4>
<p><span style="font-family: 'times new roman', times, serif; font-size: 14pt;">If you are looking for any support on Hybrid Mobile App Development, Feel free to <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/contact-us/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>reach our consulting team</strong></a> or comment below. </span></p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/hybrid-mobile-app-development-considered-underrated/">Why Is Hybrid Mobile App Development Considered Underrated</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/hybrid-mobile-app-development-considered-underrated/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Secrets of the Successful Hybrid Mobile Apps</title>
		<link>/blog/secrets-successful-hybrid-mobile-apps/</link>
					<comments>/blog/secrets-successful-hybrid-mobile-apps/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 12:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ionic Framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hasotech.com/?p=2345</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/secrets-successful-hybrid-mobile-apps/">Secrets of the Successful Hybrid Mobile Apps</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p>Mobile apps are one of the best ways for making money. But not all the business apps or Hybrid Mobile apps are successful. If you are looking to develop a successful mobile app, that too in the Hybrid platform.  Then you must know these secrets of the successful Hybrid Mobile Apps. We have gone through several Hybrid Mobile apps that are running successfully. And we came up with some secrets that actually made those apps successful.</p>
<h2>Choosing the Right Platform</h2>
<p>When it comes to Hybrid Mobile App Development, choosing the right framework is the most important one. There are many frameworks available and PhoneGap is the mother of all. However, PhoneGap has become outdated one and there are many new frameworks with more features. Some of them are Ionic Framework, Xamarin, Unity, Titanium. Most of the Hybrid apps are powered by Cordova backbone. Out of all these frameworks, Ionic Framework is said to be the best one which provides many components and plugins. If you are a c# Developer then you may go with Xamarin or Unity. And Unity is must if you are looking at developing games.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/get-your-virtual-reality-mobile-application/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Get your Virtual Reality Mobile Application</a></h3>
<h2>Designing Hybrid Mobile Apps</h2>
<p>The more the app is user-friendly with good user experience, The more that app will be a successful one. Though there are many ready designs are available. It is better to go with a unique design which is impressive. Ionic Framework is providing many UI components which made the designing bit easier. The more we make easy to use the app and understand the concept of the app, The more chance for the success we will get.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/not-go-hybrid-mobile-app-development/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Don’t go with Hybrid Mobile App Development</a></h3>
<h2>Why Hybrid Mobile Apps</h2>
<p>This might be the first question while reading this article. Though there are native platforms available for developing Android and iOS applications. There must be a special reason to choose Hybrid mobile platform. If you are looking to make the application on a different platform in short period of time. And also in low budget, then the Hybrid platform is the best one.</p>
<p>There are many constraints to be considered before going with Hybrid Mobile apps platform. Feel free to <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/contact-us/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">contact us</a> for a free consultation on developing with Hybrid mobile apps.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/cross-platform-mobile-app-development-things-to-know/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cross Platform Mobile App Development – Things To Know</a></h3>
<h2>Choosing the right Niche</h2>
<p>Focusing on particular Niche will increase the chance of getting the app success. The more the app solves a particular problem, The more the app will get succeed. Most of the successful apps are concentrating on a very specific niche and Solving a specific problem. Also making the app more interactive and entertainment will get more user engagement.</p>
<h2>Making the Revenue Model</h2>
<p>The revenue model and the amount of revenue of an application decides the success of an app. The more revenue it gets, The more success the app is. Concentrating more on attracting a huge range of customers automatically increase revenue. More customers =  More revenue. With the ads in free app version, or launching business driving model with app surely will help for more revenue.</p>
<p>Shameless marketing is more important. After making the app with perfect UI and good revenue model, Marketing has to be done in proper way. The amount and time used to develop the application, Double it in marketing for a good reach.</p>
<p>Feel free to share your reviews over comments and <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/contact-us/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reach us</a> for any clarifications or consultations.</p>
<h4 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/double-your-profit-with-mobile-app-for-blog/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Double Your Profit With Mobile App for Blog</a></h4>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/secrets-successful-hybrid-mobile-apps/">Secrets of the Successful Hybrid Mobile Apps</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/secrets-successful-hybrid-mobile-apps/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Don&#8217;t go with Hybrid Mobile App Development</title>
		<link>/blog/not-go-hybrid-mobile-app-development/</link>
					<comments>/blog/not-go-hybrid-mobile-app-development/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2017 01:59:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hasotech.com/?p=2249</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/not-go-hybrid-mobile-app-development/">Don&#8217;t go with Hybrid Mobile App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<h1>Why You Should Not Go To Hybrid Mobile App Development</h1>
<p>Hybrid Mobile App Development is one of the best ways to develop mobile apps on different platforms. If you are looking to develop mobile apps on Android, iOS, and other platforms. Then Hybrid Mobile App Development is the best. Of course, Hybrid Mobile App Development reduces cost and time of Development. But, There are some factors to consider before going into development. Before selecting the Hybrid app Development platform. Make sure your app doesn&#8217;t fall into these categories.</p>
<p>Are you still looking for what is Hybrid Mobile App development? Check this <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/blog/mobile-application/hybrid-mobile-application-development/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">link</a> for more.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/iphone-x-ios-11-mobile-app-development/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Build Intelligent Mobile App</a></h3>
<h2>Check Lists Before going with Hybrid Mobile App Development</h2>
<p>Before selecting Hybrid App Development platform, Make sure your app doesn&#8217;t fall under below lists.</p>
<ul>
<li>Are you expecting very high performance?</li>
<li>Is your app using many native functions?</li>
<li>Does your target users know your platform?</li>
<li>Is your competitor App is using the Native platform?</li>
<li>Is the app is very complex one?</li>
<li>Any animated or graphics to be integrated with App?</li>
</ul>
<p>If the answer is YES for all the questions, Then it is better to move with Native Mobile App Development than Hybrid.</p>
<h2>Who Should use Hybrid Mobile App Development</h2>
<p>Most of the above-mentioned features are important for a Mobile app development. However, if your answer is YES for those questions but still thinking to go with Hybrid App Development. Or looking for the answer for Who should use Hybrid Mobile App Development, Here it is.</p>
<p>If you are looking to develop the App in less time and cost. Then Hybrid Mobile App Development is the best. It doesn&#8217;t mean that You will get a less performance, non-native functions using application. Hybrid App development needs an experienced developer to make effective App.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/whats-crazy-mobile-app-development/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">What’s crazy on Mobile App Development</a></h3>
<p>One can able to develop high performance, using native functions, implementing complex functionalities Hybrid Mobile app. If he is well experienced and knows how to use the Hybrid platform in the best way.  If you have confidence on your developer to get you delivered Hybrid Mobile App with all features, You can still proceed with it.</p>
<h2>Which Framework for Hybrid Mobile App Development</h2>
<p>There are many frameworks available for Hybrid Mobile App Development. And we suggest you go with <a href="http://ionicframework.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ionic Framework</a> which is good. Ionic Framework uses Angular 4 which is being used on Developing PWA Applications. Before developing the application, Make sure you get your hands dirty with Ionic Framework. If you are looking for any help on Ionic Framework, Feel free to comment below.</p>
<h3><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/ionic-mobile-app-developer/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Check more about Ionic Framework</a></h3>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>Going to Hybrid Mobile App Development, Doesn&#8217;t mean that you will get the worst application. If you choose a right framework and a Good developer. Then you can able to get a Good standard Application. Hybrid Mobile Application reduces your cost and Time. Consider your motive of developing the application and choose the right one.</p>
<p>Feel free to share your thoughts with us over Comments or Mailbox: info@hasotech.com</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/five-things-that-you-never-expect-on-mobile-app-development/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Five Things That You Never Expect On Mobile App Development</a></h3>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/not-go-hybrid-mobile-app-development/">Don&#8217;t go with Hybrid Mobile App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/not-go-hybrid-mobile-app-development/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: web.hasotech.com @ 2022-10-26 10:36:50 by W3 Total Cache
-->