<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>AngularJS Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<atom:link href="/blog/tag/angularjs/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/tag/angularjs/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 07:45:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/cropped-logo-1-rb-32x32.png</url>
	<title>AngularJS Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/tag/angularjs/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Is AngularJS Good or Bad For Your Web Development?</title>
		<link>/blog/blog-is-angularjs-good-or-bad-for-your-web-development/</link>
					<comments>/blog/blog-is-angularjs-good-or-bad-for-your-web-development/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[MEAN Stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OutSourcing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Angular]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AngularJS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[front-end web framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web app]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6372</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The creation of Web applications is always seen as a challenging undertaking in ensuring the collaboration of the user interface, all the components, and the database data. Many web apps are made from server-side technology. Since AngularJS has both good and bad features for web applications. However, greater customer logic, because the processing capabilities of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/blog-is-angularjs-good-or-bad-for-your-web-development/">Is AngularJS Good or Bad For Your Web Development?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The creation of Web applications is always seen as a challenging undertaking in ensuring the collaboration of the user interface, all the components, and the database data. Many web apps are made from server-side technology. Since AngularJS has both good and bad features for web applications.</p>



<p>However, greater customer logic, because the processing capabilities of today&#8217;s terminals are good, is the most recent demand. To fulfill this demand, many Javascript Frameworks are introduced. Angularjs are especially advisable among these.</p>



<p>You will discover whether AngularJS is helpful or harmful for your web development in this post. Let us briefly reconstruct the key advantages of original AngularJS, among other front-end development frameworks, and identify the main disadvantages of the instrument.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><strong>What Is AngularJS</strong></p>



<p><strong>AngularJS </strong>is a javascript open-source framework used to create Single Page dynamic applications. The syntax of HTML will be extended to provide a succinct and definite demonstration of application components.</p>



<p>We can create with Angularjs. The administration of front-end management procedures was simplified. It decreases the code you want to develop. Angular JS supports developers in creating apps at the architectural level.</p>



<p>Packed with several frameworks and plugins suitable for developers and designers alike. Desktop, mobile, and tablet applications were created utilizing the newest angular9 react across platforms.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><strong>Why Should You Use AngularJS For Your Web Development?</strong></p>



<p><strong>Two-way data binding</strong> </p>



<p>It was created with the architecture of the model view controller. And the frame of the model and the view synced. When the data changes in the model, the view also changes. The binding of two ways of data helped engineers to minimize the duration of development because no new code was required to create ongoing views and models.</p>



<p><strong>Supports SPA features</strong></p>



<p>A quicker website transition is the key reason for building single-page apps. The website works and looks like an app. Instead of using the browser default technique for loading new pages, the Website will dynamically communicate with the Web browser by replacing the old website with new webserver information. This is known as a <a href="https://medium.com/@NeotericEU/single-page-application-vs-multiple-page-application-2591588efe58">Single Page Application (SPA)</a>.</p>



<p><strong>Dom manipulations</strong></p>



<p>The view extends the dom to show data and manipulates the dom to embed behavior. But the dom-manipulation code is within the directives and not in the view with angular. It implies that views containing placeholder data such as the HTML Page are shown. This vision fits nicely with the designers of the user interface.</p>



<p><strong>Optimal Web Application Management</strong></p>



<p>The code generally must be broken down into three separate components: Modeling, Viewing, and Control (MVC). The developers then integrate their components&#8217; code manually.</p>



<p>It saves time when this frame strings code together automatically. Application data is maintained and managed by the model component.</p>



<p>The view component presents to users all of the data or parts of the data. While the control component determines how the model and the view are linked.</p>



<p><strong>Community</strong> </p>



<p>This framework was quite popular among developers right from the very beginning. A robust community has given sufficient training materials, conversations, and tools for third parties to start utilizing this framework and find a solution to virtually any problem emerging.</p>



<p><strong>Frequent Testing </strong></p>



<p>Using this framework, developers may check an app to guarantee the application is error-free as often as feasible. This is one of the main advantages of building AngularJS web apps. This takes care of the entire object lifecycle. Developers need not bother about namespace and instance. This frame eliminates handling and dynamic loading problems.</p>



<p><strong>Powerful Framework</strong></p>



<p>A solid solution for speedier front-end development is another benefit for this. It contains several characteristics, including MVC patterns, directives, and the injection of dependencies. It is a frequently available platform among developers. Developers can therefore enhance the HTML syntax and construct client-side apps.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><strong>Why You Shouldn&#8217;t Use AngularJS For Your Web Development?</strong></p>



<p><strong>Specific Libraries</strong></p>



<p>This framework does not operate effectively with other libraries. There is an issue. You will need to utilize various test stacks while testing a single rich app with several JavaScript iterations.</p>



<p><strong>Not Secure </strong></p>



<p>The apps developed with this framework are not safe as a JavaScript-only framework. Authentication and authorization on the server side are required to secure an application.</p>



<p><strong>Lagging UI</strong></p>



<p>If more than 2000 observers are present, but the user interface can delay considerably. the potential intricacy of the angular shapes is therefore restricted. This covers the grids and lists of big data.</p>



<p><strong>JavaScript support mandatory</strong></p>



<p>It is a JavaScript frame when JS is deactivated to access numerous PCs and laptops. That implies you may not be able to access your website by people linked with such a system.</p>



<h4 class="has-medium-font-size">Conclusion</h4>



<p>Hope you have learned why AngularJS should and should not be used. In the end, your web development needs to have the proper AngularJS. We are here to help you apply and solve your problems on schedule.<br /><em>If you are looking to<a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"> hire an AngularJS application developer for your application</a>, you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/blog-is-angularjs-good-or-bad-for-your-web-development/">Is AngularJS Good or Bad For Your Web Development?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/blog-is-angularjs-good-or-bad-for-your-web-development/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Is MEAN Stack Development?</title>
		<link>/blog/what-is-mean-stack-development/</link>
					<comments>/blog/what-is-mean-stack-development/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[JavaScript]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LAMP Stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MEAN Stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stack Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AngularJS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Expressjs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lamp stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MEAN stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[monogodb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nodejs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6419</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It is certainly a digital era in the twenty-first century. And you need a standardized and consistent MEAN stack in order to create an application from scratch in this age. However, a wealth of software stacks such as LAMP, Ruby on Rails, and many more are available in the current environment. The piled field was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/what-is-mean-stack-development/">What Is MEAN Stack Development?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>It is certainly a digital era in the twenty-first century. And you need a standardized and consistent MEAN stack in order to create an application from scratch in this age.</p>



<p>However, a wealth of software stacks such as LAMP, Ruby on Rails, and many more are available in the current environment. The piled field was packed with its abundance.</p>



<p>That is why many developers are employing a variety of technologies today for mobile, web, and app development to get better and quicker outcomes. Thus MEAN Stack is used by developers.</p>



<p>You&#8217;ll see What is MEAN Stack in this article? The significance and advantages of the frameworks.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:35px"><strong>What is MEAN Stack?</strong></p>



<p>MEAN is a JavaScript-based technology collection that includes MongoDB, Express.js, AngularJS, and Node.js. A new age of creating robust, fast, and scalable Web applications leveraging its powerful design patterns such as model/view/controller (MVC) is released by the lightweight and highly efficient MEAN stack.&nbsp;</p>



<p>It&#8217;s software open source. It&#8217;s quick-running and structured. The stack utilizes just JavaScript programming language. This means that every level of the program works in one language. It&#8217;s a flexible stack for building both mobile and online applications.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:33px"><strong>Frameworks Of MEAN Stack Development</strong></p>



<p><strong>MongoDB</strong></p>



<p>The application data is stored in this framework. Due to Javascript in the database and the program, when an object moves inside the software, the requirement to translate is skipped.</p>



<p><a href="https://medium.com/chingu/an-overview-of-mongodb-mongoose-b980858a8994">MongoDB </a>is very scalable, performing and storing well. It excels at large data handling overall. Developers may use it easily to create fields and accomplish their job simpler.</p>



<p>MongoDB is famous for its speed and storage scalability. You may also add fields to the database without refreshing the whole table.</p>



<p><strong>ExpressJS</strong></p>



<p>The backend for a MEAN Stack application is this framework. Express.js supports interactions between the web application&#8217;s database and the front end. It forms part of a seamless flow of data to the end-user. The chain is efficient. It avoids overwriting of variables by developers.</p>



<p>Express.js&#8217; approach is minimalism. It is capable of efficiently handling all procedures. The minimalist nature doesn&#8217;t mean featureless. It must be noted.</p>



<p>It avoids overwriting of variables by developers. In this way, a variable that you created before cannot be mistakenly redefined. This contributes to saving a lot of money and time.</p>



<p><strong>AngularJS</strong></p>



<p>AngularJS is an extremely popular JavaScript front-end frame. The Angular JS server is used in the MEAN stack to create the application&#8217;s user-facing side.</p>



<p>JavaScript builds the front end, backend, and database. As a result, all elements of the application have a fluid data flow.</p>



<p>Angular JS, with its easy-to-use templates and finely tuned performance, is a perfect front-end frame. In addition, apps for both mobile and desktop may be developed simultaneously.</p>



<p><strong>Node.JS</strong></p>



<p>Node.JS is MEAN Stack&#8217;s backbone. Express.js is specially built to work with Node.js. Node.JS also links to Angular JS for the fast delivery of data.Node.JS enables the deployment of the MongoDB database in the cloud easier thanks to an integrated webserver.&nbsp;</p>



<p>It is extremely scalable and may be connected to thousands of concurrent links. Compared to a resource-heavy resource, it is compatible with small resource demands.</p>



<h4>How does MEAN Stack Works?</h4>



<p>In MEAN Stack development follows five phases.</p>



<ul><li>In the <strong>first phase, </strong>AngularJS is used as a customer language while working with Javascript. This implies that AngularJS handles it when a customer requests.</li><li>In the <strong>second phase</strong>, The application is making its way to Node.JS, the language side of the server.</li><li>In the <strong>third phase</strong>, Express JS enters an application for a database inquiry.</li><li>In the <strong>fourth phase</strong>, MongoDB accesses the information and returns the appropriate answer to ExpressJS.</li><li>And in the <strong>last phase, </strong>This reply then goes back to NodeJS and subsequently back to AngularJS.</li></ul>



<h5>Advantages of MEAN Stack Development</h5>



<p><strong>Ease of Isomorphic Coding</strong></p>



<p>A significant advantage of adopting MEAN Stack Development Technology in web development is the ease with which code that is developed in one framework is transferred to another. This not only increases productivity significantly, but it also improves the performance as the transmission of data across the application layers is done in the form of the JavaScript Object Notation (JSON).</p>



<p><strong>High flexibility</strong></p>



<p>The developer may simply test the application on a cloud platform when the app development is complete. MEAN stack is extremely versatile since the application without any problems may be developed, tested, and introduced. In addition, adding a field to the form, allows you to enter more information. MongoDB supports the entire cluster and automated replication.</p>



<p><strong>Cost-effectiveness</strong></p>



<p>Total developers are not so required for MEAN Stack, while others demand developers with a wealth of knowledge of JavaScript, MySQL, and PHP technologies. MEAN stack is an economic web development technique that simply relies on developers&#8217; Javascript skills.</p>



<p><strong>High Speed &amp; Reusability</strong></p>



<p>Thanks to the non-blocking design of Node.js, the creation of the MEAN stack is rapid and reusable. In addition, AngularJS offers testability, reusability, and maintenance, which is an open-source JavaScript framework. Once the libraries have been built they may be utilized easily for the front end and the backend, which will increase productivity considerably.</p>



<p><strong>Cloud compatible</strong></p>



<p>For the development process, the MEAN stack leverages libraries and public repositories. When using this technology, the overall development cost is also lower. Furthermore, MongoDB leverages the cloud features of the app to save disc space costs.</p>



<p><strong>Ease of Debugging</strong></p>



<p>Since MEAN Stack uses only one language to operate in layers, the execution thread can be traced more easily. Developers can monitor the manipulation of the data and debug the flow with a consistent set of open-source tools.</p>



<p><strong>Single Language Usage</strong></p>



<p>The whole development code is provided in JavaScript, which includes the client and the server-side while working with the MEAN Stack technologies. This makes it easier for both front-end developers and backend developers to learn from MEAN Stack development. Developers don&#8217;t have to worry about the interoperability of code between multiple levels.</p>



<h6>Conclusion</h6>



<p>The technology of MEAN stacking keeps improving every day. MEAN stack technologies are used widely by most of the major online and mobile app developing businesses in the delivery of cutting-edge web and mobile apps.</p>



<p><em>If you are looking to</em><a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"><em> hire a MEAN Stack developer for your application</em></a><em>, you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.&nbsp;</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/what-is-mean-stack-development/">What Is MEAN Stack Development?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/what-is-mean-stack-development/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: web.hasotech.com @ 2022-10-26 12:09:20 by W3 Total Cache
-->