<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>LAMP Stack Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<atom:link href="/blog/category/lamp-stack/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/category/lamp-stack/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:08:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/cropped-logo-1-rb-32x32.png</url>
	<title>LAMP Stack Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/category/lamp-stack/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>What Is MEAN Stack Development?</title>
		<link>/blog/what-is-mean-stack-development/</link>
					<comments>/blog/what-is-mean-stack-development/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[JavaScript]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LAMP Stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MEAN Stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stack Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AngularJS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Expressjs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lamp stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MEAN stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[monogodb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nodejs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6419</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It is certainly a digital era in the twenty-first century. And you need a standardized and consistent MEAN stack in order to create an application from scratch in this age. However, a wealth of software stacks such as LAMP, Ruby on Rails, and many more are available in the current environment. The piled field was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/what-is-mean-stack-development/">What Is MEAN Stack Development?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>It is certainly a digital era in the twenty-first century. And you need a standardized and consistent MEAN stack in order to create an application from scratch in this age.</p>



<p>However, a wealth of software stacks such as LAMP, Ruby on Rails, and many more are available in the current environment. The piled field was packed with its abundance.</p>



<p>That is why many developers are employing a variety of technologies today for mobile, web, and app development to get better and quicker outcomes. Thus MEAN Stack is used by developers.</p>



<p>You&#8217;ll see What is MEAN Stack in this article? The significance and advantages of the frameworks.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:35px"><strong>What is MEAN Stack?</strong></p>



<p>MEAN is a JavaScript-based technology collection that includes MongoDB, Express.js, AngularJS, and Node.js. A new age of creating robust, fast, and scalable Web applications leveraging its powerful design patterns such as model/view/controller (MVC) is released by the lightweight and highly efficient MEAN stack.&nbsp;</p>



<p>It&#8217;s software open source. It&#8217;s quick-running and structured. The stack utilizes just JavaScript programming language. This means that every level of the program works in one language. It&#8217;s a flexible stack for building both mobile and online applications.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:33px"><strong>Frameworks Of MEAN Stack Development</strong></p>



<p><strong>MongoDB</strong></p>



<p>The application data is stored in this framework. Due to Javascript in the database and the program, when an object moves inside the software, the requirement to translate is skipped.</p>



<p><a href="https://medium.com/chingu/an-overview-of-mongodb-mongoose-b980858a8994">MongoDB </a>is very scalable, performing and storing well. It excels at large data handling overall. Developers may use it easily to create fields and accomplish their job simpler.</p>



<p>MongoDB is famous for its speed and storage scalability. You may also add fields to the database without refreshing the whole table.</p>



<p><strong>ExpressJS</strong></p>



<p>The backend for a MEAN Stack application is this framework. Express.js supports interactions between the web application&#8217;s database and the front end. It forms part of a seamless flow of data to the end-user. The chain is efficient. It avoids overwriting of variables by developers.</p>



<p>Express.js&#8217; approach is minimalism. It is capable of efficiently handling all procedures. The minimalist nature doesn&#8217;t mean featureless. It must be noted.</p>



<p>It avoids overwriting of variables by developers. In this way, a variable that you created before cannot be mistakenly redefined. This contributes to saving a lot of money and time.</p>



<p><strong>AngularJS</strong></p>



<p>AngularJS is an extremely popular JavaScript front-end frame. The Angular JS server is used in the MEAN stack to create the application&#8217;s user-facing side.</p>



<p>JavaScript builds the front end, backend, and database. As a result, all elements of the application have a fluid data flow.</p>



<p>Angular JS, with its easy-to-use templates and finely tuned performance, is a perfect front-end frame. In addition, apps for both mobile and desktop may be developed simultaneously.</p>



<p><strong>Node.JS</strong></p>



<p>Node.JS is MEAN Stack&#8217;s backbone. Express.js is specially built to work with Node.js. Node.JS also links to Angular JS for the fast delivery of data.Node.JS enables the deployment of the MongoDB database in the cloud easier thanks to an integrated webserver.&nbsp;</p>



<p>It is extremely scalable and may be connected to thousands of concurrent links. Compared to a resource-heavy resource, it is compatible with small resource demands.</p>



<h4>How does MEAN Stack Works?</h4>



<p>In MEAN Stack development follows five phases.</p>



<ul><li>In the <strong>first phase, </strong>AngularJS is used as a customer language while working with Javascript. This implies that AngularJS handles it when a customer requests.</li><li>In the <strong>second phase</strong>, The application is making its way to Node.JS, the language side of the server.</li><li>In the <strong>third phase</strong>, Express JS enters an application for a database inquiry.</li><li>In the <strong>fourth phase</strong>, MongoDB accesses the information and returns the appropriate answer to ExpressJS.</li><li>And in the <strong>last phase, </strong>This reply then goes back to NodeJS and subsequently back to AngularJS.</li></ul>



<h5>Advantages of MEAN Stack Development</h5>



<p><strong>Ease of Isomorphic Coding</strong></p>



<p>A significant advantage of adopting MEAN Stack Development Technology in web development is the ease with which code that is developed in one framework is transferred to another. This not only increases productivity significantly, but it also improves the performance as the transmission of data across the application layers is done in the form of the JavaScript Object Notation (JSON).</p>



<p><strong>High flexibility</strong></p>



<p>The developer may simply test the application on a cloud platform when the app development is complete. MEAN stack is extremely versatile since the application without any problems may be developed, tested, and introduced. In addition, adding a field to the form, allows you to enter more information. MongoDB supports the entire cluster and automated replication.</p>



<p><strong>Cost-effectiveness</strong></p>



<p>Total developers are not so required for MEAN Stack, while others demand developers with a wealth of knowledge of JavaScript, MySQL, and PHP technologies. MEAN stack is an economic web development technique that simply relies on developers&#8217; Javascript skills.</p>



<p><strong>High Speed &amp; Reusability</strong></p>



<p>Thanks to the non-blocking design of Node.js, the creation of the MEAN stack is rapid and reusable. In addition, AngularJS offers testability, reusability, and maintenance, which is an open-source JavaScript framework. Once the libraries have been built they may be utilized easily for the front end and the backend, which will increase productivity considerably.</p>



<p><strong>Cloud compatible</strong></p>



<p>For the development process, the MEAN stack leverages libraries and public repositories. When using this technology, the overall development cost is also lower. Furthermore, MongoDB leverages the cloud features of the app to save disc space costs.</p>



<p><strong>Ease of Debugging</strong></p>



<p>Since MEAN Stack uses only one language to operate in layers, the execution thread can be traced more easily. Developers can monitor the manipulation of the data and debug the flow with a consistent set of open-source tools.</p>



<p><strong>Single Language Usage</strong></p>



<p>The whole development code is provided in JavaScript, which includes the client and the server-side while working with the MEAN Stack technologies. This makes it easier for both front-end developers and backend developers to learn from MEAN Stack development. Developers don&#8217;t have to worry about the interoperability of code between multiple levels.</p>



<h6>Conclusion</h6>



<p>The technology of MEAN stacking keeps improving every day. MEAN stack technologies are used widely by most of the major online and mobile app developing businesses in the delivery of cutting-edge web and mobile apps.</p>



<p><em>If you are looking to</em><a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"><em> hire a MEAN Stack developer for your application</em></a><em>, you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.&nbsp;</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/what-is-mean-stack-development/">What Is MEAN Stack Development?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/what-is-mean-stack-development/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why LAMP Stack For Your Web Application?</title>
		<link>/blog/why-lamp-stack-for-your-web-application/</link>
					<comments>/blog/why-lamp-stack-for-your-web-application/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 07:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[JavaScript]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LAMP Stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MEAN Stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PHP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stack Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Apache]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lamp stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linux]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MEAN stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MySql]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web app]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6426</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Solution Stacks are a mix of computer software and application applications. The aim is to offer the proper foundation for web applications. Multiple developers are technical in developing, maintaining, and managing the different components. However, many developers can execute the whole solution LAMP stack component. It is known as Full-Stack developers. The packs are usually [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/why-lamp-stack-for-your-web-application/">Why LAMP Stack For Your Web Application?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Solution Stacks are a mix of computer software and application applications. The aim is to offer the proper foundation for web applications. Multiple developers are technical in developing, maintaining, and managing the different components. However, many developers can execute the whole solution LAMP stack component.</p>



<p>It is known as Full-Stack developers. The packs are usually called according to the components utilized, resulting in an acronym. This method of naming helps you recall the parts utilized and explain the entire stack components. In this article, we’ll discuss “LAMP Stack” You may get knowledge, advantages, and functionality of a LAMP stack.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:35px"><strong>What is LAMP Stack?</strong></p>



<p>A <strong>LAMP stack </strong>is an open-source bundle of software for websites and Web applications that may be used. LAMP is an abbreviation that usually includes the operating system of <strong>Linux</strong>, <strong>Apache</strong> HTTP Server, <strong>MySQL</strong> relational database management system, and the language of <strong>PHP</strong> programming.</p>



<p>LAMP comprises four elements named LAMP STACK combined.</p>



<ul><li>Operating System</li><li>Webserver</li><li>Database&nbsp;</li><li>Scripting&nbsp;</li></ul>



<p><strong>Operating System</strong></p>



<p>Our initial piece is the operating system (OS). For the stack model, Linux lays the basis. On this layer, all other layers are running. Linux is the lowest layer and the operating system supplies it.</p>



<p>Each component is running Linux. However, you do not restrict yourself particularly to Linux; it is easy for you to execute any component on Microsoft Windows and Mac OS X or Unix if necessary.</p>



<p>The foundation of the stack pattern is set by Linux and is used to host web apps. The operating system is the lowest layer of the stack, with all other layers on top of the layer. Make it the LAMP stack&#8217;s backbone.</p>



<p><strong>Webserver</strong></p>



<p>The second part of the stack is the Apache webserver. A web server is server software that satisfies the requirements of customers around the world. The matching client to server is then done through HTTP (HyperText Transfer Protocol).</p>



<p>This layer is located above the Linux layer. Web servers shall translate their proper webpage from web browsers. Mechanics for a user to access a webpage are provided by Apache.</p>



<p>It operates more than 65 percent of all internet-based sites and is a reliable, mission-critical, and competent server. PHP is within Apache and you construct your dynamic pages together by using Apache and PHP.</p>



<p><strong>Database&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Databases dwell in the 3rd element. Details that may be requested to build a website using MySQL are saved. MySQL normally resides next to the Apache/layer on top of the Linux layer. MySQL can be downloaded to a second host server in high-end setups. MySQL supplies the LAMP system&#8217;s data storage side.</p>



<p>You have access to a very competent database for big and complicated locations using MySQL. In the format, you can simply query with the SQL language all your information, products, accounts, and other information kinds will be available in this database within your Web application.</p>



<p>Collectively, this layer may comprise user accounts, user information, descriptive product names, or even website analytics. Web managers may have to edit their website material frequently and users may need to change its content. Inclusion of the database layer may do so.</p>



<p><strong>Scripting</strong></p>



<p>PHP is the original stack&#8217;s fourth piece since it interacts extremely well with MySQL. It is often used for web development since it is a language with dynamical characteristics which makes working with it fast and easy.</p>



<p>If you are a newbie, this feature is very attractive. PHP is so useful because it can be integrated with HTML so that you may jump in and out as you desire.</p>



<p>PHP is a simple, effective language for programming, which sticks the other elements of the LAMP system together. In the MySQL database and some of the functions provided by Linux, you write dynamic contents with PHP to access data.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:33px"><strong>LAMP Stack Alternatives</strong></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><strong>Open-source alternatives are:</strong></p>



<ul><li><strong><a href="https://www.hostnamaste.com/blog/how-to-install-the-lemp-stack/">LEMP</a> </strong>(Linux, NGINX, MySQL/MariaDB, PHP/Perl/Python)</li><li><strong>LAPP </strong>(Linux, Apache, PostgreSQL, PHP)</li><li><strong>LEAP </strong>(Linux, Eucalyptus, AppScale, Python)</li><li><strong>LLMP </strong>(Linux, Lighttpd, MySQL/MariaDB, PHP/Perl/Python)</li></ul>



<p>While non-open source alternatives include:</p>



<ul><li><strong>WAMP </strong>(Windows, Apache, MySQL/MariaDB, PHP/Perl/Python)</li><li><strong>WIMP</strong>(Windows, Internet Information Services, MySQL/MariaDB, PHP/Perl/Python)</li><li><strong>MAMP</strong> (Mac OS x, Apache, MySQL/MariaDB, PHP/Perl/Python)</li></ul>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:30px"><strong>Advantages Of LAMP</strong></p>



<p><strong>Scalability</strong></p>



<p>Every LAMP stack development program or website you design might expand in size or decrease based on your needs. You hold the secret to making your blog easier to use.</p>



<p><strong>Highly secure</strong></p>



<p>We can guarantee that this technology is highly safe thanks to the number of updates, encryptions, security architectures, and much more in Lamp Stack.</p>



<p><strong>Customization</strong></p>



<p>The person will be able to personalize the app by the user. Customizing using LAMP will never be a problem. In a few steps, you can accomplish it.</p>



<p><strong>Independent platform</strong></p>



<p>You may utilize OS with several platforms, including Windows, Android, iOS, and Linux. You may join and reap maximum benefits from separate platforms.</p>



<p><strong>Fast development</strong></p>



<p>Since numerous possible alternatives are accessible, the application may be developed quickly. Developers don&#8217;t have to worry about the time because everything will happen faster.</p>



<h4>Conclusion</h4>



<p>You should understand what the LAMP stack is after reading this article. Whether you opt for the original FOSS(free and open-source software) software or the alternative stack, all resources and expertise are available.</p>



<p><em>If you are looking to</em><a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"><em> hire a LAMP Stack developer</em></a><em>, you can consult our software development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.&nbsp;</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/why-lamp-stack-for-your-web-application/">Why LAMP Stack For Your Web Application?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/why-lamp-stack-for-your-web-application/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: web.hasotech.com @ 2022-10-26 10:37:58 by W3 Total Cache
-->