<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Business Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<atom:link href="/blog/tag/business/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/tag/business/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 07:06:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/cropped-logo-1-rb-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Business Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/tag/business/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>You can Give Black Friday Deals &#8211; Products at 90% offer</title>
		<link>/blog/you-can-give-black-friday-deals-products-at-90-offer/</link>
					<comments>/blog/you-can-give-black-friday-deals-products-at-90-offer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 02:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[offers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Augmented Reality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cross platform mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iphone x]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[magento]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[magento2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=5951</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/you-can-give-black-friday-deals-products-at-90-offer/">You can Give Black Friday Deals &#8211; Products at 90% offer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p>Here we are at Black Friday Deals, While all other hosting companies and E-commerce stores are announcing awesome black Friday deals.  <a href="http://www.hasotech.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">HasoTechnology </a>can&#8217;t sit calm and watch. Yes, we are too on the ground. While rest of the world giving black Friday deals on different products. We thought of giving the products that can build the world. You might be probably giving your Black Friday Deals next year. It&#8217;s your time to change the world, Don&#8217;t just looking for others, Start giving your own.</p>
<p> </p>
<h3><a href="http://www.hasotech.com/blackfridaysales/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Black Friday Deals &#8211; Grab Products at</a> <a href="http://www.hasotech.com/blackfridaysales/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">90% offer</a></h3>
<p> </p>
<h3>How can I give Black Friday Deals !!</h3>
<p>It&#8217;s your time now, Are you looking to do your own startup? Looking to make your own product?? Waiting to make your own sales? Here we are, <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/contact-us/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Get started with us</a>. If you are looking make your startup and looking for some tech company or app development company to get started. Then you are at right place. We are here to develop the application or product you are looking for. Get your product with us and start giving your own from next year.</p>
<p> </p>
<h4><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/secrets-successful-hybrid-mobile-apps/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Secrets of the Successful Hybrid Mobile Apps</a></h4>
<p> </p>
<h3>How to get started with Black Friday Deals</h3>
<p>Are you ready to grab the deals? Get started with us. Select the products from <a href="http://www.hasotech.com/blackfridaysales/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Black Friday Deals</a> which you think very apt to get started with your product. Check the demo and <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/contact-us/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">reach our support team</a> who all are always waiting to provide our valuable services. Share all the necessary details and get your products delivered instantly.</p>
<p> </p>
<h4><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/how-to-get-free-magento-2-mobile-app/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to get Free Magento 2 Mobile App</a></h4>
<p>There will be no hidden charges, no locks, full source code will be provided without any restrictions. And we will provide our support team to help you anytime.</p>
<p> </p>
<h4><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/not-go-hybrid-mobile-app-development/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Don’t go with Hybrid Mobile App Development</a></h4>
<p> </p>
<h3>What if my product is not there</h3>
<p>If you couldn&#8217;t find <a href="http://www.hasotech.com/blackfridaysales/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">any get started products</a> on our Black Friday deals. No worries, Just <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/contact-us/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">r</a><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/contact-us/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">each us with the requirements</a> on what you are looking to develop the product. Or simply <a href="mailto:info@hasotech.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Email your Requirements</a> or <a href="hasotech" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">skype us</a> whatever you are comfortable with. We will reach you in very shorter time, Grab your requirements, Get your application done.</p>
<p>We are super excited to hear from you. Or just simply share your views on comments or mail us: info@hasotech.com</p>
<p> </p>
<h4><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/get-your-augmented-reality-app-for-android-and-ios/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Get your Augmented Reality App for Android and iOS</a></h4>
<p> </p>
<h3><a href="http://www.hasotech.com/blackfridaysales/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Black Friday Deals &#8211; Grab Products at 90% offer</a></h3>
<p> </p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/you-can-give-black-friday-deals-products-at-90-offer/">You can Give Black Friday Deals &#8211; Products at 90% offer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/you-can-give-black-friday-deals-products-at-90-offer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Double Your Profit With Mobile App for Blog</title>
		<link>/blog/double-your-profit-with-mobile-app-for-blog/</link>
					<comments>/blog/double-your-profit-with-mobile-app-for-blog/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 07:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hasotech.com/?p=2141</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/double-your-profit-with-mobile-app-for-blog/">Double Your Profit With Mobile App for Blog</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<h1>Double Your Profit With Mobile App for Blog</h1>
<p>Blogging is one of the best ways to gain knowledge and earn money. If you are looking this, you might be a blogger looking to earn more money. It&#8217;s easy to get started in blogging but very hard to be in blogging. There may be numerous tricks to earn more money with blogging. But in reality, it is very hard and it sets to few. Most difficult part of blogging is doing SEO and maintaining it for long period. Get rid of all these headaches. Get mobile app for blog and increase your profit.</p>
<h2>Mobile App for Blog</h2>
<p>We have made pretty simple to get a mobile app for blog. A ready-made solution for WordPress blogs. You can get mobile app for blog very easily. We have made the app with super cool mobile features like offline, night mode, easy sharing and more. Are you an Apple fan? Don&#8217;t worry, we provide the app for iOS too. You might be thinking how much do we have to pay to get this Mobile app for blog.  It&#8217;s ZERO cost and completely free. And of course, we expect some return back from your side for the free blog.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/whats-crazy-mobile-app-development/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">What’s crazy on Mobile App Development</a></h3>
<h2>How to get FREE Mobile app for Blog</h2>
<ul>
<li>Go to <a href="http://www.hasotech.com/wp2app" target="_blank" rel="noopener">http://www.hasotech.com/wp2app</a></li>
<li>Click on know more</li>
<li>Fill all the details asked for</li>
<li>Submit the application</li>
</ul>
<p>We will review the application and reach you over email.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/very-easy-to-develop-a-mobile-app/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Very easy to Develop a Mobile App</a></h3>
<h2>Benefits of Having Mobile App for Blog</h2>
<ul>
<li>Double your profit from Web and Mobile app</li>
<li>Engage your viewers with Mobile App</li>
<li>Instant Push Notification on each post publish</li>
<li>One time promotions to get Installs</li>
<li>Get rid of doing SEO regularly to maintain the blog</li>
<li>More custom features</li>
</ul>
<p>You can also check the demo app here <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.wp2app.hasotech" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.wp2app.hasotech</a></p>
<p>Feel free to share your reviews over comments.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/get-your-virtual-reality-mobile-application/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Get your Virtual Reality Mobile Application</a></h3>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/double-your-profit-with-mobile-app-for-blog/">Double Your Profit With Mobile App for Blog</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/double-your-profit-with-mobile-app-for-blog/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Five Things That You Never Expect On Mobile App Development</title>
		<link>/blog/five-things-that-you-never-expect-on-mobile-app-development/</link>
					<comments>/blog/five-things-that-you-never-expect-on-mobile-app-development/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 11:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hasotech.com/?p=2049</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/five-things-that-you-never-expect-on-mobile-app-development/">Five Things That You Never Expect On Mobile App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<h1>Five Things That You Never Expect On Mobile App Development</h1>
<p>There is always huge craze on Mobile App Development. Especially when it comes to android mobile app development. The scope of mobile app  with lots of ideas. Many mobile app base startups are working hard to make something. But many mobile applications are missing the needs of users. The development of the mobile application is always focused on the concept. But it is not enough, The main focus should be on end users. The one who is going to use the application. There is no use of providing lots of features. Even a small button should be helpful to end user. Let&#8217;s check on 5 things you never expect on Moblie app development.</p>
<h4 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/whats-crazy-mobile-app-development/">What’s crazy on Mobile App Development</a></h4>
<h2>Mockups &#8211; Gamechanger</h2>
<p>In most of the Mobile app development scenario, mockups don&#8217;t consider as important. And also it&#8217;s not expected by mobile app development team head in some case. To make a successful app, Mockups is very important which is a game changer. Mockups help to develop the application in a focused way. With mockup, one can set app design, flow, and structure. There are many free online mockups tools available. moqups.com,framebox.org,invisionapp.com are some of the online mockups tools.</p>
<h2>App Security &#8211; Don&#8217;t compromise</h2>
<p>When it comes to mobile app some might not be taking app security seriously. But as like web applications, There are many chances to hack mobile app. Developing an application like WhatsApp or Facebook will need rest API. Rest API is helpful to connect with database. But these should be done in a secure way. There should not be any loopholes. Some security flaws may happen over logs too. Make sure all the data are safe with the mobile application.</p>
<h4 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/never-mess-business-mobile-app-development/">Never Mess With Business Mobile App Development</a></h4>
<h2>Optimized Mobile App Development</h2>
<p>It is necessary to check optimization of the app. The amount of CPU usage consumed, RAM used by the app, Memory consumption. These are very important to check while developing the application. There should be no repeated coding and code should be optimized. The less number of lines in an application, the more optimized it will be.</p>
<h2>Adhoc Testing After Development</h2>
<p>All the mobile app development companies will be with a testing team. But those testers will be in a box and they test the functionalities but not real time. Real app bugs are exposed when it goes real time. It is better to make complete testing after mobile app development. This kind of testing will help to make the app stronger. The more bug an app is exposed, The stronger it will.</p>
<h2>Using Version Control</h2>
<p>It is necessary to use version control to make a proper mobile app development. Version control helps the developers to know what changes are done and when it is done and for what purpose it was made. These data will be very helpful while making changes after many days. Also having such version control will help to protect the code with proper backups.</p>
<p>You might not be considering these as important. Sometimes you never expect those but these are very important for mobile app development. Share your views on these over comments.</p>
<h4 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/know-about-mobile-app-development/">Know about Mobile App Development</a></h4>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/five-things-that-you-never-expect-on-mobile-app-development/">Five Things That You Never Expect On Mobile App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/five-things-that-you-never-expect-on-mobile-app-development/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Never Mess With Business Mobile App Development</title>
		<link>/blog/never-mess-business-mobile-app-development/</link>
					<comments>/blog/never-mess-business-mobile-app-development/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 06:54:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hasotech.com/?p=2034</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/never-mess-business-mobile-app-development/">Never Mess With Business Mobile App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<h1>Never Mess With Business Mobile App Development</h1>
<p>Are you running a business? Business Mobile App Development is needed one. Don&#8217;t mind what is your business is about. Having a Mobile App Development team for your business is important. The scope of Mobile application has been increasing every day. The more we engage with our customers, The more business we will get.  And one of the best ways to make customer engagement is having a Business Mobile App Development. Let&#8217;s check in detail on Having a business mobile app development team. Pros and cons of mobile application and much more details.</p>
<h2>Business Mobile App Development</h2>
<p>When it comes to business mobile app development. It&#8217;s not necessary to be more professional. The objective of the mobile application should bring more business. Brand awareness is also another important factor. Make sure your business mobile app development team is focusing on user engagement. The application should bring more customers rather than just offering many features. Having such mobile application will help to connect directly with customers. And customers feedback is always very important for business development.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/very-easy-to-develop-a-mobile-app/">Very easy to Develop a Mobile App</a></h3>
<h2>Can I afford a Mobile App Development team?</h2>
<p>It&#8217;s always very easy to find a mobile app development team. There are many software companies offering such services. When it comes to cost, Business owners hesitate to invest more money for app development. You can find a mobile app development company at a cheaper price and also at a very high price. It&#8217;s all about what you give is what you get. When you invest more money on making a mobile app, The more standard application you will get.</p>
<p>In case if you would like to start with a low budget. Start making the mobile app with minimal features and provide to the customers. Based on customer response and if you feel this would increase the business. Then no doubt, go with complete features.</p>
<p>In short, If you have good confidence and budget. Start making a compelete mobile app with all features. Else go with step by step by developing alpha, beta and improve it.</p>
<h2>Tips for Business Mobile App Development</h2>
<p><strong>Choosing the right development team:</strong> is very first one. A good team always provides good suggestions and helps for better development. Make sure the development team is flexible and have some business domain knowledge.This would help to make a better application.</p>
<p><strong>Understand the customer needs:</strong> There is no use of developing a mobile app without any need. Make proper analysis how the mobile application going to help your customers. And also very important is, how it is going to bring more business.</p>
<p><strong>Don&#8217;t dump with all features:</strong> It&#8217;s not necessary to provide more features. The more we give unique features which solve a customer problem. The more we get customers engagement.</p>
<p><strong>Don&#8217;t invest more</strong>: Before implementing the app, Don&#8217;t make a huge investment on it. Getting started with the small application is more enough. Having a step by step development at the proper time is always recommended.</p>
<p><strong>Push Notification:</strong> Let your customers know that you are working for them. Provide them regular updates over push notification. Let them know your offers and services.</p>
<p><strong>Analyse the customer Problem:</strong> This might be the last point, but this should be the first step. Before getting a mobile app development team analyze the customer need or problem statement. And develop the application which solves the customer problem.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/whats-crazy-mobile-app-development/">What’s crazy on Mobile App Development</a></h3>
<h2>Pros of Business Mobile App Development</h2>
<ul>
<li>Business Mobile Application always increases your business and brings more customers</li>
<li>Get customers engaged and get closer with them</li>
<li>Push notification may drive more business</li>
<li>Having direct communication with customers will always help to get better feedback</li>
<li>Increase your business brand</li>
<li>More reach of mobile app = more business</li>
</ul>
<h2>Cons of Business Mobile App Development</h2>
<ul>
<li>There are many benefits you may get with the business mobile app. But at the same time, if the application is worse it may spoil your brand name</li>
<li>If the idea is not unique, It may create many competitors</li>
<li>The mobile application may irritate the customers</li>
</ul>
<p>There are always pros and cons in everything. The more we avoid cons, The better business we will get. Hope this article has helped you to get an idea of Business Mobile App Development.</p>
<p>Let us know about your business, And we will tell how a mobile app can help to grow your business. Share your views in comments and get to know more.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/know-about-mobile-app-development/">Know about Mobile App Development</a></h3>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/never-mess-business-mobile-app-development/">Never Mess With Business Mobile App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/never-mess-business-mobile-app-development/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: web.hasotech.com @ 2022-10-26 16:58:33 by W3 Total Cache
-->