<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>JavaScript Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<atom:link href="/blog/category/java-script/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/category/java-script/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:15:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/cropped-logo-1-rb-32x32.png</url>
	<title>JavaScript Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/category/java-script/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Progressive Web App Advantages And Disadvantages</title>
		<link>/blog/progressive-web-app-advantages-and-disadvantages/</link>
					<comments>/blog/progressive-web-app-advantages-and-disadvantages/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cross platform mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ionic Framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[JavaScript]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[javascript]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PWA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web app]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6391</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Customers nowadays should be able to provide the best mobile experience for their visitors. Some companies thus opt not to apply native. We shall present another new technology called Progressive Web Apps in this post (PWAs). We discover how Progressive Web App operates, how they overcome the problems and weaknesses of PWA applications. Progressive web [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/progressive-web-app-advantages-and-disadvantages/">Progressive Web App Advantages And Disadvantages</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Customers nowadays should be able to provide the best mobile experience for their visitors. Some companies thus opt not to apply native. We shall present another new technology called Progressive Web Apps in this post (PWAs). We discover how Progressive Web App operates, how they overcome the problems and weaknesses of PWA applications.</p>



<p>Progressive web apps (PWAs) are a fascinating technology that can revolutionize the way we create mobile and online applications. Some people may suggest though that PWA is only a website that&#8217;s turned into a mobile app, while some people argue about its capacity, safety, and performance.</p>



<p>So, This article explains the <strong>pros and cons of Progressive web apps</strong>, useful for your future web and mobile apps.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:33px"><strong>What Is Progressive Web App?</strong></p>



<p>The progressive web app provides a user-like mobile experience. Therefore, the UX is tailored for the PWA device to provide the greatest information and features.</p>



<p>PWA is accessed by web users to enable consumers access to important native features, such as mobile home screen application, offline access, PWA notices of push</p>



<p>PWA allows web apps to load, synchronize and smoothly execute things when no network is present while giving your users a native experience.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:30px"><strong>Advantages Of Progressive Web App</strong></p>



<p><strong>PWAs are cheaper than other apps</strong></p>



<p>Material has to be generated only once, which saves time and money by making content for iOS, Android and a website individually. In addition, PWAs need not be updated (some find this feature specifically cool). No new information needs to be downloaded by users. You don&#8217;t have to worry about their development if a PWA is operating.</p>



<p><strong>Reliable</strong></p>



<p>When loading, the app should be bright and should be shut and open if there is not a network or a relatively low-speed network like 2G. Google discovered if the page was loaded longer than 3 seconds, that 53% of people left the website.</p>



<p><strong>User friendly</strong></p>



<p>You don&#8217;t depend on app stores with PWAs. Search engines and other platforms can find PWAs. You may also provide a PWA on social networks, on your homepage, or through another element of your ecosystem. However, app stores offer the benefit of being able to reach a wide public in one shot.</p>



<p><strong>Installable</strong></p>



<p>If we want to bring web apps closer to native applications, they must be installed and reside with other native applications on the home screen, so that the user can use PWA with only one click.</p>



<p><strong>Splash Screen</strong></p>



<p>Adds a splash screen upon starting the app to the progressive Web App. That makes the PWA more resemble a native application.</p>



<p><strong>Highly engage-able</strong></p>



<p>Users should remain engaged with the app. PWA offers features such as push notifications to help users glorify their commitment, home screen icon, the full screen, and offline-first app.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:25px"><strong>Disadvantage Of Progressive Web App</strong></p>



<p><strong>Drains battery power</strong></p>



<p>Since the phones have to work harder to comprehend the code, as they are written in complicated codes. This is why PWAs use more battery compared to native applications. So, consumers don&#8217;t worry about their battery life anymore and may not have to download such an application.</p>



<p><strong>Unable to access various device features&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>PWAs do not have access to numerous functionalities on your smartphone, therefore they are behind native applications. No access to NFC devices and also Bluetooth devices, sophisticated camera settings and so much more is available to PWAs. This means that the application is less than optimal for users.</p>



<p><strong>No access to app stores</strong></p>



<p>You are not exposed in an Apple or Android application store as a corporation if you build a <a href="https://medium.com/weekly-webtips/create-a-progressive-web-app-a-quick-tutorial-7e3b4e9c040a">PWA</a>. Apps are frequently identified since they appear on one of the renowned app marketplaces. Therefore, it is a significant drawback that this &#8220;springboard&#8221; cannot be used by a wider public.</p>



<p><strong>Functionalities&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Fewer and consequently less UX functionality. These web apps offer less functionality, unlike native apps. On Apple devices, iOS does not support complete PWAs functionality.&nbsp;</p>



<p>This means that many users have restricted choices for PWAs, which is a pity. A lack of experience in UX (user experience) is a genuine loss at least as important in a world as the marketing of the product itself.</p>



<p><strong>Lesser technical option</strong></p>



<p>It is not possible to apply to PWAs all technical alternatives, such as Bluetooth or Near Field Communication (NFC). This implies that the applications you may have for your application are restricted. The question is whether PWAs can also make use of other future advances.</p>



<h4 style="font-size:22px">Conclusion</h4>



<p>Using the Progressive Web App you have read the benefits and cons for development. In the end, it is vital that you have your application supported and solved problems on time by the proper PWA app development firm.</p>



<p><em>If you are looking to</em><a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"><em> hire an application developer for your application,</em></a><em> you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/progressive-web-app-advantages-and-disadvantages/">Progressive Web App Advantages And Disadvantages</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/progressive-web-app-advantages-and-disadvantages/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Is MEAN Stack Development?</title>
		<link>/blog/what-is-mean-stack-development/</link>
					<comments>/blog/what-is-mean-stack-development/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[JavaScript]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LAMP Stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MEAN Stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stack Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AngularJS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Expressjs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lamp stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MEAN stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[monogodb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nodejs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6419</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It is certainly a digital era in the twenty-first century. And you need a standardized and consistent MEAN stack in order to create an application from scratch in this age. However, a wealth of software stacks such as LAMP, Ruby on Rails, and many more are available in the current environment. The piled field was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/what-is-mean-stack-development/">What Is MEAN Stack Development?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>It is certainly a digital era in the twenty-first century. And you need a standardized and consistent MEAN stack in order to create an application from scratch in this age.</p>



<p>However, a wealth of software stacks such as LAMP, Ruby on Rails, and many more are available in the current environment. The piled field was packed with its abundance.</p>



<p>That is why many developers are employing a variety of technologies today for mobile, web, and app development to get better and quicker outcomes. Thus MEAN Stack is used by developers.</p>



<p>You&#8217;ll see What is MEAN Stack in this article? The significance and advantages of the frameworks.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:35px"><strong>What is MEAN Stack?</strong></p>



<p>MEAN is a JavaScript-based technology collection that includes MongoDB, Express.js, AngularJS, and Node.js. A new age of creating robust, fast, and scalable Web applications leveraging its powerful design patterns such as model/view/controller (MVC) is released by the lightweight and highly efficient MEAN stack.&nbsp;</p>



<p>It&#8217;s software open source. It&#8217;s quick-running and structured. The stack utilizes just JavaScript programming language. This means that every level of the program works in one language. It&#8217;s a flexible stack for building both mobile and online applications.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:33px"><strong>Frameworks Of MEAN Stack Development</strong></p>



<p><strong>MongoDB</strong></p>



<p>The application data is stored in this framework. Due to Javascript in the database and the program, when an object moves inside the software, the requirement to translate is skipped.</p>



<p><a href="https://medium.com/chingu/an-overview-of-mongodb-mongoose-b980858a8994">MongoDB </a>is very scalable, performing and storing well. It excels at large data handling overall. Developers may use it easily to create fields and accomplish their job simpler.</p>



<p>MongoDB is famous for its speed and storage scalability. You may also add fields to the database without refreshing the whole table.</p>



<p><strong>ExpressJS</strong></p>



<p>The backend for a MEAN Stack application is this framework. Express.js supports interactions between the web application&#8217;s database and the front end. It forms part of a seamless flow of data to the end-user. The chain is efficient. It avoids overwriting of variables by developers.</p>



<p>Express.js&#8217; approach is minimalism. It is capable of efficiently handling all procedures. The minimalist nature doesn&#8217;t mean featureless. It must be noted.</p>



<p>It avoids overwriting of variables by developers. In this way, a variable that you created before cannot be mistakenly redefined. This contributes to saving a lot of money and time.</p>



<p><strong>AngularJS</strong></p>



<p>AngularJS is an extremely popular JavaScript front-end frame. The Angular JS server is used in the MEAN stack to create the application&#8217;s user-facing side.</p>



<p>JavaScript builds the front end, backend, and database. As a result, all elements of the application have a fluid data flow.</p>



<p>Angular JS, with its easy-to-use templates and finely tuned performance, is a perfect front-end frame. In addition, apps for both mobile and desktop may be developed simultaneously.</p>



<p><strong>Node.JS</strong></p>



<p>Node.JS is MEAN Stack&#8217;s backbone. Express.js is specially built to work with Node.js. Node.JS also links to Angular JS for the fast delivery of data.Node.JS enables the deployment of the MongoDB database in the cloud easier thanks to an integrated webserver.&nbsp;</p>



<p>It is extremely scalable and may be connected to thousands of concurrent links. Compared to a resource-heavy resource, it is compatible with small resource demands.</p>



<h4>How does MEAN Stack Works?</h4>



<p>In MEAN Stack development follows five phases.</p>



<ul><li>In the <strong>first phase, </strong>AngularJS is used as a customer language while working with Javascript. This implies that AngularJS handles it when a customer requests.</li><li>In the <strong>second phase</strong>, The application is making its way to Node.JS, the language side of the server.</li><li>In the <strong>third phase</strong>, Express JS enters an application for a database inquiry.</li><li>In the <strong>fourth phase</strong>, MongoDB accesses the information and returns the appropriate answer to ExpressJS.</li><li>And in the <strong>last phase, </strong>This reply then goes back to NodeJS and subsequently back to AngularJS.</li></ul>



<h5>Advantages of MEAN Stack Development</h5>



<p><strong>Ease of Isomorphic Coding</strong></p>



<p>A significant advantage of adopting MEAN Stack Development Technology in web development is the ease with which code that is developed in one framework is transferred to another. This not only increases productivity significantly, but it also improves the performance as the transmission of data across the application layers is done in the form of the JavaScript Object Notation (JSON).</p>



<p><strong>High flexibility</strong></p>



<p>The developer may simply test the application on a cloud platform when the app development is complete. MEAN stack is extremely versatile since the application without any problems may be developed, tested, and introduced. In addition, adding a field to the form, allows you to enter more information. MongoDB supports the entire cluster and automated replication.</p>



<p><strong>Cost-effectiveness</strong></p>



<p>Total developers are not so required for MEAN Stack, while others demand developers with a wealth of knowledge of JavaScript, MySQL, and PHP technologies. MEAN stack is an economic web development technique that simply relies on developers&#8217; Javascript skills.</p>



<p><strong>High Speed &amp; Reusability</strong></p>



<p>Thanks to the non-blocking design of Node.js, the creation of the MEAN stack is rapid and reusable. In addition, AngularJS offers testability, reusability, and maintenance, which is an open-source JavaScript framework. Once the libraries have been built they may be utilized easily for the front end and the backend, which will increase productivity considerably.</p>



<p><strong>Cloud compatible</strong></p>



<p>For the development process, the MEAN stack leverages libraries and public repositories. When using this technology, the overall development cost is also lower. Furthermore, MongoDB leverages the cloud features of the app to save disc space costs.</p>



<p><strong>Ease of Debugging</strong></p>



<p>Since MEAN Stack uses only one language to operate in layers, the execution thread can be traced more easily. Developers can monitor the manipulation of the data and debug the flow with a consistent set of open-source tools.</p>



<p><strong>Single Language Usage</strong></p>



<p>The whole development code is provided in JavaScript, which includes the client and the server-side while working with the MEAN Stack technologies. This makes it easier for both front-end developers and backend developers to learn from MEAN Stack development. Developers don&#8217;t have to worry about the interoperability of code between multiple levels.</p>



<h6>Conclusion</h6>



<p>The technology of MEAN stacking keeps improving every day. MEAN stack technologies are used widely by most of the major online and mobile app developing businesses in the delivery of cutting-edge web and mobile apps.</p>



<p><em>If you are looking to</em><a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"><em> hire a MEAN Stack developer for your application</em></a><em>, you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.&nbsp;</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/what-is-mean-stack-development/">What Is MEAN Stack Development?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/what-is-mean-stack-development/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why LAMP Stack For Your Web Application?</title>
		<link>/blog/why-lamp-stack-for-your-web-application/</link>
					<comments>/blog/why-lamp-stack-for-your-web-application/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 07:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[JavaScript]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LAMP Stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MEAN Stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PHP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stack Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Apache]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lamp stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linux]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MEAN stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MySql]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web app]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6426</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Solution Stacks are a mix of computer software and application applications. The aim is to offer the proper foundation for web applications. Multiple developers are technical in developing, maintaining, and managing the different components. However, many developers can execute the whole solution LAMP stack component. It is known as Full-Stack developers. The packs are usually [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/why-lamp-stack-for-your-web-application/">Why LAMP Stack For Your Web Application?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Solution Stacks are a mix of computer software and application applications. The aim is to offer the proper foundation for web applications. Multiple developers are technical in developing, maintaining, and managing the different components. However, many developers can execute the whole solution LAMP stack component.</p>



<p>It is known as Full-Stack developers. The packs are usually called according to the components utilized, resulting in an acronym. This method of naming helps you recall the parts utilized and explain the entire stack components. In this article, we’ll discuss “LAMP Stack” You may get knowledge, advantages, and functionality of a LAMP stack.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:35px"><strong>What is LAMP Stack?</strong></p>



<p>A <strong>LAMP stack </strong>is an open-source bundle of software for websites and Web applications that may be used. LAMP is an abbreviation that usually includes the operating system of <strong>Linux</strong>, <strong>Apache</strong> HTTP Server, <strong>MySQL</strong> relational database management system, and the language of <strong>PHP</strong> programming.</p>



<p>LAMP comprises four elements named LAMP STACK combined.</p>



<ul><li>Operating System</li><li>Webserver</li><li>Database&nbsp;</li><li>Scripting&nbsp;</li></ul>



<p><strong>Operating System</strong></p>



<p>Our initial piece is the operating system (OS). For the stack model, Linux lays the basis. On this layer, all other layers are running. Linux is the lowest layer and the operating system supplies it.</p>



<p>Each component is running Linux. However, you do not restrict yourself particularly to Linux; it is easy for you to execute any component on Microsoft Windows and Mac OS X or Unix if necessary.</p>



<p>The foundation of the stack pattern is set by Linux and is used to host web apps. The operating system is the lowest layer of the stack, with all other layers on top of the layer. Make it the LAMP stack&#8217;s backbone.</p>



<p><strong>Webserver</strong></p>



<p>The second part of the stack is the Apache webserver. A web server is server software that satisfies the requirements of customers around the world. The matching client to server is then done through HTTP (HyperText Transfer Protocol).</p>



<p>This layer is located above the Linux layer. Web servers shall translate their proper webpage from web browsers. Mechanics for a user to access a webpage are provided by Apache.</p>



<p>It operates more than 65 percent of all internet-based sites and is a reliable, mission-critical, and competent server. PHP is within Apache and you construct your dynamic pages together by using Apache and PHP.</p>



<p><strong>Database&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Databases dwell in the 3rd element. Details that may be requested to build a website using MySQL are saved. MySQL normally resides next to the Apache/layer on top of the Linux layer. MySQL can be downloaded to a second host server in high-end setups. MySQL supplies the LAMP system&#8217;s data storage side.</p>



<p>You have access to a very competent database for big and complicated locations using MySQL. In the format, you can simply query with the SQL language all your information, products, accounts, and other information kinds will be available in this database within your Web application.</p>



<p>Collectively, this layer may comprise user accounts, user information, descriptive product names, or even website analytics. Web managers may have to edit their website material frequently and users may need to change its content. Inclusion of the database layer may do so.</p>



<p><strong>Scripting</strong></p>



<p>PHP is the original stack&#8217;s fourth piece since it interacts extremely well with MySQL. It is often used for web development since it is a language with dynamical characteristics which makes working with it fast and easy.</p>



<p>If you are a newbie, this feature is very attractive. PHP is so useful because it can be integrated with HTML so that you may jump in and out as you desire.</p>



<p>PHP is a simple, effective language for programming, which sticks the other elements of the LAMP system together. In the MySQL database and some of the functions provided by Linux, you write dynamic contents with PHP to access data.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:33px"><strong>LAMP Stack Alternatives</strong></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><strong>Open-source alternatives are:</strong></p>



<ul><li><strong><a href="https://www.hostnamaste.com/blog/how-to-install-the-lemp-stack/">LEMP</a> </strong>(Linux, NGINX, MySQL/MariaDB, PHP/Perl/Python)</li><li><strong>LAPP </strong>(Linux, Apache, PostgreSQL, PHP)</li><li><strong>LEAP </strong>(Linux, Eucalyptus, AppScale, Python)</li><li><strong>LLMP </strong>(Linux, Lighttpd, MySQL/MariaDB, PHP/Perl/Python)</li></ul>



<p>While non-open source alternatives include:</p>



<ul><li><strong>WAMP </strong>(Windows, Apache, MySQL/MariaDB, PHP/Perl/Python)</li><li><strong>WIMP</strong>(Windows, Internet Information Services, MySQL/MariaDB, PHP/Perl/Python)</li><li><strong>MAMP</strong> (Mac OS x, Apache, MySQL/MariaDB, PHP/Perl/Python)</li></ul>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:30px"><strong>Advantages Of LAMP</strong></p>



<p><strong>Scalability</strong></p>



<p>Every LAMP stack development program or website you design might expand in size or decrease based on your needs. You hold the secret to making your blog easier to use.</p>



<p><strong>Highly secure</strong></p>



<p>We can guarantee that this technology is highly safe thanks to the number of updates, encryptions, security architectures, and much more in Lamp Stack.</p>



<p><strong>Customization</strong></p>



<p>The person will be able to personalize the app by the user. Customizing using LAMP will never be a problem. In a few steps, you can accomplish it.</p>



<p><strong>Independent platform</strong></p>



<p>You may utilize OS with several platforms, including Windows, Android, iOS, and Linux. You may join and reap maximum benefits from separate platforms.</p>



<p><strong>Fast development</strong></p>



<p>Since numerous possible alternatives are accessible, the application may be developed quickly. Developers don&#8217;t have to worry about the time because everything will happen faster.</p>



<h4>Conclusion</h4>



<p>You should understand what the LAMP stack is after reading this article. Whether you opt for the original FOSS(free and open-source software) software or the alternative stack, all resources and expertise are available.</p>



<p><em>If you are looking to</em><a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"><em> hire a LAMP Stack developer</em></a><em>, you can consult our software development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.&nbsp;</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/why-lamp-stack-for-your-web-application/">Why LAMP Stack For Your Web Application?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/why-lamp-stack-for-your-web-application/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why NodeJS For App Development?</title>
		<link>/blog/why-nodejs-for-app-development/</link>
					<comments>/blog/why-nodejs-for-app-development/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 07:52:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cross platform mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[JavaScript]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MEAN Stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stack Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[App development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[javascript]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nodejs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web app]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6430</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Many modifications to JavaScript&#8217;s increased popularity and today&#8217;s web development landscape have been drastically different. NodeJS has not only been a JavaScript altercation but is built mostly on it. NodeJS was then created and with quickness turned the minds of the developers. JavaScript was not just faster than anybody imagined on the server, but often [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/why-nodejs-for-app-development/">Why NodeJS For App Development?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Many modifications to JavaScript&#8217;s increased popularity and today&#8217;s web development landscape have been drastically different. NodeJS has not only been a JavaScript altercation but is built mostly on it.</p>



<p>NodeJS was then created and with quickness turned the minds of the developers. JavaScript was not just faster than anybody imagined on the server, but often It was quicker than Java and other choices.</p>



<p>Since then, its constant diet of tiny, rapid, infinite data requests has increased the dynamism of NodeJS websites. It currently plays a key role in the technological pool of many leading firms that rely on its advantages.</p>



<p>In this article, We&#8217;ll cover &#8220;why to select NodeJS to create an application?&#8221; We will see What is NodeJS before we enter the topic?</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:35px"><strong>What Is NodeJS?</strong></p>



<p>NodeJS is open and free, utilized by thousands of developers worldwide. It adds several advantages to the table, making it superior to other platforms on the server, such as Java or PHP.</p>



<p>It is a strong JavaScript-based framework for developing online chat apps, video streaming sites, single-page apps, and several other I/O-intensive web applications and web applications. It&#8217;ll be utilized by major, established firms and freshly formed boot stocks, based on Google Chrome&#8217;s JavaScript V8 engine.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:33px"><strong>What Makes NodeJS a Powerful Technology?</strong></p>



<p>NodeJS components include V8, libuv, C-ares, HTTP-parser, OpenSSL, and Zlib. While it is appreciated the attention of developers from its inception and has been utilized in real-time applications excellently. NodeJS is without a doubt a unique collection of capabilities that have helped developers make it their favorite choice for the creation of online apps.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:30px"><strong>Why Choose NodeJS?</strong></p>



<ul><li>NodeJS works together to smoothly develop the front-end parts of an application with business-level web technology like ReactJS and AngularJS.</li><li>NodeJS works with a wide variety of popular framework systems, such as Express.js, Connect, and Socket.io.</li><li>NodeJS features a robust ecosystem of thousands of open-source libraries hosted on the NPM site.</li><li>Great community and support for developers.</li><li>NodeJS, based on Google V8 JavaScript, can be handled incredibly quickly and easily.</li><li>All tools operate on NodeJS based on JavaScript.</li></ul>



<h5>Benefits Of NodeJS</h5>



<p><strong>High Performance and Event-Based Model</strong></p>



<p>With their quick growth, the companies are searching for frameworks that can be readily adapted and scaled as the user base expands and that NodeJS can accommodate any audience.</p>



<p>It is a favorite choice for different solutions that demand rapid changes in data such as chats, video conferencing, and more, whether it concerns non-blocking replies, single-theme nature, or the use of a common language for both Client and Server.</p>



<p><strong>Runtime environment</strong>.&nbsp;</p>



<p>NodeJS allows the programming of the server using JavaScript. This involves little overhead for most boot stapping tasks that you need to perform to create a server application. However, the framework you want to utilize still has to be determined.</p>



<p>You may discover several blog entries on whether performance, speed, usability, and so on are superior based. However, the option ultimately depends on the individual preferences of the developer.</p>



<p><strong>Easy Maintenance</strong></p>



<p>Since software developing businesses nowadays have a specialized team of experts to support server administration and maintenance, why are NodeJS&#8217;s server-free and hardware-free options for you complicated?. This reduces time and costs and improves developers and software development firms&#8217; efficiency and productivity in this context.</p>



<p><strong>Single Programming Language</strong></p>



<p>NodeJS delivers a front-end and back-end Javascript cocktail of comparable languages. It is easier to access, more versatile than it seems. It robustly and seamlessly makes the whole web app development cycle for developers and companies.</p>



<p>It spares more useful and lucrative time, energy, and human-hour commitment. This conveniently creates web apps and makes them the most favored technology now on the market.</p>



<p><strong>Developing Cross-Platform Apps With NodeJS</strong></p>



<p>Platforms like Electron and NW.js have offered a new method to use NodeJS-style <a href="https://instabug.com/blog/cross-platform-development/">cross-platform apps.</a> You may now use a few code lines from your online applications to construct desktop programs using NodeJS, especially for macOS, Windows, and Linux.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:25px"><strong><a href="https://hasotech.com/cross-platform-mobile-app-development-things-to-know/">Cross-Platform Mobile App Development – Things To Know</a></strong></p>



<p><strong>Scalable systems</strong></p>



<p>The lightweight nature of NodeJS facilitates the horizontal measurement of apps by launching several project instances on various hosts. You may also grow the system upwards utilizing a module that incorporates a cluster, which forks all the CPUs you have for the application process.</p>



<h6>NodeJS based business solutions</h6>



<p><strong>Real-time Web Applications</strong></p>



<p>NodeJS may also be used to construct web apps in real-time, such as a chat room in which users can speak with one another in real-time since it is particularly good at managing a lot of I/O activities.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Or perhaps a tool of cooperation where employees work simultaneously on the same paper. Done! Constructing a web application for video conferencing won&#8217;t be an issue either. The Node Events API and WebSockets make it feasible.</p>



<p><strong>Chat Application</strong></p>



<p>Chat is the most common multi-user application in real-time. The capacity of IRC to implement anything now in NodeJS, using several proprietary open Protocols operating on non-standard port 80 over WebSockets with a standard port 80 function.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The chat application is NodeJS&#8217;s sweet example: a lightweight and high-data application running across dispersed devices.</p>



<p><strong>Server-side Web Applications</strong></p>



<p>It may also be used with Express.js for generating traditional server web applications. This request-response paradigm, however, in which NodeJS carries rendered HTML is not the most frequent use-case. This method must be supported and opposed by arguments.&nbsp;</p>



<p><strong>Backend for Social Media Networking</strong></p>



<p>On NodeJS several well-known names are reconstructed like LinkedIn and Medium. A key mix of nodes is provided to construct a backend for a social media website. It offers its V8 engine and secure authentication for flashing fast routing. The scalability of a network of social media is one of the most important elements.</p>



<p><strong>Data Streaming</strong></p>



<p>This was embraced by giants to service 190 countries, with more than 100 million hours streaming and counting over 120 million users. NodeJS has a distinct edge as super-fast processing of files and encodes and uploads of plumbing. Many e-Shops and applications with enormous data streaming videos have been involved in this.</p>



<h6>Conclusion</h6>



<p>So I see significant grounds for NodeJS&#8217;s choice of web apps for a seamless and good user experience with the above-mentioned futuristic characteristics.</p>



<p><em>If you are looking to</em><a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"><em> hire a Node developer for your application</em></a><em>, you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/why-nodejs-for-app-development/">Why NodeJS For App Development?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/why-nodejs-for-app-development/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is React Native Important In 2021?</title>
		<link>/blog/is-react-native-important-in-2021/</link>
					<comments>/blog/is-react-native-important-in-2021/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 07:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cross platform mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ionic Framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[JavaScript]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[App development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Native app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[react native]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6463</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/is-react-native-important-in-2021/">Is React Native Important In 2021?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p>There has been a really good option for indigenous development for quite some time now and this is React Native development. By utilizing the same code on all platforms, the major benefit is decreased time and cost.</p>
<p>Due to the worldwide pandemic and loss of direct relations between friends, participation in cultural events, and the operation of a business in the model we knew before, online shopping, gaming, social media trends have certainly grown over the last year.</p>
<p>We have found new smartphone apps that have enabled us to continue with most of our activities in many situations. You have to keep an eye on the facts if you want to create a mobile application.</p>
<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size: 35px"><strong>What is React Native?</strong></p>
<p>React Native is a complete framework for building mobile apps and reacting to native <a href="https://medium.com/flutter-community/create-a-cross-platform-app-using-flutter-in-2021-59e582cb625f">cross Platforms</a>. React Native is the finest technology to create an application for both iOS and Android.</p>
<p>The codebase may be reduced by roughly 95%, saving you time and money. It has several open-source libraries with pre-construction components and therefore accelerates the development process.</p>
<p>React Native apps have been designed with strong and state-of-the-art technology to enable companies around the world to reach new clients on mobile platforms.</p>
<p><strong>Native application</strong></p>
<p>Native applications are installed in an app store. They are particularly built for one platform and can use all smartphone capabilities, like the camera, GPS, speed meter, compass, contact list, etc.</p>
<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size: 30px"><strong>React Native is better than Native?</strong></p>
<p>React native is better and unique because it has</p>
<ul>
<li>Lower the <strong>development time</strong></li>
<li>Easy for <strong>Web developers </strong></li>
<li>Cost-effective </li>
</ul>
<p>Native </p>
<ul>
<li>High <strong>development time</strong></li>
<li>High cost</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Development Time</strong></p>
<p>In a native application, you need two distinct teams to make your application available on both platforms, i.e. the Android development team and the iOS development team. This includes additional effort and time to create a mobile app.</p>
<p>In React Native&#8217;s instance, the same developer writes a single code for both platforms, which implies that React native applications may be created for Android and iOS using the same codes.</p>
<p><strong>Mobile App Cost</strong></p>
<p>The response to the cost of developing the mobile app also helps to find the suitable technology for the creation of your mobile app. The app creation using React Native is the top mobile app development firm, but the cost of Native App Development for the same app project may be reduced by 30%-35% in comparison.</p>
<p><strong>Scalability</strong></p>
<p>It offers mobile app developers more chances in comparison with Native technology to handle a greater quantity of work in an app and to publish higher-functionality updates. The winner in terms of scalability of the Native app vs the Reacts Native app is thus React Native.</p>
<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size: 28px"><strong>React Native for Android Developers</strong></p>
<p>React Native is a smooth development in which the features of Native Code easily use, Hot Reloading, and the management of Hassle-free states lead to smooth, efficient, and efficient development.</p>
<p>A platform-sized experience, which boasts native Android and iOS components while the program runs, is the main advantage React Native offers.</p>
<p>This makes it possible for natives to manage the interaction even with a coding foundation written in JavaScript, so that memory, footprint, flexibility, and experience stay preserved.</p>
<p>It is compatible with native code. React Native is a structure that allows you to create the most powerful applications in combination with JavaScript. It offers impeccable performance with native components, guaranteeing that most applications operate seamlessly and native apps operate more often than before.</p>
<p>Reduce time to develop. Apart from open source projects, app developers might experience a 40 percent quicker development time because many elements can be used locally. Reaction Native also supports both Android and iOS, making it easy for both platforms to exchange data and a single code base. The task may therefore be accomplished in less time.</p>
<p>React Native comes with a Live Reload functionality which allows you to view the newest updates as soon as they are made. This makes it easy for the developer. We are passionate about online and mobile app development, we only advise our clients what is correct.</p>
<p>Find the ideal technological combination. You may use React Native to list your application in the Appstore and Playstore and make use of the sensors and device functionality and also wish to perform effectively. The first thing you want to do is to upgrade the mobile app and explore React Native.</p>
<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size: 25px"><strong>Conclusion</strong></p>
<p>In summary, therefore, you know to which end you are turning if you wish to build an ever-change multi-dimensional mobile app. From startups to successful business leaders, people embrace mobile applications instead of just websites. Most of you still know that mobile apps function totally differently from the standard website.</p>
<p><em>If you are looking to</em><a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"><em> hire an application developer, </em></a><em> you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.</em></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/is-react-native-important-in-2021/">Is React Native Important In 2021?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/is-react-native-important-in-2021/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: web.hasotech.com @ 2022-10-26 10:37:50 by W3 Total Cache
-->