<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Magento 2 Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<atom:link href="/blog/category/magento-2/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/category/magento-2/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 07:15:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/cropped-logo-1-rb-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Magento 2 Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/category/magento-2/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>How to get Free Magento 2 Mobile App</title>
		<link>/blog/how-to-get-free-magento-2-mobile-app/</link>
					<comments>/blog/how-to-get-free-magento-2-mobile-app/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 09:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Magento]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Magento 2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[magento]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[magento2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hasotech.com/?p=2158</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/how-to-get-free-magento-2-mobile-app/">How to get Free Magento 2 Mobile App</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<h1>How to get Free Magento 2 Mobile App</h1>
<p>Magento is one of the most popular E-commerce Platform. Small-scale industries and startups are using Magento 2 as the primary solution. Especially the Magento version 2.0 has come up with a lot of issues fixed and many features. Magento 2 has made with mobile optimization and good loading speed. In this mobile world, it is mandatory to have a mobile application for E-commerce. Magento 2 Mobile app will increase the sales and gets users engagement. Lots of improvement can be made. Increase your profit with Magento 2 Mobile app.</p>
<h2>Magento 2 Mobile App</h2>
<p>With Magento 2 Mobile app, It&#8217;s pretty easy to keep users engaged. With regular Push notifications, and other activities keep your users engaged. But as features increase the cost of developing Magento 2 mobile app also increase. Some small businesses might not able to afford such mobile apps. There is no use of launching a mobile app with minimal features. But with a ready-made solution, One can able to get it at an affordable price. To make it even easier, We thought of giving the solution for free. Here is how to get Free Magento 2 Mobile App.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/get-your-virtual-reality-mobile-application/">Get your Virtual Reality Mobile Application</a></h3>
<h2>How to get Free Magento 2 Mobile App</h2>
<p>We have made very simple to provide Free Mobile app for your Magento 2 E-commerce site.</p>
<p>Just follow the below mentioned steps</p>
<ul>
<li>Add following links in your E-Commerce site footer
<ul>
<li><a href="http://www.hasotech.com/">http://www.hasotech.com/</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.hasotech.com/magento2mobileapp/">http://www.hasotech.com/magento2mobileapp/</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>After adding the links Email us your Magento 2 E-commerce website link <strong><a href="mailto:info@hasotech.com">info@hasotech.com</a> </strong></li>
<li>Our team will review the site and get the required details</li>
<li>Get your free Ecommerce Mobile app for Android</li>
<li>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.web.hasotech.com/ecommerce-app-development/">Ten Unbelievable Facts About E-commerce App Development</a></h3>
</li>
</ul>
<p>The free version of Magento 2 mobile app will be with the features as in <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/blog/works/amaz4u-2/">https://www.hasotech.com/blog/works/amaz4u-2/</a></p>
<p>Also, the free version includes only android. If you are looking for iOS, We appreciate to reach us over email <a href="mailto:info@hasotech.com">info@hasotech.com  </a></p>
<p>Feel free to comment your reviews and feedbacks about the free version of Magneto 2 mobile app. Also If you are looking for customized E-commerce Mobile application comment your requirements. Or Email us <a href="mailto:info@hasotech.com">info@hasotech.com</a>.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/very-easy-to-develop-a-mobile-app/">Very easy to Develop a Mobile App</a></h3>
<p>For any kind of customized solution on E-Commerce on both web and Mobile app. Feel free to reach us for better solutions in a different way.</p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/how-to-get-free-magento-2-mobile-app/">How to get Free Magento 2 Mobile App</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/how-to-get-free-magento-2-mobile-app/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Easiest way to install Magento 2 in NGINX VPS</title>
		<link>/blog/easiest-way-install-magento-2-nginx-vps/</link>
					<comments>/blog/easiest-way-install-magento-2-nginx-vps/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 06:07:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Digital Ocean]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Magento]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Magento 2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PUTTY]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hasotech.com/blog/?p=123</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Magento is fast growing E-commerce Platform with good security and standard. But when it comes to usage, It&#8217;s a little bit complicated one from installing to managing and also Magento expects luxury server configuration. If you have any idea on installing Magneto in shared hosting, Just kick it off and start using dedicated or VPS server. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/easiest-way-install-magento-2-nginx-vps/">Easiest way to install Magento 2 in NGINX VPS</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Magento is fast growing E-commerce Platform with good security and standard. But when it comes to usage, It&#8217;s a little bit complicated one from installing to managing and also Magento expects luxury server configuration. If you have any idea on installing Magneto in shared hosting, Just kick it off and start using dedicated or VPS server. And of course, they are bit costlier at the same time there are some affordable service providers like Digital Ocean, Bluehost. <a href="https://m.do.co/c/fcd6e5a5e705">Digital ocean</a> is providing Free $10 credit for the new users, You may get the offer with this <a href="https://m.do.co/c/fcd6e5a5e705">link</a>. So here we see the easiest way to install Magento 2 in NGINX server.</p>
<h2>Magento 2 &#8211; Setting up Server</h2>
<p>Let&#8217;s check on installing Magento 2  with Digital Ocean server. Get an account with Digital Ocean and create a New Droplet there.</p>
<ol>
<li>Select Distributions</li>
<li>Ubuntu 16.04</li>
<li> $10 / mo ( For Magento we need minimum $10 plan and you may choose $10 or above if required ),</li>
<li>There is nothing to do with Add block storage</li>
<li> Choose Data center region which one is suitable for the Magneto 2 Installation requirement</li>
<li>Don&#8217;t forget to add SSH key which is very important to play with VPS server. You can generate SSH key with <a href="http://www.putty.org/">PUTTYGEN</a>.</li>
<li>Download and Install PUTTY and open PUTTY GEN and click on Generate then move the mouse over the blank area.</li>
<li>Enter Key passphrase which is like Password and save both the public and private key</li>
<li>Upload the private key in Digital Ocean SSH area</li>
</ol>
<h2>Let&#8217;s play with Magento 2 using PUTTY</h2>
<p>Now we have created a Virtual Private server to Install Magento 2 with NGINX. To play with the server, We need the PUTTY tool to connect. Get Putty from www.putty.org and install it in your system.</p>
<ol>
<li>Open Putty and enter the IP Address which you can find in your droplet</li>
</ol>
<p>2. Add the SSH file by selecting SSH -&gt; Auth -&gt; Browse .ppk file which is used in digital ocean and click on open</p>
<p>3. If the private key is authenticated properly, It will connect to the server and ask for login user. Login as &#8220;root&#8221; and enter the passphrase if you have entered while generating the &#8220;.ppk&#8221; file.</p>
<p>4. Now we have connected successfully to the server using PUTTY. Let&#8217;s start the game.</p>
<h2>Install Magento 2 in NGINX VPS</h2>
<p>Now we are going to install Magento 2 in NGINX with below commands. The interesting part is, We don&#8217;t have to install NGINX, MYSQL, MAGENTO 2 one by one. It&#8217;s all can be installed by executing the below commands. To paste the command in PUTTY, just copy by using Ctrl + C command and right click on putty.</p>
<ol>
<li>Update Ubuntu
<pre> sudo apt-get update</pre>
</li>
<li>Install Git
<pre> sudo apt-get install git</pre>
</li>
<li>Clone the configuration
<pre>git clone https://github.com/DavidBelicza/magento2-server-configuration.git</pre>
</li>
<li>Get into configuration Directory  ( cd m and hit TAB )
<pre>cd magento2-server-configuration</pre>
</li>
<li>Edit Configuration
<pre> nano install.ini</pre>
</li>
<li> Domain, base URL to be replaced with the IP address which can be found in Digital Ocean droplet</li>
<li>Get the Magento connect public and private key <a href="https://marketplace.magento.com/customer/accessKeys/list/">here</a></li>
<li>Replace admin email with your email ID. And don&#8217;t forget to save all the details in local file for further use</li>
<li>Press Ctrl + x  then Y and hit enter to save the changes</li>
<li>To start the installation process
<pre> sudo bash install.sh</pre>
</li>
<li>It will take little bit time to install and once the installation is done you can start using Magento by calling the IP Address in your browser</li>
<li>To get admin URL, Navigate to
<ul>
<li><code>cd /var/www/html/youripaddress/webroot</code></li>
<li><code>php bin/magento info:adminuri</code></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>It will display the admin URL like below. Add the path with your IP like ipaddress/admin_1wgrah
<pre><code>Admin Panel URI: /admin_1wgrah </code></pre>
</li>
<li>Enter the admin login name and admin login pass which you can find in configuration file</li>
</ol>
<p>In some cases, we may get the error like site broken or doesn&#8217;t load properly and if you are the one facing the issue, Execute the below commands.</p>
<ul>
<li>Navigate into Magneto root directory
<ul>
<li><code>cd /var/www/html/youripaddress/webroot</code></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Execute the below commands one by one
<ul>
<li><code>chown -R :www-data .</code></li>
<li><code>find . -type d -exec chmod 770 {} \;</code></li>
<li><code>find . -type f -exec chmod 660 {} \;</code></li>
<li><code>chmod u+x bin/magento</code></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p>That&#8217;s all, Now we have successfully installed Magento 2 with NGINX, MYSQL in Ubuntu. If you are facing any issues or having doubts, Feel free to comment it below and we are very happy to give our best on it.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/easiest-way-install-magento-2-nginx-vps/">Easiest way to install Magento 2 in NGINX VPS</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/easiest-way-install-magento-2-nginx-vps/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Free Buy now Button in Magento 2</title>
		<link>/blog/buy-now-button-magento2/</link>
					<comments>/blog/buy-now-button-magento2/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 05:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Magento]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Magento 2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Magento extension]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hasotech.com/blog/?p=13</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/buy-now-button-magento2/">Free Buy now Button in Magento 2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-14 size-full" src="https://www.hasotech.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/10/Magento-logo.png" alt="" width="570" height="200" /></p>
<h4>About Magento</h4>
<p>Magento is one of the fast growing e-commerce sites which is having vast features and high-end security.</p>
<h4>Why Magento?</h4>
<p>Yes, your thought is right why you have pick Magento framework, while there are many eCommerce developing platforms in the market because Magento platform is scalable, upgradable, extendable, flexible and modular which is exactly why this platform is favored. It also provides the analytical reports about the users and Magento provides Support tools to makes sure that any issues you encounter to get solved quickly moreover it also provide the higher end security.It also provides the API which is very much helpful in developing the mobile application for your eCommerce site.</p>
<h2>Buy now in Magento2</h2>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Of course Magento provides all the functionalities easy but even though there are little complication in some modules, For example, Magento does not provide Buy now option, to overcome that it Magento provides Add to cart, Which means even the customer wants to buy a single product they have to add their product to the cart then they have to do the Checkout function. It&#8217;s complicated, right? ..there are many plugins and extensions available in the Magento Marketplace but still now for Magento2, it&#8217;s a bit complicate to find the desired extension to get Buy now button.</p>
<p>While I came through several sites and extensions I finally had a chance to find the Buy now plugins which are suitable for Magento2. All you have to do is just follow the below link,</p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/prince108/Magento2-Buynow" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://github.com/prince108/Magento2-Buynow</a></p>
<p>Follow the below steps using FileZilla or PuTTY</p>
<ol>
<li>Download and extract the Zip file.</li>
<li>Open your root directory.</li>
<li>Insert the file into &#8211; magento/app/code</li>
<li>Run the command &#8211; php bin/magento setup:upgrade</li>
<li>Deploy by using the command &#8211; php bin/magento setup:static-content:deploy</li>
</ol>
<p>That&#8217;s all you were done !! Now you get Buy now button in your Magento site.(It will add Buy now button int your site, if there is any issue get occurred in this Buy now button, Open your Admin panel &#8211; &gt; Store &#8211; &gt; Advanced -&gt; Advanced, you just have to disable and press Save Config and then enable and press Save Config, then refresh your Cache).</p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/buy-now-button-magento2/">Free Buy now Button in Magento 2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/buy-now-button-magento2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>10</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: web.hasotech.com @ 2022-10-26 10:38:47 by W3 Total Cache
-->