<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Cross platform mobile app Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<atom:link href="/blog/tag/cross-platform-mobile-app/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/tag/cross-platform-mobile-app/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:34:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/cropped-logo-1-rb-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Cross platform mobile app Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/tag/cross-platform-mobile-app/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Pros And Cons Of Hybrid Mobile App Development</title>
		<link>/blog/pros-and-cons-of-hybrid-mobile-app-development/</link>
					<comments>/blog/pros-and-cons-of-hybrid-mobile-app-development/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cross platform mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ionic Framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web app]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6377</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New heights have reached the evolution of customized app creation. Not just smartphones and tablets, but also other user devices and smart gadgets, are available for development. Time has become a requirement for cross-platform, hybrid, and native application development, which enables companies to produce more efficient goods. While native applications offer numerous benefits, the popularity [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/pros-and-cons-of-hybrid-mobile-app-development/">Pros And Cons Of Hybrid Mobile App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>New heights have reached the evolution of customized app creation. Not just smartphones and tablets, but also other user devices and smart gadgets, are available for development. Time has become a requirement for cross-platform, hybrid, and native application development, which enables companies to produce more efficient goods. </p>



<p>While native applications offer numerous benefits, the popularity of hybrid mobile applications has grown. It&#8217;s due to its flexibility on many platforms. This idea leads to the development of a single application for many platforms. In addition, these apps make reserving a position in the app store market somewhat faster.</p>



<p>Those platform frameworks are extremely popular however, the advantage and disadvantages of hybrid mobile apps will be discussed in this article. Let&#8217;s get right in with that statement!</p>



<h2 style="font-size:35px">What Is a Hybrid Application?</h2>



<p>A <strong>hybrid application </strong>allows the same software to be installed and even execute on different browsers in different operating systems like Android, iOS, Windows, and so on.</p>



<p>The use of a third-party <a href="https://medium.com/flutterdevs/hybrid-apps-the-future-of-mobile-technology-259bac9a985f">hybrid platform</a> is the development of a hybrid app or hybrid strategy. Third-party examples include React Native, PhoneGap, Ionic, Cordoba, or Xamarin. You may also use web technologies to create the app (HTML, CSS, and Javascript).</p>



<p>The development of this mobile app is primarily a way to build a mobile application utilizing a single code base for several platforms, such as Android and iOS. In this way, development expenses are dramatically reduced. On the other side though, there are certain advantages and disadvantages to this app creation.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:30px"><strong>Pros Of Hybrid Mobile Application</strong></p>



<p><strong>Lower Development Costs</strong></p>



<p>The creation of hybrid apps has proven 30% cheaper compared to the native application development strategy. The hybrid method means that the developers just require an Android and iOS project. However, the expense of maintaining the mobile app on both platforms is increasing as the requirement for customization rises.</p>



<p><strong>Easy To Maintain</strong></p>



<p>The simpler maintenance of these mobile applications also benefits. For native applications, new versions need to be developed by the development teams. In addition, with each new version release, consumers will need to upgrade their apps. This app skips versioning and facilitates app maintenance in real-time, as it updates a web page.</p>



<p><strong>Easy Scaling</strong></p>



<p>Scale hybrid programs to a number of devices and OSes is extremely simple. That&#8217;s because web technology on all platforms is nearly 100% the same. This allows the code to be reused easily without any need to recompile the app at all.</p>



<p><strong>Offline Support</strong></p>



<p>The lack of offline support often implies that mobile applications suffer from restrictions. It is difficult for firms who serve clients in rural areas or places where connection to the Internet is a challenge. Statistics show that 70% of users quit an app because it takes too much loading time. One of the advantages of this application is its offline accessibility. The end-users thereby have continuous access to the data without any performance breakdowns.</p>



<p><strong>Support for Cloud &amp; Enterprise-Level Solutions</strong></p>



<p>The Exchange Integration Code may be simply included in the cloud in this framework such as Ionic, Titanium, and PhoneGap. These frameworks are essentially simple to utilize, helping developers update program features, aesthetics, and validity. This allows developers to integrate hybrid applications easily with well-known cloud platforms such as Salesforce and AWS.</p>



<p><strong>Improved Performance</strong></p>



<p>Like native applications, this app provides excellent speed and performance. In fact, they are significantly quicker than advanced and responsive applications in some situations. The reason for this is that there is no reliance on network connectivity and even on apps with more users on all devices is greater.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center has-black-color has-text-color has-large-font-size"><strong><a href="https://hasotech.com/10-quick-tips-for-hybrid-mobile-app-developers/">10 Quick Tips for Hybrid Mobile App Developers</a></strong></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:30px"><strong>Cons Of Hybrid Mobile Application</strong></p>



<p><strong>UX</strong></p>



<p>UX is really concerned with these applications. A hybrid application can never deliver a totally native experience for users. Native applications employ user-friendly system interface components, may produce a meaningful solution, and can contribute to maintaining the entire workflow. Without compromising performance, this cannot be accomplished with a hybrid app. Better UX enables increased consumer participation and the app&#8217;s future.</p>



<p><strong>Limited capabilities</strong></p>



<p>Due to the nature of the design of this mobile app, plugins allow you to use the integrated device capabilities. A method&#8217;s drawback is that these are outdated or unlikely to be trustworthy. In addition, if there are no prepared solutions that allow you to have access to a specific element of the device functionality, developers may require plug-ins alone.</p>



<p><strong>Long Wait for New Features</strong></p>



<p>Whenever Apple and Google release a new feature for iOS and Android platforms, hybrid app developers need some time to add support to the new feature. This is because new SDKs are available in the native apps much more quickly than the multifunctional framework. If you have developed your mobile apps with a native approach, it provides your rivals an edge over you.</p>



<p><strong>Design</strong></p>



<p>Design problems remain a consideration as many OSes work differently. The designer must thus change the look according to different operating systems. This might compel us to challenge ourselves in the process of mending. In hybrid applications the breadth of visual and graphical representation is limited.</p>



<p><strong>Poor user experience</strong></p>



<p>This needs to be high irrespective of what you want: a hybrid app or a native app. Unfortunately, the experience of the user is not a strong part of the hybrid apps because the interface should meet in the middle both for iOS and Android platforms. If you concentrate too much on Android, for iOS users, the experience will be poorer and vice versa.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:30px"><strong><a href="https://hasotech.com/secrets-successful-hybrid-mobile-apps/">Secrets of the Successful Hybrid Mobile Apps</a></strong></p>



<h4>Conclusion&nbsp;</h4>



<p>Considering everything, whether or not you should go down to one thing with the construction of hybrid mobile apps. For companies to gain a competitive edge, hybrid mobile applications are crucial. Knowledge and experience in the development of mobile multi-platform applications.</p>



<p><em>If you are looking to</em><a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"><em> hire a hybrid mobile application developer for your application</em></a><em>, you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.&nbsp;</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/pros-and-cons-of-hybrid-mobile-app-development/">Pros And Cons Of Hybrid Mobile App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/pros-and-cons-of-hybrid-mobile-app-development/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Improve Your Business With A Mobile App</title>
		<link>/blog/how-to-improve-your-business-with-a-mobile-app/</link>
					<comments>/blog/how-to-improve-your-business-with-a-mobile-app/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 07:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cross platform mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Custom Relationship Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[offers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OutSourcing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[App development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Improve business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile app Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6433</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A mobile app plays an important part in the growth of any business in the 21st century. The mobile app successfully enhances client loyalty, brand recognition, and efficiency for a company. Each entrepreneur&#8217;s objective is to enhance its sales and retain its customers in a rapid turnaround. They employed plenty of ads, leaflets, pamphlets, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/how-to-improve-your-business-with-a-mobile-app/">How To Improve Your Business With A Mobile App</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A mobile app plays an important part in the growth of any business in the 21st century. The mobile app successfully enhances client loyalty, brand recognition, and efficiency for a company.</p>



<p>Each entrepreneur&#8217;s objective is to enhance its sales and retain its customers in a rapid turnaround. They employed plenty of ads, leaflets, pamphlets, and catalogs a number of years ago to promote sales.</p>



<p>In addition, the notion of the mobile app is vital not only for major companies but also for small enterprises. In addition, a mobile app discusses the full advantages.</p>



<p>Mobile applications are great for any business growth. No random individual or company does, but many studies of various kinds of enterprises have demonstrated this.</p>



<p>So How To Improve Your Business With A Mobile App? Read on to find out.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:35px"><strong>How To Improve Your Business With Mobile App</strong></p>



<p><strong>Better Branding</strong></p>



<p>Mobile applications may assist raise brand recognition and improve loyalty to individuals. It is easy to forget or disregard whether the name or emblem of your organization is shown on the user&#8217;s mobile device. In addition, mobile applications include other capabilities, for example, push notifications.</p>



<p>A particular offer to draw consumers&#8217; attention might be reminded. Such personal branding will only work if you have the appropriate information or knowledge of your clients.</p>



<p><strong>Brings new customers</strong>&nbsp;</p>



<p>A mobile app is the leading digital platform to reach and attract new users with its broad audience. Mobile apps with user-friendly features may be readily downloaded from the app store and it also provides users 24&#215;7 access from wherever without any restriction.</p>



<p>The greatest approach to increase your business reach is with a powerful mobile app for your company. We all know that mobile apps are incredibly simple to use, making your mobile app increasingly available to clients.</p>



<p>The app also offers consumers a number of amenities that can be accessed with a few clicks. It&#8217;s a sensible move to get new clients into your business to develop a mobile app for your business.</p>



<p><strong>Customer Engagement</strong></p>



<p>Nearly 30 hours are spent on mobile applications each month. This provides companies a fantastic chance to get customers involved and get the desired result. As people already utilize their mobile devices, the commission rate on applications is higher.</p>



<p>All they need to do is launch the app and within a few seconds, you have the desired outcome. An easy approach to enhance involvement is to share social media which enables people to share their material and bring you more eyeballs on social media platforms.</p>



<p><strong>Increases loyal customers&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Customers may keep exclusive deals for all businesses at regular intervals. Mobile applications are the greatest way to tell clients about any decrease in the price of a certain product or service.</p>



<p>Offers and discount coupons are important in replicating and building a solid relationship with the prior consumers in any <a href="https://www.bigcommerce.com/blog/">e-commerce</a> business. Mobile applications are fantastic to develop client loyalty to your company.</p>



<p>And mobile applications are fantastic for building client loyalty for your organization with ongoing commitment through alerts and a customer service system.</p>



<p><strong>Push Notifications</strong></p>



<p>Push notifications are a great method to remind your clients to buy their favorite products. You can also market new items or services to regular purchasers based on their previous purchases and interests to keep them as loyal clients with the use of the push notification function in your mobile app.</p>



<p>On the other side, you may inform them about the discounts or deals that you are now offering. So give them a place to connect with and appreciate your brand directly. All of this helps to generate more visitors and more purchases.</p>



<p><strong>Competitive Advantage</strong></p>



<p>In this day, because of the tough competition on the app market, you cannot afford to be lazy. Well, your competitors and the services and goods that you provide require some time to investigate. You&#8217;re going to be creative from here.</p>



<p>You may attract more clients to your businesses if you are careful with this element. After that, you will have the opportunity to do a timely analysis to enhance these services.</p>



<p>This field should not be forgotten that it is not static. That is why when it comes to generating income for your application you have to do your best progress.</p>



<p><strong>Boost Profits</strong></p>



<p>Typically, sales also improve as customer happiness increases. The more individuals with your product and business are engaged and happy, the more consumer demand will increase.</p>



<p>And if you can&#8217;t wait to receive a product from your consumers, let me guarantee you that this request will provide you some big returns.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:25px"><strong>Conclusion</strong></p>



<p>You must understand the previous discussion on the importance of developing a mobile application to promote the brand, expand the accessibility of your services and raise your business sales.</p>



<p>So, I propose that you develop apps on both Android and iOS platforms if you have decided to make a mobile app. Both platforms are popular and your application may reach a pretty big number of users on these platforms.</p>



<p><em>If you are looking to</em><a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"><em> hire a mobile app developer for your application</em></a><em>, you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.&nbsp;</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/how-to-improve-your-business-with-a-mobile-app/">How To Improve Your Business With A Mobile App</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/how-to-improve-your-business-with-a-mobile-app/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is React Native Important In 2021?</title>
		<link>/blog/is-react-native-important-in-2021/</link>
					<comments>/blog/is-react-native-important-in-2021/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 07:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cross platform mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ionic Framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[JavaScript]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[App development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Native app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[react native]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6463</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/is-react-native-important-in-2021/">Is React Native Important In 2021?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p>There has been a really good option for indigenous development for quite some time now and this is React Native development. By utilizing the same code on all platforms, the major benefit is decreased time and cost.</p>
<p>Due to the worldwide pandemic and loss of direct relations between friends, participation in cultural events, and the operation of a business in the model we knew before, online shopping, gaming, social media trends have certainly grown over the last year.</p>
<p>We have found new smartphone apps that have enabled us to continue with most of our activities in many situations. You have to keep an eye on the facts if you want to create a mobile application.</p>
<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size: 35px"><strong>What is React Native?</strong></p>
<p>React Native is a complete framework for building mobile apps and reacting to native <a href="https://medium.com/flutter-community/create-a-cross-platform-app-using-flutter-in-2021-59e582cb625f">cross Platforms</a>. React Native is the finest technology to create an application for both iOS and Android.</p>
<p>The codebase may be reduced by roughly 95%, saving you time and money. It has several open-source libraries with pre-construction components and therefore accelerates the development process.</p>
<p>React Native apps have been designed with strong and state-of-the-art technology to enable companies around the world to reach new clients on mobile platforms.</p>
<p><strong>Native application</strong></p>
<p>Native applications are installed in an app store. They are particularly built for one platform and can use all smartphone capabilities, like the camera, GPS, speed meter, compass, contact list, etc.</p>
<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size: 30px"><strong>React Native is better than Native?</strong></p>
<p>React native is better and unique because it has</p>
<ul>
<li>Lower the <strong>development time</strong></li>
<li>Easy for <strong>Web developers </strong></li>
<li>Cost-effective </li>
</ul>
<p>Native </p>
<ul>
<li>High <strong>development time</strong></li>
<li>High cost</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Development Time</strong></p>
<p>In a native application, you need two distinct teams to make your application available on both platforms, i.e. the Android development team and the iOS development team. This includes additional effort and time to create a mobile app.</p>
<p>In React Native&#8217;s instance, the same developer writes a single code for both platforms, which implies that React native applications may be created for Android and iOS using the same codes.</p>
<p><strong>Mobile App Cost</strong></p>
<p>The response to the cost of developing the mobile app also helps to find the suitable technology for the creation of your mobile app. The app creation using React Native is the top mobile app development firm, but the cost of Native App Development for the same app project may be reduced by 30%-35% in comparison.</p>
<p><strong>Scalability</strong></p>
<p>It offers mobile app developers more chances in comparison with Native technology to handle a greater quantity of work in an app and to publish higher-functionality updates. The winner in terms of scalability of the Native app vs the Reacts Native app is thus React Native.</p>
<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size: 28px"><strong>React Native for Android Developers</strong></p>
<p>React Native is a smooth development in which the features of Native Code easily use, Hot Reloading, and the management of Hassle-free states lead to smooth, efficient, and efficient development.</p>
<p>A platform-sized experience, which boasts native Android and iOS components while the program runs, is the main advantage React Native offers.</p>
<p>This makes it possible for natives to manage the interaction even with a coding foundation written in JavaScript, so that memory, footprint, flexibility, and experience stay preserved.</p>
<p>It is compatible with native code. React Native is a structure that allows you to create the most powerful applications in combination with JavaScript. It offers impeccable performance with native components, guaranteeing that most applications operate seamlessly and native apps operate more often than before.</p>
<p>Reduce time to develop. Apart from open source projects, app developers might experience a 40 percent quicker development time because many elements can be used locally. Reaction Native also supports both Android and iOS, making it easy for both platforms to exchange data and a single code base. The task may therefore be accomplished in less time.</p>
<p>React Native comes with a Live Reload functionality which allows you to view the newest updates as soon as they are made. This makes it easy for the developer. We are passionate about online and mobile app development, we only advise our clients what is correct.</p>
<p>Find the ideal technological combination. You may use React Native to list your application in the Appstore and Playstore and make use of the sensors and device functionality and also wish to perform effectively. The first thing you want to do is to upgrade the mobile app and explore React Native.</p>
<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size: 25px"><strong>Conclusion</strong></p>
<p>In summary, therefore, you know to which end you are turning if you wish to build an ever-change multi-dimensional mobile app. From startups to successful business leaders, people embrace mobile applications instead of just websites. Most of you still know that mobile apps function totally differently from the standard website.</p>
<p><em>If you are looking to</em><a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"><em> hire an application developer, </em></a><em> you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.</em></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/is-react-native-important-in-2021/">Is React Native Important In 2021?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/is-react-native-important-in-2021/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>10 Quick Tips for Hybrid Mobile App Developers</title>
		<link>/blog/10-quick-tips-for-hybrid-mobile-app-developers/</link>
					<comments>/blog/10-quick-tips-for-hybrid-mobile-app-developers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 06:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cross platform mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=5949</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/10-quick-tips-for-hybrid-mobile-app-developers/">10 Quick Tips for Hybrid Mobile App Developers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p>Though <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/hybrid-mobile-app-development-considered-underrated/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hybrid Mobile App development considered underrated</a>, There are still many Hybrid Mobile apps are being developed. Being Hybrid Mobile App Developers, <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/why-we-love-hybrid-mobile-app-development/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">we love Hybrid Mobile App Development.</a> There are many popular apps like Amazon, Uber, Evernote, Facebook etc., The frameworks used to develop Hybrid apps makes Hybrid Mobile app developers easy to make it. To develop a successful mobile app, Hybrid Mobile app developers should follow some <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/secrets-successful-hybrid-mobile-apps/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">secret methods</a>. Though there are many frameworks available to develop Hybrid Mobile apps like <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/ionic-mobile-app-developer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Ionic Framework</a>, There are some tips for Hybrid Mobile App developers to follow.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Choose the Right Framework</h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>When going with Hybrid Mobile app development, Choosing the right framework to develop is very important. There are many frameworks available. Some of them are Ionic Framework, React Native, Xamarin, PhoneGap etc., The very confusion moment is choosing between Ionic Framework or React Native. Ionic Framework is on Angular 4 and React Native is on React js. Since both are booming in the market, It&#8217;s hard to choose the right one.</li>
<li>Anyways, The purpose of developing the Hybrid Mobile App can define it. If you are looking to develop both Web and Mobile app, Then our suggestion is to go with Ionic Framework. Since it is on Angular JS which can be used in both Web and Mobile App, Number of resources to be used can be reduced.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h4><a href="https://www.web.hasotech.com/why-we-love-hybrid-mobile-app-development/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">We Love Hybrid Mobile App Development</a></h4>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>There is a licensing Problem with React Native. It license says They can make it to full premium version anytime. So before choosing React Native, Make sure you can able to overcome the license problem.</li>
<li>If you are a .NET / C# Developer, Then the only option is Xamarin. Xamarin is a Microsoft product which uses C# as a base language to develop Hybrid Mobile app. Of course, You need Visual Studio tools to complete the development.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Ionic Framework &#8211; Lazy Loading Issue</h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>If you are using Ionic Framework, Then you might be facing Lazy Loading issue in the new version. Still, Ionic Framework is working on it to overcome, There are some ways to fix the issue on our own. Instead of declaring all the Nodule Modules in the Main and pages where the node modules to be implemented. Declare the Node modules only in the pages. As the number of Node Modules increases on the Main page, The Lazy Loading time increases.</li>
<li>It is better to avoid unwanted node modules on the main page.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h4><a href="https://www.web.hasotech.com/not-go-hybrid-mobile-app-development/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Don’t go with Hybrid Mobile App Development</a></h4>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Choosing the right Plugins</h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>When we come to Hybrid Mobile App development, Definitely it is going to be on both Android and iOS and sometimes in Windows. While deploying the app to different platforms Plugins may get conflict. Some plugins may support only in Android and not on iOS.</li>
<li>Before choosing a plugin to implement the native function in Mobile App, Make sure it supports in all the platforms.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Checklist for Hybrid Mobile App Developers</h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>Before choosing Hybrid App, Make sure the requirement can be done in Hybrid. If there are more native functions or if the app is very complex, It is suggested to go with Native. But still, if you want to go with Hybrid, Then make sure the app is being developed with proper performance check.</li>
<li>Inspect the App in chrome browser and check for Network and console logs. Try creating the apps without any error in console logs. As the error increases, It may affect the performance.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3><a href="https://www.web.hasotech.com/hybridmobileapp/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hybrid Mobile App Development </a></h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>Make proper performance check in the browser and Mobile App testing before deploying in Play store or App store.</li>
<li>If the mobile app is targeted for lower versions of Android or iOS, Then Hybrid App is not the right choice. Hybrid Apps are meant for Android Lollipop versions and above and iOS 10. Though it supports from Jellybean, It is suggested to with Lollipop target.</li>
</ul>
<p>If you are still looking for any support to know more about Hybrid Mobile app development, Reach our <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/contact-us/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Free consultation team</a> for more details.</p>
<p><strong>Feel free to share your reviews over comments.</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/10-quick-tips-for-hybrid-mobile-app-developers/">10 Quick Tips for Hybrid Mobile App Developers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/10-quick-tips-for-hybrid-mobile-app-developers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You can Give Black Friday Deals &#8211; Products at 90% offer</title>
		<link>/blog/you-can-give-black-friday-deals-products-at-90-offer/</link>
					<comments>/blog/you-can-give-black-friday-deals-products-at-90-offer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 02:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[offers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Augmented Reality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cross platform mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iphone x]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[magento]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[magento2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=5951</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/you-can-give-black-friday-deals-products-at-90-offer/">You can Give Black Friday Deals &#8211; Products at 90% offer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p>Here we are at Black Friday Deals, While all other hosting companies and E-commerce stores are announcing awesome black Friday deals.  <a href="http://www.hasotech.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">HasoTechnology </a>can&#8217;t sit calm and watch. Yes, we are too on the ground. While rest of the world giving black Friday deals on different products. We thought of giving the products that can build the world. You might be probably giving your Black Friday Deals next year. It&#8217;s your time to change the world, Don&#8217;t just looking for others, Start giving your own.</p>
<p> </p>
<h3><a href="http://www.hasotech.com/blackfridaysales/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Black Friday Deals &#8211; Grab Products at</a> <a href="http://www.hasotech.com/blackfridaysales/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">90% offer</a></h3>
<p> </p>
<h3>How can I give Black Friday Deals !!</h3>
<p>It&#8217;s your time now, Are you looking to do your own startup? Looking to make your own product?? Waiting to make your own sales? Here we are, <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/contact-us/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Get started with us</a>. If you are looking make your startup and looking for some tech company or app development company to get started. Then you are at right place. We are here to develop the application or product you are looking for. Get your product with us and start giving your own from next year.</p>
<p> </p>
<h4><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/secrets-successful-hybrid-mobile-apps/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Secrets of the Successful Hybrid Mobile Apps</a></h4>
<p> </p>
<h3>How to get started with Black Friday Deals</h3>
<p>Are you ready to grab the deals? Get started with us. Select the products from <a href="http://www.hasotech.com/blackfridaysales/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Black Friday Deals</a> which you think very apt to get started with your product. Check the demo and <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/contact-us/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">reach our support team</a> who all are always waiting to provide our valuable services. Share all the necessary details and get your products delivered instantly.</p>
<p> </p>
<h4><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/how-to-get-free-magento-2-mobile-app/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to get Free Magento 2 Mobile App</a></h4>
<p>There will be no hidden charges, no locks, full source code will be provided without any restrictions. And we will provide our support team to help you anytime.</p>
<p> </p>
<h4><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/not-go-hybrid-mobile-app-development/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Don’t go with Hybrid Mobile App Development</a></h4>
<p> </p>
<h3>What if my product is not there</h3>
<p>If you couldn&#8217;t find <a href="http://www.hasotech.com/blackfridaysales/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">any get started products</a> on our Black Friday deals. No worries, Just <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/contact-us/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">r</a><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/contact-us/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">each us with the requirements</a> on what you are looking to develop the product. Or simply <a href="mailto:info@hasotech.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Email your Requirements</a> or <a href="hasotech" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">skype us</a> whatever you are comfortable with. We will reach you in very shorter time, Grab your requirements, Get your application done.</p>
<p>We are super excited to hear from you. Or just simply share your views on comments or mail us: info@hasotech.com</p>
<p> </p>
<h4><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/get-your-augmented-reality-app-for-android-and-ios/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Get your Augmented Reality App for Android and iOS</a></h4>
<p> </p>
<h3><a href="http://www.hasotech.com/blackfridaysales/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Black Friday Deals &#8211; Grab Products at 90% offer</a></h3>
<p> </p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/you-can-give-black-friday-deals-products-at-90-offer/">You can Give Black Friday Deals &#8211; Products at 90% offer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/you-can-give-black-friday-deals-products-at-90-offer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: web.hasotech.com @ 2022-10-26 12:09:59 by W3 Total Cache
-->