<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>cons Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<atom:link href="/blog/tag/cons/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/tag/cons/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:35:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/cropped-logo-1-rb-32x32.png</url>
	<title>cons Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/tag/cons/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ionic Application Development &#8211; Pros And Cons</title>
		<link>/blog/ionic-application-development-pros-and-cons/</link>
					<comments>/blog/ionic-application-development-pros-and-cons/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ionic Framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cons]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pros]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web app]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6366</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Businesses worldwide desire an advanced mobile app on their Android and iOS platforms to serve their company. Most of them are caught in the middle where they have difficulty selecting the ideal technologies like ionic, hybrid, native for themselves. Each approach to technology and development has its pros and cons, from which you have to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/ionic-application-development-pros-and-cons/">Ionic Application Development &#8211; Pros And Cons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Businesses worldwide desire an advanced mobile app on their Android and iOS platforms to serve their company. Most of them are caught in the middle where they have difficulty selecting the ideal technologies like ionic, hybrid, native for themselves. </p>



<p>Each approach to technology and development has its pros and cons, from which you have to select the best solution for your company. If you think Ionic is the correct platform application development, below are a few advantages and disadvantages of Ionic development.</p>



<p>Ionic Framework helps us to develop apps using only one codebase for several platforms. Let us learn how it works and what are this solution&#8217;s benefits and downsides. The frameworks are quite popular, however, in this blog, we will focus on the advantages and disadvantages of ionic application development. Let&#8217;s get right in with that statement!</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><br><strong>What is an Ionic Application?</strong></p>



<p>It is used to build <a href="https://hasotech.com/why-we-love-hybrid-mobile-app-development/">hybrid mobile apps </a>using the Open Source Software Development Kit(SDK). It is fully Apache Cordova and Angular based on this ionic framework. More specifically, Ionic is an npm module that requires Node JS to be installed.</p>



<p>The conditions for building these applications are excellent HTML, CSS and JavaScript commands. Because of their suitable properties and usefulness, many developers today opt for ionic frameworks. The main objective is to construct a hybrid mobile app in ionic framework development.</p>



<p>Hybrid applications provide several advantages compared with native applications, in particular in terms of development time. Essentially, the construction of ionic apps allows the captivating design and soft animations of native mobile components.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center has-black-color has-text-color has-large-font-size"><strong><a href="http://Ionic/ Mobile App Developer">Ionic Mobile App Developer</a></strong></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><br><strong>Ionic Applications</strong> <strong>Are</strong></p>



<p><br>●<strong> <a href="https://uptech.team/blog/native-vs-cross-platform-app-development">The cross-platform </a></strong>– single code base for both platforms (except native components)</p>



<p>● <strong>Web-based </strong>– Built using web-views and can be displayed in a browser like PWAs.</p>



<p>● <strong>Access to native API components</strong> – They can access the native device’s cameras, files, and others.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><br><strong>Advantages Of Ionic Application</strong></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>A single codebase across various platforms</strong></p>



<p>It was developed using the Angular and Apache Cordova frame and used as the fundamental technologies for app development HTML 5, CSS, and JavaScript. Alongside the current release of the Ionic, you may utilize Angular with all its advantages and disadvantages for the first time.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Free Open Source Framework</strong></p>



<p>This frame is an open-source framework that is entirely free. Ionic framework applications offer platform-specific, optimized CSS features to match the native appearance of the different mobile operating systems. This Framework offers one of the primary advantages in the provision of CSS, HTML, and JS mobile-optimized code and reducing code rewriting needs.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Cross Mobile App Development</strong></p>



<p>In application development, the development of efficient, compatible, and bespoke apps is of major importance. Ionic integrates with AngularJS, which enhances the interoperability of this code with mobile platforms. Ionic helps to swiftly create apps that make the app more popular and save time and money.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Testing convenience</strong></p>



<p>While Ionic Apps only operate via a review, the browser of the device may be used to test the app. It is much handier because test equipment does not even need to be used to make sure it is all working properly. The same principle applies in the current world to a range of mobile devices.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Appealing Default UI</strong></p>



<p>There are numerous common JavaScript and CSS components in these Framework apps covering many fundamental elements that would like to be developed by a moving app. The menu slides, inputs, buttons, lists, navigation, tab, sliding box, and pop-ups. standard styles are clean and simple, and developers may simply change them by adding CSS classes that have been given by the user to the device.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Quick Development and Time To Market</strong></p>



<p>This development may benefit entrepreneurs and company owners when comparing a mobile app with native apps on both platforms in a short time. Constructing native apps particularly for each platform can take time, which can lead to a market delay and the cost of development of native applications is sometimes costly.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><br><strong>Disadvantages Of Ionic Application</strong></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Performance Issue</strong></p>



<p>The performance of heavy apps is inappropriate for this application. When created with this Framework, apps with heavy realism or heavy graphics might crash.</p>



<p>The major reason behind this is that this application makes its graphics using a browser that does many stages on the screen.</p>



<p>There are, then, study performance optimization strategies to achieve better outcomes if you still want to develop a high-performance application utilizing Ionic.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Security Issues</strong></p>



<p>You must not regard it as a con of this application on your own, but rather the possibility of a hazard with which you have to cope. </p>



<p>Security is a typical problem for the creation of hybrid apps as long as your program can be reversed. Ionic CLI is a prevalent approach since version 4 that makes the code tough for hackers to understand.</p>



<p> But you must also realize that there is no code uglification when you use Angular CLI or earlier versions of Ionic. The code will have to be Uglified by your developers yourself.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Dependency on Plugins</strong></p>



<p>Even Ionic app development firms would admit that they must rely on plugins to have access to native features. You won&#8217;t be able to locate a corresponding plugin in the ionic toolset in some situations.</p>



<p>To build a plugin for very specialized features and functions, you must use the Ionic App development company. </p>



<p>If there is no plug-in, you will be able to discover a module most commonly. You&#8217;d probably have to make something that&#8217;s not in store with the aid of a native developer.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-normal-font-size"><strong>Hot Reloading not Available</strong></p>



<p>To make modifications to the application code, this platform employs a variety of approaches. Hot reloading is regarded as a vital characteristic in the software engineering industry. </p>



<p>Because it allows you to make changes without having to refresh the entire program. It takes some getting accustomed to because it does not support hot reloading and instead relies on live reloading. </p>



<p>When you make changes, live reloading will refresh the whole app to make the changes active. That implies that whenever your developers wish to make changes, their program will be restarted.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><strong>conclusion</strong></p>



<p>For your development, you have reviewed the pros and cons of utilizing this framework. Finally, it is crucial to have your application supported and problems solved on time by the proper Ionic application development firm.</p>



<p><em>If you are looking to<a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"> hire an ionic application developer for your application</a>, you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/ionic-application-development-pros-and-cons/">Ionic Application Development &#8211; Pros And Cons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/ionic-application-development-pros-and-cons/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: web.hasotech.com @ 2022-10-26 12:07:37 by W3 Total Cache
-->