<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Framework Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<atom:link href="/blog/tag/framework/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/tag/framework/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 07:45:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/cropped-logo-1-rb-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Framework Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/tag/framework/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Is AngularJS Good or Bad For Your Web Development?</title>
		<link>/blog/blog-is-angularjs-good-or-bad-for-your-web-development/</link>
					<comments>/blog/blog-is-angularjs-good-or-bad-for-your-web-development/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[MEAN Stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OutSourcing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Angular]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AngularJS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[front-end web framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web app]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6372</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The creation of Web applications is always seen as a challenging undertaking in ensuring the collaboration of the user interface, all the components, and the database data. Many web apps are made from server-side technology. Since AngularJS has both good and bad features for web applications. However, greater customer logic, because the processing capabilities of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/blog-is-angularjs-good-or-bad-for-your-web-development/">Is AngularJS Good or Bad For Your Web Development?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The creation of Web applications is always seen as a challenging undertaking in ensuring the collaboration of the user interface, all the components, and the database data. Many web apps are made from server-side technology. Since AngularJS has both good and bad features for web applications.</p>



<p>However, greater customer logic, because the processing capabilities of today&#8217;s terminals are good, is the most recent demand. To fulfill this demand, many Javascript Frameworks are introduced. Angularjs are especially advisable among these.</p>



<p>You will discover whether AngularJS is helpful or harmful for your web development in this post. Let us briefly reconstruct the key advantages of original AngularJS, among other front-end development frameworks, and identify the main disadvantages of the instrument.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><strong>What Is AngularJS</strong></p>



<p><strong>AngularJS </strong>is a javascript open-source framework used to create Single Page dynamic applications. The syntax of HTML will be extended to provide a succinct and definite demonstration of application components.</p>



<p>We can create with Angularjs. The administration of front-end management procedures was simplified. It decreases the code you want to develop. Angular JS supports developers in creating apps at the architectural level.</p>



<p>Packed with several frameworks and plugins suitable for developers and designers alike. Desktop, mobile, and tablet applications were created utilizing the newest angular9 react across platforms.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><strong>Why Should You Use AngularJS For Your Web Development?</strong></p>



<p><strong>Two-way data binding</strong> </p>



<p>It was created with the architecture of the model view controller. And the frame of the model and the view synced. When the data changes in the model, the view also changes. The binding of two ways of data helped engineers to minimize the duration of development because no new code was required to create ongoing views and models.</p>



<p><strong>Supports SPA features</strong></p>



<p>A quicker website transition is the key reason for building single-page apps. The website works and looks like an app. Instead of using the browser default technique for loading new pages, the Website will dynamically communicate with the Web browser by replacing the old website with new webserver information. This is known as a <a href="https://medium.com/@NeotericEU/single-page-application-vs-multiple-page-application-2591588efe58">Single Page Application (SPA)</a>.</p>



<p><strong>Dom manipulations</strong></p>



<p>The view extends the dom to show data and manipulates the dom to embed behavior. But the dom-manipulation code is within the directives and not in the view with angular. It implies that views containing placeholder data such as the HTML Page are shown. This vision fits nicely with the designers of the user interface.</p>



<p><strong>Optimal Web Application Management</strong></p>



<p>The code generally must be broken down into three separate components: Modeling, Viewing, and Control (MVC). The developers then integrate their components&#8217; code manually.</p>



<p>It saves time when this frame strings code together automatically. Application data is maintained and managed by the model component.</p>



<p>The view component presents to users all of the data or parts of the data. While the control component determines how the model and the view are linked.</p>



<p><strong>Community</strong> </p>



<p>This framework was quite popular among developers right from the very beginning. A robust community has given sufficient training materials, conversations, and tools for third parties to start utilizing this framework and find a solution to virtually any problem emerging.</p>



<p><strong>Frequent Testing </strong></p>



<p>Using this framework, developers may check an app to guarantee the application is error-free as often as feasible. This is one of the main advantages of building AngularJS web apps. This takes care of the entire object lifecycle. Developers need not bother about namespace and instance. This frame eliminates handling and dynamic loading problems.</p>



<p><strong>Powerful Framework</strong></p>



<p>A solid solution for speedier front-end development is another benefit for this. It contains several characteristics, including MVC patterns, directives, and the injection of dependencies. It is a frequently available platform among developers. Developers can therefore enhance the HTML syntax and construct client-side apps.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><strong>Why You Shouldn&#8217;t Use AngularJS For Your Web Development?</strong></p>



<p><strong>Specific Libraries</strong></p>



<p>This framework does not operate effectively with other libraries. There is an issue. You will need to utilize various test stacks while testing a single rich app with several JavaScript iterations.</p>



<p><strong>Not Secure </strong></p>



<p>The apps developed with this framework are not safe as a JavaScript-only framework. Authentication and authorization on the server side are required to secure an application.</p>



<p><strong>Lagging UI</strong></p>



<p>If more than 2000 observers are present, but the user interface can delay considerably. the potential intricacy of the angular shapes is therefore restricted. This covers the grids and lists of big data.</p>



<p><strong>JavaScript support mandatory</strong></p>



<p>It is a JavaScript frame when JS is deactivated to access numerous PCs and laptops. That implies you may not be able to access your website by people linked with such a system.</p>



<h4 class="has-medium-font-size">Conclusion</h4>



<p>Hope you have learned why AngularJS should and should not be used. In the end, your web development needs to have the proper AngularJS. We are here to help you apply and solve your problems on schedule.<br /><em>If you are looking to<a href="https://hasotech.com/contact-us/"> hire an AngularJS application developer for your application</a>, you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/blog-is-angularjs-good-or-bad-for-your-web-development/">Is AngularJS Good or Bad For Your Web Development?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/blog-is-angularjs-good-or-bad-for-your-web-development/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: web.hasotech.com @ 2022-10-26 12:09:37 by W3 Total Cache
-->