<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Ecommerce Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<atom:link href="/blog/tag/ecommerce/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/tag/ecommerce/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 12:37:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/cropped-logo-1-rb-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Ecommerce Archives - Hasotech</title>
	<link>https://hasotech.com/blog/tag/ecommerce/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Is One Page Checkout Better Than Multi-Page</title>
		<link>/blog/is-one-page-checkout-better-than-multi-page/</link>
					<comments>/blog/is-one-page-checkout-better-than-multi-page/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 12:22:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marketplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Multi Vendor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[multi-page checkout]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[one-page checkout]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=7017</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How many people visit your website, but how many converts it, depends not on the success of your eCommerce business. The more conversions you receive, the higher your income and it depends mostly on your page checkout. One of the important phases of the buying experience is the checkout procedure. Of course, bringing people to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/is-one-page-checkout-better-than-multi-page/">Is One Page Checkout Better Than Multi-Page</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>How many people visit your website, but how many converts it, depends not on the success of your eCommerce business. The more conversions you receive, the higher your income and it depends mostly on your page checkout.</p>



<p>One of the important phases of the buying experience is the checkout procedure. Of course, bringing people to your check-out page is never easy, and even if you get them to that stage, many things might arise to prevent them from paying.</p>



<p>For years, e-commerce specialists have been working on optimizing the checkout page. You should use the purchasing behavior of your purchasers to choose the greatest alternative for your buyers. Knowing your target consumers better and running an efficient test is a good thing to set up your various checkout pages.</p>



<p>There is no end to the argument over a one-page checkout vs a multi-page checkout. While several professional eCommerce experts favor a one-page review, some believe it is a superior alternative for a multi-page checkout.</p>



<p>We will compare both approaches in this post to help you choose the one that&#8217;s perfect for you. Let&#8217;s get started.</p>



<h2>One-Page Checkout</h2>



<p><strong>What is One-Page checkout?</strong></p>



<p>All functions and fields of the checkout are shown on one single page using a one-page checkout. This covers all information required for customers to complete their checkout, including billing, delivery address, payment choices, delivery options, and associated fields.</p>



<p>One-page checkout is a standard Magento 2 store model (the standard checkout page), which is very much improved in shopping optimization when compared to Magento 1, as all these stages may now be found in only one page, instead of 6 steps spanning over six pages.</p>



<h3><strong>Benefits of One-Page Checkout</strong></h3>



<p><strong>Quick Checkout</strong></p>



<p>It enables clients to check out rapidly with full checkout information at an early stage. You get rid of clicking repeatedly to get to the next phase (in the event of multi-phase checkout) and may input all your billing, shipping, and payment data on the same page.</p>



<p><strong>Reduce Carts Abandoned</strong></p>



<p>Studies have revealed that 21 percent of online consumers usually give up their carts before the checkout since the shopping site takes too slow to react and is difficult to grasp. You may minimize the abandoned number of cards by expediting the process by having all check-out items on one page and boosting the conversion rate.</p>



<p><strong>Higher Conversion Rates</strong></p>



<p>Statistics suggest that one-page check-outs are probably 10% to 20% more than multi-page checkouts however, this also relies on the sort of items you are marketing. The statistics showed that However, quicker and simpler checkout pages may certainly convert and promote purchase decisions more effectively.</p>



<p><strong>Easy to Understand</strong></p>



<p>A one-stage checkout makes it quick and easy to grasp the design of your website and gives your clients a clear image. It also makes it easier for you to check your data because you do not have to move between pages.</p>



<p><strong>Why You Shouldn’t Adopt One-Page Checkout?</strong></p>



<p><strong>Site speed</strong></p>



<p>It might increase the loading time required for the site than always because it comprises too many components on one page. Shoppers like to buy things quickly, therefore it is a good idea not only to work effectively but also to load your homepage swiftly. Otherwise, we worry you may lose consumers who fear wasting their valuable time.</p>



<p><strong>Limited Analysis</strong></p>



<p>If you use Google Analytics and utilize this tool to monitor your pages, you will not need a one-page checkout. It is difficult to identify with a one-page checkout at what point the client left the process. You can, however, read clearly on which page the consumer exited the purchase cycle using the multi-page checkout.</p>



<h4>Multi-Page Checkout</h4>



<p><strong>What is Multi-Page checkout?</strong></p>



<p>Checkouts multi-step, distribute over multiple pages the checkout procedures. Typically, this sort of checkout demands that customers enter their desired mode of delivery, delivery and billing information, and payment information manually. The full check-out procedure is completed in multiple pages through a multi-page or multi-phase check-out.&nbsp;</p>



<p>To complete the checkout process, customer must provide their data independently on each page. Checkouts of several pages are split into different Web sites, generally from 3 to 4 pages, as opposed to one-page checkout, which has all needed components and data on the same screen.</p>



<h5><strong>Benefits of Multi-Page Checkout</strong></h5>



<p><strong>Clean and Simple Layout</strong></p>



<p>As each page contains a certain type of information alone, input fields are presented in a clean design with fewer embroilments at every phase since the checkout is separated into parts. The consumers will not be overwhelmed, thus. Although it needs more clicks to proceed, it will be less frightening and easier to fill in for certain people.</p>



<p><strong>Good User Experience</strong></p>



<p>The multi-step inspection procedure separates the inspection process into many phases. Each stage includes simply a few fields to cover that can make consumers less frightening. In addition, the progress indicator enables clients to understand how far they have gone in the checkout process and how many further steps the purchase can take.</p>



<p><strong>Better Analytics</strong></p>



<p>Multi-page checkouts help website developers to understand better the behavior of their consumers to evaluate and discover stages through which users exit and abandon carts. This sort of information is very useful in making correct modifications and improving the conversion rates of any online shop.</p>



<p><strong>Higher Security</strong></p>



<p>If the procedure is slower and clients are permitted to fill in step-by-step their information, they will probably be more sure to shop on a website. This sensation is especially essential when customers buy something costly and worthwhile for minor nuances.</p>



<p><strong>Email Collection</strong></p>



<p>The customer’s contact data are collected in the first phase of the multi-stage checkout procedure. Even if the consumer does not finish the checkout, if the first stages have been completed, you will receive emails from potential customers. These emails can be used for advertising emails later.</p>



<p><strong>Why You Shouldn’t Adopt Multi-Page Checkout?</strong></p>



<p><strong>Time-consuming</strong></p>



<p>The consumers need to complete their orders by too many tiny stages instead of completing the check-out in one move. They may not be encouraged to go into another store rather than stay at your place if you&#8217;re in a quick hurry or don&#8217;t have much patience.</p>



<p><strong>Harder to change or correct details&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Since each stage includes various facts on multiple pages, if you wish, it is difficult to correct or modify information. For example, you should go back to update your billing address, if you are about to pay, but find there is a mistake. This might create irritation and the possibility of cart loss.</p>



<h6><strong>Conclusion</strong></h6>



<p>There is no single size suited for every eCommerce website check-out procedure because each site has a diverse mix of consumers and items. The optimal control procedure for your site varies depending on several aspects, including the percentage of repeat purchases, needs for sales funnel analytics, product type, and the amount of information necessary.</p>



<p>The ideal answer is to test the two checkouts A/B and find out if your online shop may be better by taking the one-page or multi-stage checkout procedure.</p>



<p><em>If you are looking to </em><a href="http://hasotech.com/contact-us/"><strong><em>hire an eCommerce application developer for your application</em></strong></a><em>, you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/is-one-page-checkout-better-than-multi-page/">Is One Page Checkout Better Than Multi-Page</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/is-one-page-checkout-better-than-multi-page/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Your eCommerce Site Needs Mobile Application?</title>
		<link>/blog/why-your-ecommerce-site-needs-mobile-application/</link>
					<comments>/blog/why-your-ecommerce-site-needs-mobile-application/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dhivyameena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:35:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Needs Of Ecommerce Mobile App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Website]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hasotech.com/?p=6342</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For eCommerce companies, the sky is the limit. Today, more than ever, people buy online. All industries worldwide are involved in this assertion. The internet power has enabled you to contact consumers from any device at any time, anyplace. But your sort of gadgets will have a big influence on your success. The full potential [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/why-your-ecommerce-site-needs-mobile-application/">Why Your eCommerce Site Needs Mobile Application?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>For eCommerce companies, the sky is the limit. Today, more than ever, people buy online. All industries worldwide are involved in this assertion. The internet power has enabled you to contact consumers from any device at any time, anyplace. But your sort of gadgets will have a big influence on your success.</p>



<p><br>The full potential of your eCommerce shop with a website alone is never reached. When you study the latest trends in eCommerce, you notice immediately that everything is moving. In this article, we will discuss in detail, the importance of mobile apps to grow an e-commerce business. Take a look.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:23px"><br><strong>Reason Your eCommerce Site Needs Mobile Application</strong></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><br><strong>Easy Accessibility<br></strong></p>



<p>Smartphones are simple to carry, and currently, it&#8217;s a trend that makes mobile app access easier than websites. Mobile applications improve the comfort level by effortlessly linking them to a vital tool for on-the-go interaction with clients.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><br><strong>Direct-to-Customer Marketing Channel<br></strong></p>



<p>Brands must consistently and steadily engage with mobile eCommerce to exploit the potential of connected clients. The mobile trade app not only helps consumers remain linked to the business but also efficiently provides customers with agreements, offers, and promotions.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><br><strong>Shoppers prefer apps to browsers<br></strong></p>



<p>It is not unexpected that you choose to use Mobile applications. Ecommerce apps are considerably easier to use when buying, particularly when you are not visiting an online business on a one-off basis. To begin with, you don&#8217;t have to recall a URL and log in to the shop. Moreover, apps offer superior safety and performance than mobile browsers.</p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><br><strong>Personalization </strong></p>



<p><br>Use your clients&#8217; information in the application for your benefit. For example, by using priority features and relevant suggestions based on the previous buying, you can enable your consumers to personalize their experience in your business.<br></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><strong>Push notifications</strong></p>



<p>To communicate with your consumers, use push notifications. Notify them or make them know when they wish to return to stock on sales and special offers. Make alerts easier by specifying the name of your users.<br></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><strong>Ecommerce push notification<br></strong></p>



<p>Content exclusive. Implement only mobile offerings available – such as limited discounts or unique rates for applicants. Special incentives motivate your regular clients to download and raise conversion rates.<br></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><strong>Rewards system<br></strong></p>



<p>By creating a fidelity program you may urge your consumers to continue returning. They can be utilized in the form of points for a free item or a significant discount, early access to a new collection, or benefits for future purchases.<br></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><strong>Ecommerce rewards system on the mobile app<br></strong></p>



<p>Support advanced. Good assistance for customers goes much further. Create a strong connection between your shop and your consumers 24 hours a day. Instead of switching to the desktop version, customers should be able to fix their issues via live chat or chat in the app.<br></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><strong>Customer loyalty<br></strong></p>



<p>The key reason to take into account is to develop your mobile app for client loyalty. With all the distractions out there, due to the huge volume of advertising all around us, we eventually lose our effect on clients. It&#8217;s time to establish a true and honest relationship with your customers and make them loyal to your goods and service.<br></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><strong>Apps Referrals<br></strong></p>



<p>Mobile applications make social movement the most effective manner. The applications include common buttons that may be used to disseminate further information. A well-conceived and the effective app can achieve the consumers&#8217; confidence. It may be used to distribute information in this way. Thus, the number of individuals using a certain app might gradually rise.<br></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><a href="https://www.convinceandconvert.com/digital-marketing/improve-user-experience/"><strong>A better and enhanced UX</strong></a><strong><br></strong></p>



<p>A good presentation of e-business helps consumers comprehend the company goal in increasing mobile app marketing. Mobile applications offer considerably better navigation and are now built to take account of the screen size of the user utilizing responsive features. Less distraction and better navigation enable buyers to concentrate more on their items and therefore increase sales growth.<br></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color" style="font-size:18px"><strong>Lower mobile shopping cart abandonment rate<br></strong></p>



<p>Shopping cart abandonment is a big issue for eCommerce. One thing is to get clients to add things to their carts and another is to take them fully through a checkout. Whereas in the mobile application the delivery and payment information is saved within the system, which enables users to make one-click transactions. This allows consumers, without unwanted distractions, to check out quickly.<br></p>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><strong>Conclusion</strong></p>



<p><br>We believe that the post will explain why the development of an e-commerce business is important to mobile apps. So, do not wait and start creating a mobile website for eCommerce shopping immediately if you are an eCommerce business owner.</p>



<p><br><em>If you are looking to <strong><a href="http://hasotech.com/contact-us/">hire an eCommerce application developer</a> </strong>for your application, you can consult our development experts and understand how we can convert your idea into reality.</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/why-your-ecommerce-site-needs-mobile-application/">Why Your eCommerce Site Needs Mobile Application?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/why-your-ecommerce-site-needs-mobile-application/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You can Give Black Friday Deals &#8211; Products at 90% offer</title>
		<link>/blog/you-can-give-black-friday-deals-products-at-90-offer/</link>
					<comments>/blog/you-can-give-black-friday-deals-products-at-90-offer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 02:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[offers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Augmented Reality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cross platform mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iphone x]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[magento]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[magento2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=5951</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/you-can-give-black-friday-deals-products-at-90-offer/">You can Give Black Friday Deals &#8211; Products at 90% offer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p>Here we are at Black Friday Deals, While all other hosting companies and E-commerce stores are announcing awesome black Friday deals.  <a href="http://www.hasotech.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">HasoTechnology </a>can&#8217;t sit calm and watch. Yes, we are too on the ground. While rest of the world giving black Friday deals on different products. We thought of giving the products that can build the world. You might be probably giving your Black Friday Deals next year. It&#8217;s your time to change the world, Don&#8217;t just looking for others, Start giving your own.</p>
<p> </p>
<h3><a href="http://www.hasotech.com/blackfridaysales/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Black Friday Deals &#8211; Grab Products at</a> <a href="http://www.hasotech.com/blackfridaysales/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">90% offer</a></h3>
<p> </p>
<h3>How can I give Black Friday Deals !!</h3>
<p>It&#8217;s your time now, Are you looking to do your own startup? Looking to make your own product?? Waiting to make your own sales? Here we are, <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/contact-us/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Get started with us</a>. If you are looking make your startup and looking for some tech company or app development company to get started. Then you are at right place. We are here to develop the application or product you are looking for. Get your product with us and start giving your own from next year.</p>
<p> </p>
<h4><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/secrets-successful-hybrid-mobile-apps/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Secrets of the Successful Hybrid Mobile Apps</a></h4>
<p> </p>
<h3>How to get started with Black Friday Deals</h3>
<p>Are you ready to grab the deals? Get started with us. Select the products from <a href="http://www.hasotech.com/blackfridaysales/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Black Friday Deals</a> which you think very apt to get started with your product. Check the demo and <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/contact-us/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">reach our support team</a> who all are always waiting to provide our valuable services. Share all the necessary details and get your products delivered instantly.</p>
<p> </p>
<h4><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/how-to-get-free-magento-2-mobile-app/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to get Free Magento 2 Mobile App</a></h4>
<p>There will be no hidden charges, no locks, full source code will be provided without any restrictions. And we will provide our support team to help you anytime.</p>
<p> </p>
<h4><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/not-go-hybrid-mobile-app-development/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Don’t go with Hybrid Mobile App Development</a></h4>
<p> </p>
<h3>What if my product is not there</h3>
<p>If you couldn&#8217;t find <a href="http://www.hasotech.com/blackfridaysales/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">any get started products</a> on our Black Friday deals. No worries, Just <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/contact-us/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">r</a><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/contact-us/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">each us with the requirements</a> on what you are looking to develop the product. Or simply <a href="mailto:info@hasotech.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Email your Requirements</a> or <a href="hasotech" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">skype us</a> whatever you are comfortable with. We will reach you in very shorter time, Grab your requirements, Get your application done.</p>
<p>We are super excited to hear from you. Or just simply share your views on comments or mail us: info@hasotech.com</p>
<p> </p>
<h4><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/get-your-augmented-reality-app-for-android-and-ios/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Get your Augmented Reality App for Android and iOS</a></h4>
<p> </p>
<h3><a href="http://www.hasotech.com/blackfridaysales/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Black Friday Deals &#8211; Grab Products at 90% offer</a></h3>
<p> </p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/you-can-give-black-friday-deals-products-at-90-offer/">You can Give Black Friday Deals &#8211; Products at 90% offer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/you-can-give-black-friday-deals-products-at-90-offer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to get Free Magento 2 Mobile App</title>
		<link>/blog/how-to-get-free-magento-2-mobile-app/</link>
					<comments>/blog/how-to-get-free-magento-2-mobile-app/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 09:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Magento]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Magento 2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[magento]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[magento2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hasotech.com/?p=2158</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/how-to-get-free-magento-2-mobile-app/">How to get Free Magento 2 Mobile App</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<h1>How to get Free Magento 2 Mobile App</h1>
<p>Magento is one of the most popular E-commerce Platform. Small-scale industries and startups are using Magento 2 as the primary solution. Especially the Magento version 2.0 has come up with a lot of issues fixed and many features. Magento 2 has made with mobile optimization and good loading speed. In this mobile world, it is mandatory to have a mobile application for E-commerce. Magento 2 Mobile app will increase the sales and gets users engagement. Lots of improvement can be made. Increase your profit with Magento 2 Mobile app.</p>
<h2>Magento 2 Mobile App</h2>
<p>With Magento 2 Mobile app, It&#8217;s pretty easy to keep users engaged. With regular Push notifications, and other activities keep your users engaged. But as features increase the cost of developing Magento 2 mobile app also increase. Some small businesses might not able to afford such mobile apps. There is no use of launching a mobile app with minimal features. But with a ready-made solution, One can able to get it at an affordable price. To make it even easier, We thought of giving the solution for free. Here is how to get Free Magento 2 Mobile App.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/get-your-virtual-reality-mobile-application/">Get your Virtual Reality Mobile Application</a></h3>
<h2>How to get Free Magento 2 Mobile App</h2>
<p>We have made very simple to provide Free Mobile app for your Magento 2 E-commerce site.</p>
<p>Just follow the below mentioned steps</p>
<ul>
<li>Add following links in your E-Commerce site footer
<ul>
<li><a href="http://www.hasotech.com/">http://www.hasotech.com/</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.hasotech.com/magento2mobileapp/">http://www.hasotech.com/magento2mobileapp/</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>After adding the links Email us your Magento 2 E-commerce website link <strong><a href="mailto:info@hasotech.com">info@hasotech.com</a> </strong></li>
<li>Our team will review the site and get the required details</li>
<li>Get your free Ecommerce Mobile app for Android</li>
<li>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.web.hasotech.com/ecommerce-app-development/">Ten Unbelievable Facts About E-commerce App Development</a></h3>
</li>
</ul>
<p>The free version of Magento 2 mobile app will be with the features as in <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/blog/works/amaz4u-2/">https://www.hasotech.com/blog/works/amaz4u-2/</a></p>
<p>Also, the free version includes only android. If you are looking for iOS, We appreciate to reach us over email <a href="mailto:info@hasotech.com">info@hasotech.com  </a></p>
<p>Feel free to comment your reviews and feedbacks about the free version of Magneto 2 mobile app. Also If you are looking for customized E-commerce Mobile application comment your requirements. Or Email us <a href="mailto:info@hasotech.com">info@hasotech.com</a>.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/very-easy-to-develop-a-mobile-app/">Very easy to Develop a Mobile App</a></h3>
<p>For any kind of customized solution on E-Commerce on both web and Mobile app. Feel free to reach us for better solutions in a different way.</p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/how-to-get-free-magento-2-mobile-app/">How to get Free Magento 2 Mobile App</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/how-to-get-free-magento-2-mobile-app/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Get your Virtual Reality Mobile Application</title>
		<link>/blog/get-your-virtual-reality-mobile-application/</link>
					<comments>/blog/get-your-virtual-reality-mobile-application/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 04:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ionic Framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ionic framework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[virtual reality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hasotech.com/?p=2135</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/get-your-virtual-reality-mobile-application/">Get your Virtual Reality Mobile Application</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<h1>Get your Virtual Reality Mobile Application</h1>
<p><strong>Virtual reality mobile application</strong> has been an emerging technology. Medical, entertainment, gaming, fashion etc., are using Virtual reality technology. Virtual reality uses three-dimensional frames which make a user to feel the objects as real. Just take the users to the virtual world. One of the very best implementations of Virtual reality is E-commerce. If you are in <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/ecommerce-app-development/">E-Commerce business</a> and planning to develop an application. Virtual reality mobile application is the best technology to use. You might be thinking how about a user without virtual reality device. One can use the application in normal mode too.</p>
<h4 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/never-mess-business-mobile-app-development/">Never Mess With Business Mobile App Development</a></h4>
<p>Choosing the right tech stack to develop Virtual Reality Mobile Application is difficult one. The tech stack should be easy and beneficiary. Imagin, developing Web, Android and iOS VR application with same tech stack. With just one single code, Deploy on different platforms. Yes, It&#8217;s Hybrid Virtual Reality Mobile Application.</p>
<h2>Developing Hybrid Virtual Reality Mobile Application</h2>
<p>When it comes to <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/hybrid-mobile-application-development/">Developing Hybrid Mobile Application</a> we prefer <a href="https://www.web.hasotech.com/ionic-mobile-app-developer/">Ionic Framework</a>. Which is well-going technology for Hybrid. To deploy the application in different platform Ionic framework can be used. With single code get the app on Android and iOS and other mobile platforms. Developing Virtual reality mobile application is not possible with the Ionic framework. One of the best part going with Hybrid is, We can use Web Plugins in Mobile Applications. Similarly to develop virtual reality Mobile Application in Hybrid. We are going to use a Web Framework. <strong>aframe.io </strong>for building Virtual Reality Mobile application as well as Web Application.</p>
<h2>Get Started with Virtual Reality Mobile Application</h2>
<p>The installation process for Virtual Reality Mobile Application is very easy. aframe.io is a Javascript framework which obviously supports both on the web and hybrid mobile apps. For developing Virtual Reality Application, Initializing the Javascript file of aframe.io is enough. Check the link for detailed installation steps https://aframe.io/docs/0.7.0/introduction/installation.html</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.web.hasotech.com/whats-crazy-mobile-app-development/">What’s crazy on Mobile App Development</a></h3>
<h2>3D Models for Virtual Reality Mobile application</h2>
<p>3D Frames make best Virtual Reality Application. For a better experience, it must be developed with proper tools. There are many tools available to develop 3D images for Virtual reality.</p>
<p>Places to find 3D models include:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://sketchfab.com/" target="_blank" rel="external noopener">Sketchfab</a></li>
<li><a href="http://clara.io/" target="_blank" rel="external noopener">Clara.io</a></li>
<li><a href="http://archive3d.net/" target="_blank" rel="external noopener">Archive3D</a></li>
<li><a href="https://3dwarehouse.sketchup.com/" target="_blank" rel="external noopener">Sketchup’s 3D Warehouse</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.turbosquid.com/Search/3D-Models/free" target="_blank" rel="external noopener">TurboSquid</a></li>
</ul>
<p>These tools can be used to generate 3D images for developing Virtual reality mobile application.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/very-easy-to-develop-a-mobile-app/">Very easy to Develop a Mobile App</a></h3>
<h2>Integrating aframe.io and Ionic Framework</h2>
<p>To make virtual reality Mobile application, aframe.io should be integrated with Ionic Frameworks. The Ionic framework helps to deploy the application on Android and iOS. To make this happen, Create a new view in Ionic framework application and implement aframe.io application. This would bring the entire Virtual reality mobile application under the Ionic framework.</p>
<p>Now you are with Hybrid Virtual reality mobile application. Share your experience on virtual reality and developing such applications for your business.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/iphone-x-ios-11-mobile-app-development/">iPhone X iOS 11 Mobile App Development</a></h3>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/get-your-virtual-reality-mobile-application/">Get your Virtual Reality Mobile Application</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/get-your-virtual-reality-mobile-application/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Never Mess With Business Mobile App Development</title>
		<link>/blog/never-mess-business-mobile-app-development/</link>
					<comments>/blog/never-mess-business-mobile-app-development/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 06:54:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid Mobile app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hasotech.com/?p=2034</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/never-mess-business-mobile-app-development/">Never Mess With Business Mobile App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<h1>Never Mess With Business Mobile App Development</h1>
<p>Are you running a business? Business Mobile App Development is needed one. Don&#8217;t mind what is your business is about. Having a Mobile App Development team for your business is important. The scope of Mobile application has been increasing every day. The more we engage with our customers, The more business we will get.  And one of the best ways to make customer engagement is having a Business Mobile App Development. Let&#8217;s check in detail on Having a business mobile app development team. Pros and cons of mobile application and much more details.</p>
<h2>Business Mobile App Development</h2>
<p>When it comes to business mobile app development. It&#8217;s not necessary to be more professional. The objective of the mobile application should bring more business. Brand awareness is also another important factor. Make sure your business mobile app development team is focusing on user engagement. The application should bring more customers rather than just offering many features. Having such mobile application will help to connect directly with customers. And customers feedback is always very important for business development.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/very-easy-to-develop-a-mobile-app/">Very easy to Develop a Mobile App</a></h3>
<h2>Can I afford a Mobile App Development team?</h2>
<p>It&#8217;s always very easy to find a mobile app development team. There are many software companies offering such services. When it comes to cost, Business owners hesitate to invest more money for app development. You can find a mobile app development company at a cheaper price and also at a very high price. It&#8217;s all about what you give is what you get. When you invest more money on making a mobile app, The more standard application you will get.</p>
<p>In case if you would like to start with a low budget. Start making the mobile app with minimal features and provide to the customers. Based on customer response and if you feel this would increase the business. Then no doubt, go with complete features.</p>
<p>In short, If you have good confidence and budget. Start making a compelete mobile app with all features. Else go with step by step by developing alpha, beta and improve it.</p>
<h2>Tips for Business Mobile App Development</h2>
<p><strong>Choosing the right development team:</strong> is very first one. A good team always provides good suggestions and helps for better development. Make sure the development team is flexible and have some business domain knowledge.This would help to make a better application.</p>
<p><strong>Understand the customer needs:</strong> There is no use of developing a mobile app without any need. Make proper analysis how the mobile application going to help your customers. And also very important is, how it is going to bring more business.</p>
<p><strong>Don&#8217;t dump with all features:</strong> It&#8217;s not necessary to provide more features. The more we give unique features which solve a customer problem. The more we get customers engagement.</p>
<p><strong>Don&#8217;t invest more</strong>: Before implementing the app, Don&#8217;t make a huge investment on it. Getting started with the small application is more enough. Having a step by step development at the proper time is always recommended.</p>
<p><strong>Push Notification:</strong> Let your customers know that you are working for them. Provide them regular updates over push notification. Let them know your offers and services.</p>
<p><strong>Analyse the customer Problem:</strong> This might be the last point, but this should be the first step. Before getting a mobile app development team analyze the customer need or problem statement. And develop the application which solves the customer problem.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/whats-crazy-mobile-app-development/">What’s crazy on Mobile App Development</a></h3>
<h2>Pros of Business Mobile App Development</h2>
<ul>
<li>Business Mobile Application always increases your business and brings more customers</li>
<li>Get customers engaged and get closer with them</li>
<li>Push notification may drive more business</li>
<li>Having direct communication with customers will always help to get better feedback</li>
<li>Increase your business brand</li>
<li>More reach of mobile app = more business</li>
</ul>
<h2>Cons of Business Mobile App Development</h2>
<ul>
<li>There are many benefits you may get with the business mobile app. But at the same time, if the application is worse it may spoil your brand name</li>
<li>If the idea is not unique, It may create many competitors</li>
<li>The mobile application may irritate the customers</li>
</ul>
<p>There are always pros and cons in everything. The more we avoid cons, The better business we will get. Hope this article has helped you to get an idea of Business Mobile App Development.</p>
<p>Let us know about your business, And we will tell how a mobile app can help to grow your business. Share your views in comments and get to know more.</p>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/know-about-mobile-app-development/">Know about Mobile App Development</a></h3>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/never-mess-business-mobile-app-development/">Never Mess With Business Mobile App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/never-mess-business-mobile-app-development/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ten Unbelievable Facts About Ecommerce App Development</title>
		<link>/blog/ecommerce-app-development/</link>
					<comments>/blog/ecommerce-app-development/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 08:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hybrid App]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile App]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hasotech.com/?p=2025</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/ecommerce-app-development/">Ten Unbelievable Facts About Ecommerce App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p>Ecommerce App Development is one of the trending in the current century. The Ecommerce business includes buying and selling online. Making a purchase over the mobile app is trending now. Online payment or Cash on delivery payment has become easy. The Electronic Commerce or Ecommerce App Development makes Business to Consumer, Business to Business, Consumer to Business, Consumer to Consumer sales. The Ecommerce App Development has become easy which makes a rise in competitors. There are many frameworks available for Ecommerce App Development like Magento, Woocommerce, Shopify etc.,</p>
<h2>Ten Facts about Ecommerce App Development</h2>
<ul>
<li>
<h4><strong>Most of the</strong> <strong>Ecommerce App Development fails due to lack of investment </strong></h4>
<ul>
<li>Though there are many frameworks available, Ecommerce needs continuous development to survive in the market. Due to heavy competition, Ecommerce app development to be maintained properly.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<h4><strong>Ecommerce App Development can be done in 7 days </strong></h4>
<ul>
<li>Yes, Since there are many Web frameworks available, A basic Ecommerce site can be developed in a week with default functions.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<h4><strong>E-commerce Mobile App Needed for success </strong></h4>
<ul>
<li>There is no use of having Ecommerce App development on Web alone. 67% of the Online purchase is using Mobile application.</li>
<li>Ecommerce Mobile app development is must to survey with competitors</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/whats-crazy-mobile-app-development/">What’s crazy on Mobile App Development</a></h3>
<ul>
<li>
<h4><strong>Multivendor E-commerce app Development </strong></h4>
<ul>
<li>To move an E-commerce app development in a proper way. Better to start the development with multivendor support.</li>
<li>Multivendor helps to minimize the work and improves development</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<h4><strong>Another fail reason: More than Ecommerce App Development </strong></h4>
<ul>
<li>It&#8217;s not enough to just develop an app for Ecommerce. Proper promotion on Social Networks and SEO Optimization.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<h4><strong>It&#8217;s very cheaper to develop </strong></h4>
<ul>
<li>There is always a fact that, E-commerce app development always costs high. Of course, it costs high but at the same time, there are many ready-made solutions available on Ecommerce App development which it cheaper. The more money you invest, the more standard you get</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<h4><strong>Mobile app is easy with Hybrid </strong></h4>
<ul>
<li>If you are looking for Ecommerce mobile app development on both Android and iOS. Then it is best to go with <a href="https://www.hasotech.com/hybrid-mobile-application-development/">Hybrid Mobile App development</a>. Which are cost and time effective.</li>
<li>50% of Mobile apps are in Hybrid</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<h4><strong>Amazon is Using Hybrid </strong></h4>
<ul>
<li>The Ecommerce Gaint is using Hybrid Web view Mobile Application</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<h4><strong>Magento is Secured than Woocommerce and Shopify </strong></h4>
<ul>
<li>Magento is preferred than other frameworks When comes to Ecommerce App development,</li>
<li>Magento 2.x stands good but it is costlier</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 class="stripe_2"><a href="https://www.hasotech.com/know-about-mobile-app-development/">Know about Mobile App Development</a></h3>
<ul>
<li>
<h4><strong>Dedicated Hosting </strong></h4>
<ul>
<li>Dedicated hosting is must one for making Ecommerce Application to manage huge data</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Let us know your view about Ecommerce app development in comments. We are always happy to answer your questions.</p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/ecommerce-app-development/">Ten Unbelievable Facts About Ecommerce App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hasotech</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blog/ecommerce-app-development/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: web.hasotech.com @ 2022-10-26 12:06:10 by W3 Total Cache
-->